Chapter 400

Black Tongue (4)

◆

Vikir carried the fallen Kirko to her room.

Kkigigigig- gigigig- kkikkeog!

Pulling on the doorknob produced only a loud squeak, but the door refused to open.

This was because the hinges were covered in salt and rusted a lot.

‘…You live in a bad room.’

Vikir clicked his tongue. Well, the rooms where low-level guards live were all like that.

Vikir also lived in a room used by low-ranking guards below the rank of lieutenant until recently.

The door to the windowless stone chamber opened to reveal a simple scene: a desk and a bed.

Kirko groaned as she laid down on the hard, clean bed.

It was a side effect of releasing too much mana at once, combined with the blow from Black Tongue.

“….”

Vikir glanced down at her.

Suddenly, he remembered what Lt. Colonel Bastille had said when Kirko had been promoted to captain.

‘Strange fate, indeed. Children do resemble their parents after all.’

He had muttered this about Kirko, who had been taken by Black Tongue.

Perhaps it was because he knew her past.

Kirko’s parents, who had been used as a tool to drive a deeper wedge between prisoner and guard, and Black Tongue, who had been at the forefront of that process.

‘…I can see why Kirko’s name was not known.’

Kirko clearly has exceptional talent and qualities.

She could grow up to be an epic hero in the same league as Camus or Dolores.

But even so, the reason Vikir had never heard of her in the pre-Regression world was simple.

‘Because she was killed before she could become a hero. By Black Tongue.’

Kirko was born and raised in the worst place in the world, Nouvelle Vague.

And she had a psycho named Black Tongue as her enemy.

Perhaps it would be those two factors that would prevent her from making a name for herself in the future.

Vikir turned back to look down at Kirko, who was moaning on the bed.

“…………”

Kirko bit her lip tightly to stifle a groan, even as she fainted.

Kirko had shed so much sweat that the entire bed was damp.

Vikir sighed softly.

…Tag.

Vikir’s hand rested on Kirko’s stomach.

Tsutsutsutsutsuts…

Mana transfers from body to body.

Through his hands, Vikir transferred some of his own mana to Kirko.

The expression on Kirko’s face relaxed a little as she groaned in pain.

‘You made the leap to the higher realms too quickly, which is why it’s not a good idea to awaken in anger.’

Kirko’s anger at Black Tongue turned her into a Graduator.

This kind of awakening was actually not very healthy.

In the same way that lifting a weight you can’t handle or falling from a height can cause your muscles to tear, so does mana.

Awakening in anger is like trying to force a vein of mana to widen and burst.

While it may give you a momentary burst of power, the side effects are very similar to those of a mana surge.

Kirko’s ascension to the upper ranks of the class without becoming a cripple could only be described as a fluke, a miracle.

The odds were so slim that it was like a chimpanzee who knew nothing could sit in front of a piano and press random keys, but by chance the order would match and complete a classical symphony.

‘But that’s a good thing, because you’ve turned bad luck into good luck, and what happens next is up to you.’

Kirko, who should have been killed by Black Tongue, was saved by Vikir.

There was no way to know how this would play out in the future.

Vikir stabilised Kirko’s blood and re-aligned her mana veins.

It was a kindness not often bestowed upon others, and if Vikir had not been a swordmaster, he would not have even attempted it.

Then.

“…!”

As Vikir searched inside Kirko’s body, he noticed a strange phenomenon.

Mana flowing from Vikir’s body into Kirko’s.

It filled the wounds and holes in Kirko’s aura, filling it with more and more mana.

There was one hole, however, that Vikir’s mana could not fill.

Mana and stamina, which had seemed to be filling up at best, were leaking out again through that hole.

‘What is it?’

Vikir felt a tingling sensation and began to retrace the flow of mana.

“…! …! …! …!”

Kirko’s frown deepens as Vikir’s mana was finding its way to the leak.

She broke out in a cold sweat, and her moans of agony grew louder.

Kirko clenched the sheets and bent at the waist, but Vikir was unperturbed and continued to use his mana.

Finally, he found the leak.

Udeudeug-

Vikir laid Kirko upright and tore off the hem of her uniform.

The flesh on her lower abdomen, where the palm of Black Tongue’s hand had last touched, was black and dying.

And in the middle of it all, a black sphere.

A round, black, egg-like thing was attached to Kirko’s stomach, trying to take root.

“A leech.”

Vikir knew immediately what it was.

It was similar to those that had infested Black Tongue’s stone chamber.

Amazingly, the leech larva was growing larger and larger as it sucked Kirko’s blood and mana.

Squirming…

Hands, feet, and a head appeared, and soon a face formed.

It looked like it had been shaped into a smaller version of Kirko.

It grew larger and larger, feeding on mana and blood, until it was the shape and size of the Kirko of his childhood.

Except for the fact that everything was black from head to toe, it was almost believable that it was human.

If things continue like this, a black monster with the exact same shape as Kirko might be born.

…However.

“A leech with strange powers.”

Vikir ripped the leech from Kirko’s stomach and sealed the wound with the power of drought.

-Kkiyag!

The leech fell to the ground and was soon crushed to death by Vikir’s military boots.

“….”

Finally, Kirko’s complexion calmed.

The sweat had stopped, and her irregular moans and gasps had evened out.

Vikir murmured quietly.

“Have you ever heard of…, a leech larva that feeds on someone’s blood and mana and transforms into its own form?”

[No. I’ve never seen one].

Decarabia attached to his chest replied, rolling its eye.

Not even Vikir, who had lived through the Age of Destruction and seen it all, knew of it.

Even the long-lived Decarabia had never seen or heard of it.

‘…Perhaps Black Tongue is a new creature developed here in Nouvelle Vague.’

While there were some strange creatures on Earth, such as the Bone-Sucking Mosquito, there was no such thing as an unusual creature that steals the strength and appearance of its opponent.

[Hohoho… It’s going to be a big deal if this magical creature becomes known on earth, its uses are endless, even the demons will covet it].

This was an entirely new kind of monster that even the demons didn’t know about.

If a former Decarabia can say this much, it must be true.

Vikir’s eyes sparkled.

‘I kind of want this.’

Vikir had been thinking this ever since he had been told that the leeches he had met at his initiation were the pets of Lt. Colonel Black Tongue.

For the first time since coming to Nouvelle Vague, he wanted something.

Vikir began to formulate a plan to obtain the eggs of these leeches, which Black Tongue had developed and bred.

It was a private desire, separate from the public task of escaping.

‘Let’s organise my escape route around obtaining as many leech eggs as possible.’

In order to do so, he would have to deal with the Black Tongue Warden, who might be an obstacle to his escape.

There was no point in keeping him alive, as he was a danger whose identity, status, and affiliations were unknown.

Vikir hoped it would have a positive effect on Kirko’s future.

It was a bit of a debt of gratitude.

After all, she was Garam’s first and last love, who had lent Vikir his identity.

Seueug-

Just as Vikir was about to get out of bed.

….

Anxiously, Kirko grabbed Vikir by the collar.

She was sending him a faint glance through squinted eyes.

“….Garam”

Judging by the half-speech, she hadn’t fully regained her senses yet.

It was clear she was floating between dream and reality.

“Thank you.”

She turned her parched lips toward Vikir.

“…It was nothing.”

Vikir tried to turn away with a dry reply.

But.

“Can you not go?”

Kirko said, as if vomiting something inside.

The Ghost Castle of the Great Deep. A child born and raised here. A woman with nowhere to go.

“…I don’t want to be alone.”

Vikir looked down at Kirko in disbelief.

“I want to get out of here.”

Suddenly, he remembered the words that were always last on every page of Garam’s diary.

‘With her.’

But Vikir shook his head.

He was not Garam. Even here in Nouvelle Vague, he was only passing through, and he still had a long way to go before the final stage.

“You will not be alone.”

That’s all he could say.

“…Maybe.”

By the time Vikir finished the last word, Kirko’s hand, which was clutching his collar, had fallen to the bed.

…………

Kirko’s eyes were closed and she was fast asleep.

Vikir made sure that her complexion and breathing had completely stabilised before he left the room.

Thud.

The door closed after being held open for a moment.

It was much looser on its hinges than when it first opened.

Chapter 402

Jailbreaker (2)

◆

There was a gate.

It was massive and solid.

A perfect circle. The door was white at the top and black at the bottom, forming a Taegeuk pattern (as the big circle in the Korean flag, that is a Taegeuk pattern).

It was magnificent, overwhelming to behold, and once closed, it seemed to be impenetrable to anything in this world.

Diameter 70 meters. Thickness 5 meters. Weighing 6,535 tons. Made of mithril and adamantium, with some copper applied to the surface to prevent corrosion.

It was shaped like a rounded circle, and the world called it the Gate of Good and Evil.

It is the main entrance to Nouvelle Vague, the symbol of Nouvelle Vague, and the final dividing line between good and evil, inside and out.

Standing beneath the massive gate, which forms the ceiling at the very top of Nouvelle Vague’s castle, Vikir marveled.

“…Even if Nouvelle Vague were to fall to pieces, this gate would survive.”

[I agree. How did human technology build such a strong gate?]

When even Decarabia, whose nickname is “The Wailing Wall,” is impressed, it’s enough.

The Gate of Good and Evil, the symbol of the Nouvelle Vague, was much larger, stronger, and more magnificent than the vaults of the Bourgeois.

Even Vikir, who had seen it through to the end of the Annihilation War, couldn’t imagine it being destroyed.

[By the way, human, why are you staring at that door from earlier, are you really going to break it down, I don’t think human strength can break through it?]

At the frowning Decarabia’s words, Vikir spoke up in a low voice.

“Do you like to surf?”

[…?]

Decarabia rolled its eyes in confusion.

[Say what you’re thinking, don’t just keep your mouth shut all the time, it’s frustrating to behold!]

“Was it frustrating to behold?”

[…You’re not asking because you don’t know, are you?]

Vikir smiled weakly and looked away.

“I apologize. I’ve been disciplined to keep my mouth shut my whole life. All my talkative colleagues and brothers have been questioned.”

[…Sheesh].

Meanwhile, at the Gate of Good and Evil, a number of high-ranking guards, including Lt. Colonel Bastille, were waiting.

They were awaiting an entrance ceremony that would take place in a few hours.

“Finally, Warden Orca is coming back. He hasn’t been gone this long in a while. Over two years, I think?”

“And it’s good to see Colonels D’Ordume and Colonel Souaré back as well. It’s been a while since we’ve had the Big Three of Nouvelle Vague together.”

“And there are so many prisoners to escort that the Warden and the two Colonels had to go above all at once?”

“They say this is the biggest one yet. Security on the ground has collapsed and the criminal population has exploded.”

“Ground? Why would ground security break down? Is there another revolt?”

“I’m afraid someone in the Nouvelle Vague hasn’t been keeping up with the news. There’s a civil war. Not a group vs. group war, but a nation vs. nation war. Rumor has it that the demons have invaded.”

“That’s bullshit. Destruction and apocalypse are the stuff of religious books.”

“Well, whatever. The world is as chaotic as it was during the Warring States Period, and the Nouvelle Vague, which used to be a hellhole, is now a paradise.”

“By the way, did you hear? There’s a new Level Ten transfer coming in, sentenced directly to Level Nine without a trial. And she’s a girl. She’s even pretty.”

“Are you out of your mind? You’d have to be a monster to be sent straight to Level Nine without a trial, and that’s not even a woman.”

The prisoners were nervous and talking amongst themselves, each in their own way preparing for what was to come.

And, of course, Vikir was not interested in their conversation at all.

‘…It’s an opportunity when everyone’s eyes are focused on the news.’

The new prisoners were brought in wearing BDISSEM handcuffs.

The guards will pay close attention to the induction ceremony, both to keep an eye on the new prisoners and to keep them in line.

In the meantime, the supervision and control of the original prisoners is slightly weakened.

It’s a rhythm he’s mastered over the years as a guard.

Picking just the right moment, Vikir plans to assassinate Brigadier General BDISSEM.

Vikir recalled his past battles with her.

‘Oh, no, no… If I die… Prisoners’ restraints and iron bars… Everyone that loses their strength… That’s it… That’s it… ‘

These were the desperate words of a shriveled, dried-up BDISSEM crawling across the floor.

Her voice was so desperate that there was not a hint of false light in it.

‘When Brigadier General BDISSEM dies, all BDISSEM restraints lose their power, right?’

She had kindly spilled all her secrets, but Vikir had already guessed this before, due to several circumstances.

‘…I will kill Brigadier General BDISSEM while the guards’ attention is focused on the announcement, and the restraints on every prisoner in Nouvelle Vague will be lifted.’

BDISSEM’s handcuffs, shackles, and the bars of the cell that bind mana and power will be released.

The same goes for every prisoner in Nouvelle Vague.

When this happens, the prisoners who were once inducted will immediately turn on each other.

The guards will have to deal with the new prisoners first, and then a massive secondary wave of damage from the underground.

Level 1 on the 1st floor. Level 2 on the 2nd floor, Level 3 on the 3rd floor… As time goes on, stronger and stronger prisoners from the lower levels will rise up to the front gates of this place where word of mouth was spreading.

It was clear that there would be a riot of epic proportions, something that had never happened before in the history of Nouvelle Vague.

‘Crisis is opportunity, and every second of every day will be filled with life-changing opportunities.’

And Vikir planned to exploit the chaos, activate Poseidon, and break out of prison.

Only then would his escape be complete.

‘To do that, I’ll need to work on BDISSEM in advance.’

Vikir quietly stepped back.

With all the guards looking nervously at the Gate of Good and Evil, it was a good time to sneak around the back.

‘Wait, before I do that, I have to stop by….’

Vikir gave himself a little time before putting his plan into action.

He had two people to meet before that.

However, the first one came to him before he could get there.

“…!”

Vikir felt a hand on his back as he was being pulled backwards and spun around.

Kirko was glaring at him from behind.

Unable to guess what she was thinking, Vikir spoke in a casual tone.

“What are you doing here, Adjutant? I thought you were off-duty today.”

“…I can’t take the day off alone when my superior officer is on duty. I came out to help.”

She was fully dressed, right down to her uniform.

Vikir gave a small sigh.

“I was just heading to your room.”

For a moment, Kirko’s face flushed a faint red.

“Well, if you think my room is an easy place to go just because it happened once that night….”

At Kirko’s reaction, which seemed to indicate another misunderstanding, Vikir shook his head.

“No, don’t go back to your room tonight.”

“….”

Kirko’s face turned even redder.

“Is that an order? If you’re so adamant about it, I’ll have no choice but to obey you. I’m your subordinate, after all….”

“…?”

Vikir furrowed his brow for a moment as the conversation continued in a circle.

Then, in a voice as cold and sharp as ever, Vikir spoke to Kirko.

“Go to the fifth floor, to the gulper eel kennel, right now.”

“…?”

“Don’t ask me why. You are to wait there unconditionally until I tell you to go there. This is an order.”

Kirko shook her head, but the seriousness in Vikir’s tone made her nod.

“…I have a feeling something is about to happen, sir, I understand.”

Kirko was a smart person.

Her answer was trustworthy.

Vikir nodded and turned away.

The second hand moved relentlessly.

The predicted bloodshed.

Now it was really goodbye to the Nouvelle Vague.

◆

Dripping-

Dripping corridors.

Vikir walked through empty corridors and over the arched bridge that connected spire to spire.

Several lower-ranking guards stand guard and salute when they see Vikir.

He recognized them from his room as a low ranking guard.

Vikir returned their salute with a raised hand.

Then he said something.

“You are no longer on guard duty. Proceed to the fifth floor and stand by. The kennels will not be accessible at this time, so the closer you are, the better.”

The only way to survive what was about to happen.

Vikir said this to most of the guards he met.

The lower-ranking guards, hearing Vikir’s words, look at each other and shake their heads.

Jeobeog- jeobeog- jeobeog-

The black corridors and spiral staircases are endless.

An abyss 10,000 meters below the ocean floor. Vikir continues to fall into the dank, damp silence.

A deep-sea fish passes through a window made of flubber slime, emitting a dull glow.

Just two more turns around the corner in front of him and he would be in the room where BDISSEM was staying.

…Just then.

“Where do you think you’re going in such a hurry, Major ‘Rotten Dog’ Garam?”

An eerie voice came from the darkness up ahead.

“No, should I say Major ‘Night Hound’ Vikir, blah hathathat-”

A laugh he’d heard once before.

Vikir curled the corners of his mouth dryly.

“Okay. I was going to take a look at your face before I left.”

There was only one other being in Nouvelle Vague who sounded so unpleasant.

A man with sinisterly writhing black skin, eerie eyes, and teeth.

Lt. Colonel Black Tongue.

He was crouching in the darkness, waiting for Vikir.

Chapter 403

Jailbreaker (3)

◆

Jiiing- jing-

The magic sword Beelzebub vibrated on the wrist of his right hand.

It bared its teeth at the darkness in front of it, like the tip of a compass.

And.

“Where are you going in such a hurry, Major ‘Rotten Dog’ Garam?”

Lt. Colonel Black Tongue emerged from the darkness in the direction Beelzebub was pointing.

“No, should I say Major ‘Night Hound’ Vikir, hathathat-”

Black Tongue was much larger than he had been the last time they had seen him.

The muscles that wriggled throughout its body were clearly leeches, each and every fiber.

They were pulsing, stretching and contracting.

Black Tongue stretched out arms longer than his legs.

He crawled out of the darkness, gripping the floor and walls with palms that grew to be many times the size of his face.

“You’re not Garam, are you?”

“….”

“Common sense tells me it’s impossible for a junior garbage man to awaken one day and be promoted to senior guard.”

“….”

“The other assholes act like they’re hiding their power or something, but… I’m not. I’m the only common sense person here in Nouvelle Vague.”

Black Tongue laughed through his gaping mouth.

Vikir grinned back.

“You talk a lot for a man who tasted blood and recognized it.”

“What, did you just admit it, hathathat-”

“Yes.”

There was no point in disguising his identity on the way out.

Vikir summoned the power of the Basilisk, and the burn marks on his face were erased in an instant.

His bushy hair slicked back and the burn marks cleared away, revealing his true features.

Vikir revealed his true form, and Black Tongue lolled out in front of him.

“Prisoners are not my business, but I have no choice!”

At the same time.

Squeeze!

The darkness around Black Tongue began to move rapidly.

Just as his vision was about to get even darker, a large palm flew straight into his eyes.

“…!”

Vikir jerked his head back.

The rubbery fingers of Black Tongue flicked across his cheek.

Jjuuug-

Blood was drawn from the wound and sucked into Black Tongue’s fingers.

But.

Hududug- hududug- hududug-

Vikir’s blood was sucked towards Black Tongue’s fingers, but it quickly lost its strength and scattered to the ground.

Black Tongue had retrieved his vampiric power midway through.

“Now that I think about it, your blood looks a little strange. I think it will only be bad for my body if I suck it for no reason.”

Apparently, Black Tongue had noticed the frightening poison in Vikir’s blood.

Pis-

Vikir ducked low to avoid the flying palm behind him, and ran.

Severed hair flew behind him as Black Tongue’s body closed in on him.

Snapping his arms back, Vikir snatched Beelzebub from his wrist and aimed for Black Tongue’s empty body.

Then.

Zeeeeeeeing-

An annoying vibration burned his right arm.

The magic sword Beelzebub had been reacting abnormally since earlier.

‘…What is that?’

It’s a reaction he hasn’t seen since he got it, and while it doesn’t interfere with combat, something about it bothers him.

Vikir paused for a moment as he felt a vibration in his right hand.

“Welcome.”

The muscles of Black Tongue reacted sensitively to Vikir’s approach.

Every single muscle fiber leech stiffened, and all at once, they charged at Vikir.

It was like hundreds of arms sprouting from his body.

Vikir abandoned his approach without a word.

He swung Beelzebub and removed the leeches from the Black Tongue’s entire body, one by one.

…Peoeog! …peopeog! Hududug-

The blood, flesh, and guts of the bloody leeches began to scatter in all directions.

All the while, Beelzebub continued to tremble, but it didn’t seem to hinder the battle.

Meanwhile, while Vikir was swatting away the leeches flying through the air, Black Tongue untied the strap of the sack around his waist and began to shake out what was inside onto the ground.

It was a small ball, a leech egg.

The leeches hatched from the eggs and crawled across the floor toward Vikir.

‘This is the same stuff that was stuck to Kirko’s stomach.’

Vikir’s eyes sparkled.

The blood-sucking leeches on Black Tongue’s body weren’t particularly desirable, but those that stole the power and form of their opponents were personally desirable.

Black Tongue noticed Vikir’s gaze and spoke with a chuckle.

“This is an ultra-rare species that I have only recently succeeded in breeding and farming after a lifetime of research. Have you ever heard of a ‘doppelganger leech’?”

“No, I haven’t.”

“Hathathat- of course you haven’t, it’s a top secret even within the Nouvelle Vague!”

A purple tongue darted out of his mouth, and another mouth opened at the end of it.

“For your information, I was granted permission to use any prisoner or guard in the Nouvelle Vague as a guinea pig for my research and development of this leech.”

“Permission? Who gave you that right?”

“Who could it be? Orca, that cranky old man. He’ll do anything to increase the security of the Nouvelle Vague. He’s probably willing to work with the demons.”

Black Tongue chuckled.

“Actually, the research and development ended a long time ago~ I’d rather not call it done and have a little fun with it.”

Hearing that, Vikir nodded silently.

Suddenly, he remembered Kirko’s face.

She and her parents had lost everything, then, simply because of one psycho’s entertainment.

All the happiness of a family, all the joy and fulfillment of a parent, all the love and happiness a child deserves, all sucked out of them by a leech.

‘…Thank God, my dad’s not a bad person, my mom’s not a miserable person. I’m the only bad kid.’

He remembered Kirko’s words.

The Ghost Castle of the Great Deep. A child born and raised here. A woman with nowhere to turn.

“….”

Vikir took a deep breath and let it out.

Huh.

When the hot exhalation had been drawn out, the vibration of Beelzebub on his right arm had stopped cold.

Night Hound had decided to be a dirty dog for now.

“I will take your leech and spread the word about it, but not now.”

Vikir said briefly.

At the same time, Beelzebub’s sword protruded from his wrist, scratching sharply at the surrounding area.

…Pakang! Kkadeudeudeudeug! Deuleuleuleug! Kkigigigigigigigigig-

The tip of the awl sliced through the stone floor and stone walls.

Puff-puff-puff-puff-puff!

The huge number of crawling leeches burst into flames, all of them dead.

“….”

Black Tongue’s mouth snapped open for a moment.

He was astonished at Vikir’s ability to kill all those tiny leeches in the pitch darkness.

“Apparently you’re a much trickier prisoner than I thought, well, the fact that you removed the BDISSEM handcuffs was unusual. Hathathat-”

But Black Tongue was still slacking off.

The source of its slack was soon revealed.

“…!”

Vikir narrowed his eyes.

Black Tongue had slowly drawn back, and around him, the black balls were beginning to appear.

‘You laid this out for me, knowing I’d come for BDISSEM.’

Vikir eyed the corridor that stretched out beyond the darkness.

The leeches were so swollen that they could easily fit one or two people.

They can be seen clinging to the floor, walls, and ceiling, blocking Vikir’s path.

“Don’t worry. I didn’t tell anyone, and it wouldn’t help if the idiots came.”

Black Tongue smirked.

“My children are far more competent. Here, look. These are new species I’ve invented. Oil-sucking leeches and body heat-sucking leeches! They’re a bit difficult to breed, and they’re a minor species, so we won’t be able to mass produce them.”

Both types of leeches were plumped up and pointing their snouts in this direction.

And then.

Peopeong!

The leeches began to squirt out what was inside.

The oil-sucking leeches spewed out the oil they had stored in their guts, and the heat-sucking leeches spewed out the heat they had stored in their guts in the form of flames.

The hot oil bubbled, boiled, and flew, eventually creating a massive inferno.

It was enough firepower to make even Vikir want to avoid a head-to-head fight.

Peopeopeopeong!

Oil and flame swept down the straight corridor in a loud explosion.

The dampness that had been lingering dried up, leaving nothing but charred stone and ash all around.

“Hathathat, what a shame, a few more leeches and the fire would have lasted a little longer, but was it enough?”

Black Tongue muttered as he stared out over the thick soot.

But.

“…!”

Black Tongue’s eyes narrowed.

As the flames and smoke cleared, he could see something up ahead.

It was a blazing black light, an inferno.

It was Vikir, using Decarabia as a shield.

“Hmm? Is this all? Just when things were getting a little hot, it’s over.”

“Hathathat- you really do piss people off.”

A black line of veins sprouted on Black Tongue’s forehead.

Then, he lowered his stance to face Vikir in front of him.

“Good. You win. I have no choice but to reveal my bottom line.”

Black Tongue pulled out a longsword, roughly sheathed in bandages.

The handle was wrinkled and hard, like a whole piece of meat dried into jerky.

Black Tongue gripped it carefully, the dirty bandages tattered underneath.

Vikir asked.

“Were you a sword wielder? I’ve never heard of it.”

“Maybe, it has rarely been used against humans.”

Black Tongue grinned and took off all the bandages that had been wrapped in place of the sheath.

A moment later, the hideously distorted hilt of the sword came into Vikir’s view.

“!”

At the same time, Vikir realized why Beelzebub had been sending subtle vibrations to his right arm all along.

“…I never knew that sword was here.”

It was the resonance of his own kind.

Chapter 406

Jailbreaker (6)

◆

…Boom!

The triple-layered steel door has been smashed to pieces.

All that remained was a grid-like wire mesh made of BDISSEM.

On the other side of the grid, on the bed, Brigadier General BDISSEM sat up with a shocked expression on her face.

“What is it? What is the commotion?”

She had the appearance of a young girl, her body fully recovered from the earlier incident.

BDISSEM frowned at Vikir as he strode in through the shattered doorway.

Her gaze lingered on the rank patch on Vikir’s uniform chest patch.

“What the hell, where does a Major get the nerve to come into my room like this, are you insane?”

But when Vikir took off his hat, revealing his bare face, BDISSEM’s expression turned white.

…Peong!

The mattress of the bed exploded.

She flailed as if in a fit and soon jumped up on the bed.

“You, you bastard! Didn’t you escape?”

But that’s just wishful thinking on her part.

It was just an excuse made up without properly checking to avoid being reprimanded.

Her mind flashed back to her conversation with D’Ordume.

‘Where did the prisoner go?’

‘He’s dead!’

‘…Dead? Then where’s the body?’

‘…He went out to sea in an gulper eel.’

‘Then he’s not dead.’

‘He didn’t seem to have a clue about the circulation currents that lead to the surface, so he was bound to get caught in a trap current, and he’d be stuck in the deep for the rest of his life.’

‘…Did it happen? It definitely sounds like you didn’t see it.’

‘Yes, yes, yes, yes, I saw him ride an gulper eel out of the hole in the wall before I passed out!’

‘…You’re sure you saw the last of him, aren’t you?’

‘No, that’s right, who do you think I am, and don’t you dare look at me like that when it’s none of my business…!’

Of course, BDISSEM never saw what happened to Vikir in the end, because she passed out.

…This was the result.

The cold sweat that had gathered under her chin was dripping down like small raindrops.

Her eyes and eyebrows drooped downward, her focus dazedly unfocused and unsteady.

BDISSEM shuddered and shook as if she were an Aspen-type Ent.

“Well, well, well, whatever it is, you’re finished, and I’m calling for D’Ordume and Souaré right now!”

It seemed like she was trying to buy time by hiding behind the BDISSEM wire fence she had made.

But.

Udeudeug!

With a simple touch of his hand, Vikir snapped the BDISSEM wire with a snap.

Psssssss…

The stem of the dead and dying plant crumbled like a burnt matchstick.

The stem of BDISSEM dried up where Vikir touched it, a hole in the wire mesh just big enough for one person to fit through.

Jeobeog- jeobeog- jeobeog-

Vikir stumbled through the gaping hole.

“Uh… uuuuhhhhhh….”

BDISSEM clung to the back of the bed as the horrors of the past returned.

The hound stalked toward her, red eyes glowing in the darkness.

“Stretch your neck.”

It was time for the death sentence to be carried out.

But BDISSEM does not accept her fate as an innocent bystander easily.

“Hey! Even if it’s like this, I’m also the 5 Warden! As long as I don’t let my guard down, I won’t get caught!”

Giant kelp leaves grew up around her.

Each one was a seaweed whip with a powerful binding force.

Chalalalag!

In a few short moments, the kelp leaves formed a dense forest of seaweed and began to wrap around Vikir.

“No use.”

Vikir swung Beelzebub and cut off all the kelp leaves.

But BDISSEM didn’t attack Vikir.

It simply glided across the floor, using the seaweed leaves as a surfboard.

“Hohohoho – no one can catch me if I run away with it!”

BDISSEM shouted confidently.

But Vikir didn’t react much to her words.

He just quietly asked a question.

“…No one?”

And as soon as the words were finished, something wrapped around BDISSEM’s body as it slipped through the torn door.

Syulolololog-

It was a vine of plants.

“…?”

BDISSEM looked dazed as she hung upside down in the air.

Kkudeudeug- kkudeodeog- basasag-

The slippery kelp leaves she was riding on dried up in an instant.

Seumeolseumeolseumeolseumeolseumeolseumeolseumeol…

The roots of a plant she’d never seen before began to grow out of the tiny kelp flakes and onto the board.

<Daylily of the Blood Tree>

Danger Rating: S

Size: ?

Found in: Deep in the polar hell, ‘Inaccessible Zone (Blood Swamp, Flesh-splattered Zone of Area 4)’

-Also known as ‘Blood Swamp Daylily’ or ‘Blood Swamp Nightmare’

A mysterious plant that floats on the churning waters of the Bloodswamp, at the mouth of the ‘Lake of Blood’ in the depths of Hell.

Even in the blood swamp, where everything sinks because there is no buoyancy, you can somehow see them floating.

It is the strongest and most fearsome of all the flora and fauna that inhabit the Blood Lake, and its insatiable appetite and gluttony are feared even by its own kind.

It is said that a single Daylily sprouting from a single seed of this plant once grew so large that it brought humanity to the brink of destruction.

This plant, so bizarre that it has no place in the human world, is called the Daylily of Blood Tree.

The seeds that Vikir had scattered at the entrance had sucked in the dampness of the Nouvelle Vague and germinated!

“Huh?”

BDISSEM gasped in astonishment, gulping down the air.

The plants of the Human World and the Demon World were in a perfect food chain.

For the demonic beasts that have adapted to the harsh and barren environment of the Demon World, the plants of the Human World are merely fragile and defenseless prey.

Therefore, all plants in the Human world have an instinctive fear of demonic plants.

BDISSEM was no different.

“Aaah… aaah….”

BDISSEM realized with certainty the source of the unexplained fear she had felt when Vikir had first demonstrated the power of Starvation Drought.

But by the time she realized, it was too late.

Her body was already wrapped around the daylily’s stalks, draining her of moisture at an alarming rate.

“Daylily of Blood Tree are notoriously vicious among demons, for in colonies where they grow, all other demons around them wither and die, even those in the Human World.”

Vikir looked up at BDISSEM, who had been captured by a Daylily vine.

Even the mighty seaweed, adapted to the depths of the sea, was no match for the daylily.

Vikir stepped in front of the hanging creature.

…Thwack!

A vicious grip pressed down hard on both of her cheeks.

“Uuh! Uub!”

As the insides of the cheeks dug into his upper and lower teeth, BDISSEM was forced to open her mouth.

At that point, Vikir placed something in her mouth.

“Now, if you don’t do as I say, I’m going to stick this in your mouth.”

“Hm, hmph!”

BDISSEM was stunned.

A shadowy figure loomed before her eyes: a handful of seeds.

Walgeulag-

Daylily of Blood Tree. Countless seeds that had yet to germinate.

If all of them made it into BDISSEM’s mouth and traveled straight to her stomach, it was obvious what would happen next.

“Uu… Uuuuuuuu….”

Tears of terror welled up in BDISSEM’s eyes as she imagined the horrifying scenario.

“Please, please let m….”

BDISSEM’s face was covered in tears and she was smearing her lips.

When Vikir loosened his grip slightly, she could hear her words clearly.

“Please let me live… I’ll do anything.”

It was all she could do to say, knowing from previous battles that she had no chance of winning.

Vikir nodded.

“It would be quicker to just kill you, as usual.”

“Hic!”

BDISSEM’s face turned a deep blue.

But Vikir moved the sword of the awl and looked the other way.

“…But there’s one more thing I want. If you do it right, I might have a way to save your life.”

“What, what is it? What is it!”

BDISSEM who had gone from hell to heaven in an instant, asked breathlessly.

Vikir continued.

“I want two things. First, its original purpose. To remove the handcuffs, shackles, and cage.”

“It’s possible! It’s possible, but… can’t you do it yourself? I saw you break them earlier.”

“Not mine, but those of every prisoner here in Nouvelle Vague.”

At those words, BDISSEM’s expression hardened.

Now she understand.

Why did this man not escape from prison even after being released from his restraints.

Or why he’d turned himself in in the first place and walked into this hellhole.

He wasn’t trying to break his restraints, he was trying to break everyone’s restraints, the very system that controls individuals.

Rattling…

BDISSEM was avoiding Vikir’s gaze, desperately squinting her pupils, which were so shaky they couldn’t even focus properly.

The giant dog. A monster with burning eyes is right in front of her.

Clutching tightly at her life and death.

It’s so frightening, so terrifying, that it makes her mind go blank.

She has no idea what kind of chaos this creature is trying to unleash on Nouvelle Vague.

It has no purpose, no meaning, nothing but sheer terror.

“You don’t want to do it? Want to make it a little easier?”

Vikir shoved a Daylily seed into BDISSEM’s mouth, and she struggled, making a dying sound.

“I’ll do it, I’ll do it, I’ll do it, I’ll do it, let me do it!”

“Good. Then second.”

Vikir whispered the next order into BDISSEM’s ear.

“Wait outside the window of the kennel on the 5th floor, a person will come out. That person….”

Hearing that, BDISSEM nodded frantically.

Vikir nodded with satisfaction.

“You know what happens if these two promises are not fulfilled?”

“…Uh, what happens?”

“You will definitely see me again, but after that, I leave it to your imagination. Hehehe….”

Vikir laughed grimly.

He realized that this was probably the first time in his life that he had ever laughed out loud.

And the effect of Vikir’s laughter was profound.

“Hiiiiicc….”

BidisM’s crotch turned yellow and soaked through her pants and top.

The sight was horrifying.

Vikir jabbed the awl into BDISSEM’s throat.

“Now, go ahead and fulfill your first promise.”

“Ah, okay, wait.”

BDISSEM squeezed her eyes shut.

…Pass!

After a few seconds, she opened them again.

“Done.”

It was deceptively easy and quick.

Vikir frowned.

Was that all there was to it?

All of the systems that had kept the Nouvelle Vague alive for so long had been wiped out?

In such a ridiculously short amount of time?

Are you really telling me that all of the nullifying mana and physical force cuffs, shackles, and cages are gone?

“You’re not trying to trick me….”

Vikir was just about to reveal a glimmer of doubt.

…Thud!

The floor rumbled once more.

A heavy shockwave that had never been experienced before. Short and thick.

The instincts of a seasoned hound screamed out.

‘The BDISSEM restraints are gone.’

Vikir opened his senses and quickly scanned his surroundings.

Indeed, all of the BDISSEM materials in the vicinity were blackened and dead.

Even the fragments he’d slipped into his pockets just in case, and all of the BDISSEM that were a considerable distance away.

At this rate, the handcuffs, shackles, chains, and cages that held the prisoners downstairs would surely all be dead as well.

“It, it’s true, I’ve unlocked them, from the 1st floor to the 9th floor, believe me, please!”

BDISSEM cries out in a pathetic voice.

The truth of her words was being conveyed both audibly and visually.

Vikir nodded.

“…Yes. I guess so.”

Ordinarily, he would have preferred to cut off BDISSEM’s breathing for good, but she still had some use.

Night Hound was done hunting, and he turned away without another word.

The escape plan had reached the halfway point.

A massive uprising unprecedented in history.

The collapse of the Nouvelle Vague has just begun.

Chapter 407

End game (1)

◆

Abysmal.

It was the best word to describe the current situation in Nouvelle Vague.

Just a few hours, minutes, or seconds ago, everything was normal.

The guards were controlling the prisoners with their weapons, and the prisoners were languishing under the weight of dreadful restraints that drained their mana and strength.

Then, at a moment that no one remembers clearly, just a few seconds ago.

Thud.

The handcuffs, shackles, and cages that had held the prisoners’ wrists, ankles, and entire bodies were gone.

It happened simultaneously throughout the vast Nouvelle Vague.

“…?”

Both the guards and the prisoners were stunned into silence.

They had no idea what had just happened.

Why is this happening now? Is something wrong with my eyes? Is it a small accident? Is it something that only happened to me? A small anomaly that only happened in this area?

…But it soon became clear that it was not.

All the handcuffs, shackles, and cages in the entire Nouvelle Vague were gone.

The cuffs that threatened to crush their wrists, the shackles that threatened to snap their ankles, the cages that made it impossible for them to go outside.

All the restraints that had held them down for what seemed like eons were gone.

It was as if all the hardships and adversity had been a dream.

The prisoners felt mana flowing through their bodies.

Strength returned.

Desire and anger, long forgotten and thoroughly castrated, ignited in their hearts.

The first to adjust to the new reality were the prisoners who were in the midst of their entrance ceremony.

“Huh? What is this? My mana is flowing!”

“BDISSEM’s handcuffs are off!”

“Kiyasuuuu! I don’t know what it is, but it’s great!”

“Die, you bastards!”

The prisoners on the blade bridge suddenly turned around and began to pounce on the guards.

The other prisoners rose to their feet as well.

“Aaahhhh! Kill all the guards first!”

“Beat them to death! Kill them all!”

“Seth them on fire! Burn them all!”

“Open the Gate of Good and Evil! Let’s get out of here!”

“Fifth floor! There’s an gulper eel on the fifth floor! Let’s take the eels and get out!”

They had been living like worms for so long that their freedom was short-lived, and they quickly returned to their old savagery.

Nature never changes.

…Just then.

Kwakwang!

With a tremendous crash, the prisoners at the induction hall fell to their deaths.

Ku-gugugugugu…

In the midst of the bloody scene, in the midst of a thick cloud of sulfur, two wardens picked themselves up.

D’Ordume. And Souaré.

They each had a prisoner lying on the ground, hands and feet covered in blood.

Shake-

D’Ordume said, tossing the prisoner’s body in his hands.

“Get your heads out of your asses. This is ten thousand meters deep. You won’t make it out of here anyway. We may be outnumbered right now, but reinforcements will be coming from the ground soon. What will you do then?”

He was right.

Even if the prisoners rioted and somehow overpowered the guards, they wouldn’t be able to get out of here.

Even if they were freed, there would be no way out of the 10,000-meter deep trench, and as soon as Brigadier General Flubber abandoned the waterproofing, the place would be flooded.

By this time, Souaré, who was beside him, had brushed off the corpses stuck to the back of her heels.

“Hohoho- I’ll give you a chance now. If you stand by this side and help suppress the riot, I’ll let you become a sucker shark. I’ll cut your workload and give you a reduced sentence. We’ll even make you a junior guard, of course, first come first served~.”

The momentum exuded by the two wardens was overwhelming.

Within seconds of their appearance, they had beaten dozens of prisoners to a bloody pulp.

Furthermore, behind their backs stood the Gate of Good and Evil, a gigantic wall that was intimidating to look at.

Gulp.

From among the prisoners came those who swallowed dry saliva.

If they voluntarily submitted themselves now, their lives would be much easier in the future.

Not only will the labor be easier, but the quality of the food will be incomparably better.

Since they won’t be able to open that Gate of Good and Evil…, wouldn’t it be better to stick to the guards’ side and help suppress it and score points?

Everyone was thinking the same thing.

They finally let out their pent-up anger and hatred, but there must be a heavy and harsh price to pay for the brief moment of exaltation and freedom.

“….”

“….”

“….”

As the excitement wore off, reason returned.

The prisoners slowly began to realize the reality of their situation.

After all, it is impossible to cross the Gate of Good and Evil.

The prisoners at Nouvelle Vague knew this from years of experience.

D’Ordume and Souaré, seeing the momentum of the prisoners, which had been so fiery just moments before, cool down, realized that the situation might be easier to calm down than they thought.

But.

“The key! Here’s the key to the front door!”

An unidentified shout came from somewhere.

At the same time, something was flung into the middle of the battlefield.

A sword sculpture with an impressive white lower part of the blade, a black middle part, a reddish upper part, and a spiral embossed pattern.

…Peog!

It flew and lodged in the high ceiling in full view of all the prisoners.

A few knowledgeable prisoners opened their eyes wide.

“Is that the key to the main entrance?”

It looked like the horns of a unicorn, and it was a fragment of Orwell’s Sword of Winter!

It was a legendary sword that only those who have attained the highest level of mastery are allowed to wield it, and it once belonged to Winston, the principal of Colosseo Academy.

D’Ordume and Souaré’s eyes widened at the sight of it.

“…A key!?”

“It’s the key to the Gate of Good and Evil! Why is it here…!?”

A long time ago, Winston, the principal of Colosseo Academy, and Orca, the warden of Nouvelle Vague, worked together to capture a prisoner.

To commemorate that imprisonment, they gave each other two keys, one for the ocean floor and one for the surface, but why is one of them here now?

“Who put the key in here!”

Souaré scanned the area with sharp eyes, but there was no way she could identify a single culprit in a scene that had already been torn apart by a prisoner riot.

D’Ordume shouted at the prisoners in disbelief.

“I don’t know why the key is here, but it doesn’t change anything, and there’s no way you can get out of here once you’ve unlocked the Gate of Good and Evil…!”

But D’Ordume didn’t get to finish his sentence.

Waaaaaaaah!

A huge roar rushed in, drowning out D’Ordume’s voice.

Things don’t always work out so calmly and rationally.

The prisoners’ eyes, which had paused for a moment at the confirmation of the key’s existence, flipped once more.

Collective madness. As long as it has an excuse to ignite, it explodes regardless of whether it is valid or not, whether small or large.

“It’s the key, it’s the key!”

“That will open the Gate of Good and Evil!”

“Aaaahhhhhh! That thing will take us to the surface!”

“If you have the key, that’s it! Kill them all!”

They were now attaching sanctity to a tool called a ‘key’.

D’Ordume said in disbelief.

“Hey! Wake up! That key is only half a key! And opening the Gate of Good and Evil will only let the water rush in! Use common sense! What do you think you’re capable of in these deep seas…!”

“Hey, hey, man. Stop it, do you think they have the intelligence to think of that shit?”

Souaré stepped forward in annoyance.

She kicked one of the charging Level 1 prisoners to death with her heel, then pulled out the sledgehammer on her back.

…BANG!

A large prisoner who had been charging like a wild boar lost his head to Souaré’s sledgehammer.

The battle had begun.

The elite guards who had gathered to control the news of the incident launched a merciless killing spree.

“No need to look the other way!”

“Kill them outright!”

“They are the ones who couldn’t even eat a bowl of blood porridge anyway!”

The prisoners who had come up from the lower floors, even if they had regained their strength, their bodies were still weakened by the harsh labor and poor food.

No matter how crazy and outnumbered they were, they couldn’t pull off a coup once the guards regained their senses.

Moreover, the presence of the two wardens, rampaging like wagons in front of a line of elite guards, was overwhelming.

Kuleuleuleuleuleug! Kwakwakwakwakwang!

The axe blades on D’Ordume’s forearms created a vortex of aura that minced nearby prisoners like fish meat.

Kkulleong… kkuleuleuleug… bugeulbugeulbugeul-

The ground beneath Souaré’s feet melted away, and soon became a boiling lava that engulfed the prisoners around her.

Starting from the two who stood at the forefront of the guard camp, numerous prisoners were being torn apart.

Even the largest of men were crushed, and those who moved the fastest were caught and killed.

The two Colonels, intent on becoming the next head warden of Nouvelle Vague, were turning everything in their path to pulp.

One against a hundred. A thousand at a time. Ten Thousand Enemies

A long trail of killing centered on where D’Ordume and Souaré stood.

A bloodbath.

No prisoner had ever crossed it before.

Naturally, the morale of the guards behind the two wardens was high.

“It’s the Colonels!”

“The symbol of the Nouvelle Vague! The backbone of the fighting force!”

“They really are heroes, fighting for the position of next head warden!”

“We can do it, all the prisoners are welcome to come as many times as they want!”

The guards who were holding the induction ceremony, or who had almost suppressed the prisoners’ coup from the lower floors, were cheering with a hundred times of courage.

…However.

From far below came the voice of a terrified guard.

“Le, Level 9! Level 9, the prisoners from the 9th floor are coming up, ahhhhhhh!”

It was a report that brought a chill to the already heated atmosphere of the guards’ camp.

Chapter 409

End game (3)

◆

Rumbling…

A heavy aftermath shook the entire cavity.

The giant crocodile’s body sank to the ground.

…And all in one blow!

Colonel D’Ordume. A candidate to become the next head of the prison.

One of Nouvelle Vague’s top five wardens, and the one who was in charge of the actual force, had been knocked out so quickly.

Everyone froze, mouths agape, in shock at what had happened.

….

Prisoners and guards alike fell silent, a brief pause in the chaos of the battlefield.

Especially Lt. Colonel Bastille, D’Ordume’s direct line, who was so stunned that he thought his heart might leap out of his throat.

“Co, Co, Colonel D’Ordume?”

But D’Ordume, head down on the ground, was speechless.

Judging by the long tongue hanging out of his ear over the corner of the pit, he was either stunned or dead.

…The watching guards could only hope it was not the latter.

Meanwhile.

Vikir removed his hat, revealing his face to Nouvelle Vague once more.

“Good evening, ladies and gentlemen of the Nouvelle Vague.”

It was the reappearance of Night Hound, who was officially supposed to have escaped and met a miserable end in the middle of the sea.

In the hands of this brilliant escapee was the key to the “Gate of Good and Evil” the symbol of Nouvelle Vague, the Sword of Winter, Orwell.

It was now clear who had been responsible for the chaos at the entrance earlier.

Upon seeing it, Lt. Colonel Bastille’s face was once again colored with astonishment.

“What the hell is that thing doing there, surely it belongs to Sir Winston, the principal of Colosseo Academy?”

It was even more shocking that Orwell, the Sword of Winter, was here than that Night Hound, who had escaped and was thought to be dead, was alive.

But no matter how many questions he asked, Vikir didn’t answer them.

Then.

Swoosh.

Beyond the flames and vapor, huge shadows loomed.

Prisoners from Level 9 and Level 8 had somehow found their way to Vikir’s side.

“Too bad. D’Ordume was my prey.”

“Kid, you’re a bit of a fighter. What’s with the guard uniform?”

“Do you know anything about Orca, and when the old man is coming?”

“I can knock D’Ordume down with one blow, if I eat well enough….”

Prisoners of all shapes and sizes surrounded Vikir.

Their eyes were all fixed on the key in Vikir’s hand.

Vikir spoke briefly.

“My friends. I have no intention of monopolizing this key.”

If he did, he wouldn’t have thrown it in the middle of this mess earlier.

Once more, Vikir tossed the key into the distance.

It flew off in a parabolic arc and landed right in the center of where the prisoners and guards were standing.

Vikir had no intention of picking it up again.

It had served its purpose by drawing attention to itself twice in this desperate situation.

“Oooh! It’s a real key!”

“Open the Gate of Good and Evil!”

“Let’s go out of this nostalgic land!”

“Wait, aren’t we supposed to steal the gulper eel first?”

The prisoners scrambled to pick up the key.

Vikir watched and knew it was time to slip away.

As they all looked up, Night Hound was staring down into the depths.

‘…Now is the time to go to Level Ten.’

There, surrounded by blue lava, laid the sphere that would become humanity’s final weapon, Poseidon.

While everyone’s eyes were on the Gate of Good and Evil on the first floor, those with brains are eyeing the Gulper Eel Kennel on the 5th floor, and the all-seeing Regressor has his sights set on Poseidon on the 10th floor.

Vikir threw the key away, turned and ran away.

The eyes of prisoners as well as the guards’ were turned to the Gate of Good and Evil and its key.

It was clear that there would be a shower of blood where the key fell.

‘…I am glad I brought the key. Nothing’s better than a distraction.’

For guards, as well as prisoners, there was nothing more intriguing than the key of a prison lock.

Vikir remembered the face of Professor Sadi, who had briefly held his hand when he had confronted Winston at the Academy.

After all, it was her taking away Winston’s sword, Orwell, that had made this operation possible, so it would be nice to say hello if they ever met.

‘…If she’s alive.’

The woman who used to go by the name Ms. Ouroboros had completely disappeared after the events of Winston and the Fallen, and her whereabouts were unknown.

But the words Sadi had spoken to him as she handed him the Sword of Winter Orwell were still fresh in his mind.

‘Hand it over.’

‘Yes, I’ll give it to you – I’m sure I’ll need the key to the front gate, but… there’s another way.’

‘….’

‘Can you promise me one more thing in return, though?…If there’s ever a chance, please take it out with you.’

‘…Okay. If you get a chance.’

‘That would be great.’

Vikir needed to go to Level 10 once more, if only to fulfill his promise to Sadi.

Her request was one that could be granted while Poseidon was up and active.

Vikir sprinted down the slope, feeling all eyes on him.

And then.

…Pow!

A sharp rock protruded from the wall and grazed Vikir’s cheek.

“…!”

Vikir threw his head back to dodge.

If he hadn’t, the momentum of his run could have exploded his head with that one hit.

As Vikir turned his head, he saw the creature that had moved the boulder standing in front of him.

…There was just one person. One who hadn’t been distracted by the keys.

Colonel Souaré. One of the two colonels who represent the twin walls of the Nouvelle Vague

She stood blocking the entrance to the stairs leading downstairs, shooting Vikir a cold stare.

Souaré glanced back and forth between Vikir and D’Ordume lying behind him.

“You’re the one I put in solitary confinement, If you think about it that way, don’t you owe me something?”

“Ah, I see. Would you like me to repay you?”

“When you are capable.”

Souaré tilted her head, and Vikir nodded approvingly.

“Of course.”

At the same time, Souaré’s sledgehammer and Vikir’s sword clashed.

…Boom!

A heavy shockwave stretched out like countless snakes spreading out.

Flames, oil slicks, gas, and dirt swirled around, creating a terrifying sight.

Kwakwang! Kkaang- ttang! Ujijig! Kkang- kwakwakwang! Kkadeudeudeug!

The magic sword Beelzebub and the heavy sledgehammer were exchanging blows at an alarming rate.

Souaré was pushing hard enough to make the hammer glow red, but she couldn’t avoid being pushed backwards.

‘What kind of strength…!’

She could see why D’Ordume had been destroyed by the blow.

Her opponent was a seasoned warrior who had strength for strength, speed for speed, and nothing was missing.

Souaré realized that she wasn’t going to win in a head-to-head fight, so she drew back.

Peopeopeopeopeong!

A wave of lava rose up from where she’d stomped and slammed into Vikir.

Vikir slashed at the lava, but it quickly hardened and turned to dust.

It was followed by a second and third wave of rocks.

“…That’s a troublesome pattern.”

This wasn’t an attack designed to hurt Vikir, but to waste time.

Souaré sensed that Vikir was trying to make his way downstairs after wreaking havoc with some sort of purpose.

“I don’t know what you’re after, but give it up, I’m good at defense.”

Souaré smirked and blew out a puff of cigarette smoke.

Each of Nouvelle Vague’s twin walls had its own specialty.

D’Ordume for offense, Souaré for defense.

D’Ordume specialized in frenzied, sweeping attacks, while Souaré drew in the surrounding rocks and minerals to create a shield that stacked infinitely.

The personalities of these two were very clear and distinct.

Vikir furrowed his brow as he watched Souaré’s shield of layered rocks and alloys.

‘The compatibility isn’t very good?’

After all, Souaré was one of the formidable foes he needed to defeat here.

It seemed that the time he’d gained by using all his strength to neutralize D’Ordume would be wasted.

‘It can’t be helped. I’ll lose a lot of time, but I have to be sure to step on it….’ was thinking Vikir to himself.

Kwa-kwang!

A loud explosion erupted from the front.

It was a shockwave so powerful that the lowly guards standing around burst their eardrums and spurted blood.

“Huh!”

Souaré’s head whipped around as if it was being ripped from between her shoulders.

She was thrown out into a trajectory that flattened her to the ground and slammed her into the wall, where she promptly blacked out.

She had the same ending as D’Ordume.

“…?”

Vikir looked up from the dense dust.

A slender shadow stood over Souaré’s face.

There was a murmur of voices around him.

“Hic! Hey, it’s the newest prisoner!”

“Is it that bitch? The one who was supposed to be admitted to Level 10?”

“She came straight in without a trial, and I can’t believe she sent Souaré away in one fell swoop.”

“Another monster, I see.”

Vikir’s mind raced with information that he had previously passed over without much thought.

‘Oh, and did you hear, there’s a new one coming in, sentenced to Level 9 without a trial, and she’s a girl. They even said she was pretty.’

‘Are you out of your mind? She would be a monster of monsters if she were to be thrown straight into Level 9 without a trial and that’s if she’s a woman.’

The newest prisoner to arrive was the one who made the most noise.

Black hair mixed with silver, triangular pointed ears, and an ashen face.

Big, clear eyes like a lake in bitter eyes.

She looked up at Vikir and smiled.

“Long time no see, Husby.”

A new Night Fox had taken over from Akwilla, the Night Fox.

It was Aiyen.

Chapter 410

End game (4)

◆

Ballak.

A warrior tribe of Le Rouge Et Le Noir Mountain.

Along with Ironblooded Swordsman Baskerville, they wielded great influence throughout the Western Continent.

Aiyen is the chieftain of the Ballak and a warrior unrivaled among her people.

The daughter of Chieftain Akwilla and the young blood who succeeded her, she possessed the talents and qualities to become a Graduator at just 17 years of age.

Ordinarily, she would have been gone when the Red Death swept through the jungle, but the butterfly effect created by Vikir changed the future.

‘…But even so, I never thought I’d see you here again.’

Vikir’s mouth was half open at the unexpected outcome.

Then Aiyen smirked and nudged Vikir in the side with an elbow.

“I knew you’d be here.”

“….”

“Though I didn’t realize you were still wearing the leash.”

She smiled wickedly at the worn choker around Vikir’s neck.

Meanwhile, Vikir looked back at Souaré, who was rolling to the ground in a heap of rocks.

Surely it was Aiyen who had kicked Souaré in the head just a moment ago.

“What happened?”

“What, are you asking why I’m here, or how did I get so strong in such a short time?”

“…Both.”

Aiyen pointed a thumb behind him as Vikir asked.

“We can talk about the details as we go, aren’t we in a hurry?”

“….”

Aiyen was right.

Vikir quickly assessed the situation and left.

Aiyen knocked out two guards who stood in their way and took their bows and arrows from them.

Then she followed Vikir and spoke in a low voice.

“I, too, have been in the Hell Tree.”

“…!”

Vikir remembered when he had fought Amdusias so many years ago.

The tips of Amdusias’s horns bore the unmistakable marks of arrows.

And Aheul, whom he had met in the Hell Tree, had said the same thing.

‘I’m worried about what happened to the other tribe members. Especially my brother and the tribal leader… We were able to survive at least by falling here. If… If those who couldn’t come here suffered even more misery…… ‘

Amdusias, the Worldview Absorber, raided the Ballak’s territory and imprisoned them in the Hell Tree.

Did that mean that Aiyen was in the same Abyss Tower that Vikir had entered?

But Aiyen shook her head.

“The Hell Tree I was in was a different entity. He called it a ‘prototype’.”

Vikir knew immediately what that meant.

Vikir’s Hell Tree was a modified version of the one that made survival a little easier for the challengers in the Tower.

Aiyen, however, had entered an earlier version of the Hell Tree.

Into an object that was discarded because its survival rate was too low for those who attempted it, and alone!

“I survived in there by killing fairies and demons and eating candy. Perhaps because it was an object with many errors, clearing it was impossible, they said I would just have to stay trapped in that tower forever. That’s what the Demonic Dragon I defeated on the top floor said.”

Vikir looked genuinely surprised.

Even if it was a different version of the Hell Tree, a Demonic Dragon was usually a strong demon.

After challenging the tower several times, Aiyen succeeded in hunting down such a Demonic Dragon.

“There’s a reason why you became a comeback champion when I wasn’t looking.”

“Hehehe-but I was only able to get out of the tower because my Husby defeated Amdusias in the end.”

Frustrated that no matter how many times she cleared the tower, she couldn’t get out, Aiyen suddenly realized that she could get out of the tower.

Only later did she realize that it was because Vikir had cleared the Hell Tree in the Imperial Academy and defeated the tower’s master, Amdusias.

“After that, I left the Western Continent and traveled to the Central Continent. However, I found that the place had already been wiped out?”

Aiyen’s testimony is remarkable.

One day, countless gates suddenly appeared in the night sky, pouring out fire and demons.

Demons rampaged everywhere, and fire rained down.

The Gate of Hell had opened.

There were four ominous signs that the end of the world was approaching.

“…Wait a minute. Four things, not 10?”

Vikir asked, and Aiyen nodded.

“Endless darkness, hailstorms of fire, swarms of flies and frogs. Four things, right?”

“…Hmm. I see I’ve eliminated six of the ten, so the number of plagues is down to four.”

Vikir nodded.

Originally, there were supposed to be six more plagues on earth.

The waters turning to blood, the herds boiling over, the livestock and animals being slaughtered, the locust storms drying up all the food, the first born dying that year.

But all these things did not happen.

Vikir had already removed the causes of these disasters.

‘But the four remaining Ten Corpses are enough to destroy the world.’

It’s just a matter of time. It would take a little longer for the world to be completely destroyed, but the four great demons were steadily bringing destruction to earth.

Even at this very moment.

‘Perhaps soon, the Gates of Destruction will be fully opened. Before that happens, I must eliminate them once and for all….’

As if reading Vikir’s thoughts, Aiyen spoke in an angry voice.

“So, as soon as I went to the Imperial Capital, I went to see Cindywendy.”

“…!”

Vikir’s eyes lit up.

Cindywendy was one of Vikir’s henchmen, someone he could trust no matter what.

Vikir had given her a number of instructions before entering the Nouvelle Vague, and if Aiyen met her, things would go smoothly.

“Cindywendy was trusted because she had traded with Ballak for so long. That’s where I heard the story of my Husby. That she was falsely accused and imprisoned.”

“Not falsely accused, but, well, go on.”

“So I thought I’d take care of the things you left unfinished.”

Aiyen’s eyes glowed with a searing light.

“Pedro of Donquixote, Isolde of Usher, and Thomas of Leviathan. And their masters, Pasamonte of Donquixote, Madeline of Usher, and Hobbes of Leviathan. I tried to assassinate them all.”

Listening to her, Vikir understood what had been written in the newspaper clippings he had once obtained from a prisoner.

[Inside…] … palace guard, raiding…

-The Usher family… a mysterious attack… heavy damage… authorities have identified one suspect… the victim, Madeline… seriously injured, but not life-threatening…

The [sole] victim of a series of attacks on…

-Donquixote Family… another mystery… attack… Count Pasamonte… minor injuries… authorities have identified one suspect… believed to be the same…

[Exclusive] Suspected assassin arrested…

-Leviathan Family… Attack on Patriarch Hobbs… Blamed on the recent surge in demonic activity… Mysterious gates and strange dungeons popping up all over the Leviathan Family estate… An empire-wide investigation has been launched… The Night Hounds… A suspicious organization… A citywide scare…

The Ushers, Donquixote, and the Leviathans have been attacked, and there is only one man left standing.

And that was Aiyen.

“You could have just waited to meet me. I was planning to get out of here soon anyway.”

“That’s what I was counting on. There’s no better welcome home gift than an enemy’s head or raw liver. I am also a woman with a mood.”

“….”

Aiyen seemed genuinely depressed that she hadn’t been able to rip the heads off the rest of the Ten Corpses.

Vikir comforted her.

“You were brave to go in alone, that’s all that matters.”

“It is. It’s nothing compared to the Demonic Dragon I fought in the Hell Tree, or the entire daylily colony in the River of Flow.”

“So what happened?”

“Well. I failed, to put it mildly. I tried to march into Leviathan Family and rip out patriarch’s head… but he was much stronger than I expected, so I was captured and brought down here to Nouvelle Vague.”

“I see. His name is Flauros. A demon with great power, you probably wouldn’t have been able to do it alone. Didn’t Cindywendy stop you?”

“She didn’t. I wasn’t alone.”

“…?”

The words left out a lot, but it was clear how much Aiyen must have prepared, how much she must have thought about, in order to get her revenge.

“Thanks.”

“Ehem. That’s all you need to know. Be good to me.”

Then.

“Bastards!”

A large man stood in the way of Vikir and Aiyen.

Lt. Colonel Bastille. He was wielding a broken greatsword, blocking their path downstairs.

“I don’t know what you’re up to, but you’re not getting through!”

He knew he couldn’t stop the duo that had sent D’Ordume and Souaré away with just his strength.

So Lt. Colonel Bastille slammed his greatsword down on the ground.

Kwakwang! Jjeojeojeojeojeog-

It was meant to cause an earthquake and collapse the passage. Even if it meant sacrificing his own life.

“….”

Vikir frowned at the unexpected obstacle.

Boulders were falling from above, and the floor was deeply cracked.

But.

Hwiiiiiikk-

Aiyen smiled meaningfully and whistled.

Then something amazing happened.

Aiyen’s hair burst into flames, and a giant wolf was summoned into a body of flames.

Seeing the wolf’s face, Vikir cried out in delight.

“Bakira!”

Bakira the Wolf. The one who once had roamed the jungle with Vikir.

Aiyen laughed bitterly.

“I’m grateful he stayed by my side after his lifespan was up. We made a contract for redemption in the Hell Tree.”

The fire wolf summoned by Aiyen immediately struck Lt. Colonel Bastille with its forepaws, sending him flying.

Peong-

With a loud shockwave, Lieutenant Colonel Bastille’s body was sent flying into the distance.

[Kung!]

Bakira leaped across the crack in the floor that had opened just moments before, carrying Aiyen and Vikir on his back.

“That’s a lot of speed.”

Vikir shuddered at Bakira’s speed.

He hadn’t expected the creature that had lost its hind legs during Madame’s attack to be able to run this fast.

Then, as if on cue, Aiyen asked.

“But isn’t the 5th floor the gulper eel kennel? Why are you heading to the 10th floor instead of the 5th floor?”

“ …That.”

Vikir whispered in Aiyen’s ear and told her what was coming next.

“…I’m surprised. Was this all planned from the beginning, even your imprisonment here?”

“Of course. So far, it’s going according to plan.”

Vikir nodded at Aiyen’s question.

Indeed, so far, everything had gone well.

D’Ordume and Souaré had been knocked out, and even Lt. Colonel Bastille, who was supposed to be in charge of the guards, had fallen.

Prisoners of all levels were on a rampage, led by a handful of extraordinary prisoners from Level 9, and the guards seemed to be getting pushed back.

…But life is always unpredictable. Things don’t always go as planned.

Kwang!

A loud noise from nowhere pounded the ceiling.

Jjeojeojeojeojeojeog-

The enormous Gate of Good and Evil suddenly began to open.

Ting- teoeong! Teong! Ttudug! Ttududug! Ppagag!

The chains supporting the Gate snapped with a loud crash, and the massive pulleys made of cast iron were crushed by the unexplained force.

“Who, who, who opened the Gate of Good and Evil!”

Lt. Colonel Bastille shouted in horror as he emerged from the crack in the ground, but there was no answer.

Sswaaaaaa! Puswisisisisisig-

A cold shower of water rained down from above, cooling the heated battlefield.

All the prisoners and guards who had been fighting tooth and nail looked up in surprise.

And there they saw only one old man.

Opening the Gate of Good and Evil with only the strength of his arms, he slowly pushed himself into the Nouvelle Vague.

…Thud!

The old man hit the ground.

And the complexions of all the prisoners began to turn blue at the sight of the old man’s wrinkled face, his tightly pressed lips, his white, stiff beard, and his knife-like wrinkled uniform.

The symbol of the Nouvelle Vague.

The one who reigns in fear of all the prisoners, who holds the power over all the guards.

The prison Warden ‘Orca Montreuil-sur-Mer Javert’ fell in the middle of the battlefield.

Chapter 411

End game (5)

◆

The deep furrows that are often engraved on the faces of veterans who have crossed all kinds of harsh lines of fire.

Wrinkles that look like scars under the corners of the eyes, the ferociously growing sideburns, the eyebrows thick and full enough to hide their coldly sunken eyeballs, the flat noses and square jaws.

His uniform, despite its wetness, was creased like a knife, buttoned all the way up to his neck, and a black fur coat resembling a lion’s mane covered his broad chest and broad shoulders.

It was a perfect outfit, except for the crookedness of his belt buckle.

He was taller than anyone else in the place, and a club hung below his waist, with a sharp point of lead attached to the end.

‘Orca Montreuil-sur-Mer Javert’. The head of prison at Nouvelle Vague.

Old Man, a symbol of Nouvelle Vague for nearly one hundred years, when generations on earth have changed several times.

Chig-

Tapping the end of his cigarette against the flames on the ground, he scanned his surroundings with a lingering gaze.

A puff of cigarette smoke puffs out between cracked, salt-soaked lips.

“What is this?”

He pulled something out of his arms.

A pocket watch, blackened and shriveled.

Apparently, it was made of BDISSEM.

“I had a feeling something had happened to BDISSEM. No matter what….”

Then.

“Ooh, Orca, I’ve lived my entire life to get revenge on you, be prepared!”

A thunderous shout rang out from behind him.

It was Mammatamuz the Piercing Tusk, a prisoner of Level 9.

King of the Bandits, who once ruled an entire mountain range in his time on land.

A villain of a previous generation, so vicious that he had been sentenced to over 2,800 consecutive life sentences by the Nakajaniye Court.

He rushed forward with tremendous force.

Then he slammed his shoulder into Warden Orca’s back with such force that the Major and Lieutenant Colonel guards who stood in his way were knocked to the ground.

Peo-eong! Udeudeug!

The sound of tearing hard leather and the shattering of hard objects within echoed through the area.

The result.

“Kuaaaaaaghhh!?”

It was a crushing defeat for Mammatamuz.

Broken shoulder blades ripped through the skin.

Mammatamuz fell to the ground in a heap.

Meanwhile, Major General Orca was still standing there, unmoving.

And then.

“…What the hell.”

He raised one hand high in the air.

The gongs and spiked clubs followed Warden Orca across his arms and flashed upward over his heavy bald head.

And just like that, it struck the ground like a bolt of black lightning.

“What a sight!”

A deafening crash shook the earth.

Mammatamuz’s head exploded, and with that as its epicenter, a massive seismic wave tore and twisted the surrounding terrain apart.

With one of Level 9’s prisoners now dead, Warden Orca’s anger was beginning to show.

Just by furrowing his eyebrows, the air around him cracked.

“Hehehe- It’s Orca after all, he must have a taste for hunting.”

“That old man can’t even die.”

“No, but he’s not as strong as he used to be, he’s old.”

“He is, Mammatamuz. He had a big voice, but he wasn’t really good at anything, was he?”

The prisoners of Level 9 snickered and began to close in on the encirclement, but Warden Orca was unfazed.

“Get lost, scum.”

At the same time, his club began to wail ferociously.

The two white spots on the tip of the club’s black head were swung like the head of a killer whale.

Kwakwakwakwakwakwakwang!

Dozens of skulls exploded under the blow of the club.

Shattered skull fragments, brain water, and droplets of blood flew everywhere.

With a terrifying momentum, Warden Orca raised his club and began to beat the Level 9 prisoners to death.

With one sweep of his arm, blood spattered the walls and floor, and with one movement of his body, he split the crowd in half.

Peo-eog! Peo-eog! Peo-eog! Peo-eog! Peo-eog! Peo-eog! Peo-eog! Peo-eog!

Even the mighty monsters of Level 9 didn’t dare to step in front of Warden Orca’s club.

The gongs, thorns, and chains at the end of the club were soaked with human oil and blood to the point that their original colors were no longer visible.

“That’s right. Where are D’Ordume and Souaré, I thought they were here first?”

Warden Orca asked.

Lt. Colonel Bastille, whose face had been scratched by a wolf’s claws, bowed down and said.

“With all due respect, …they are collapsed over there.”

At the words, Major General Orca’s thick eyebrows knit together.

Turning his head, he saw two people lying on a slope with stairs leading down.

D’Ordume, face down on the floor, and Souaré, face down against the wall, stunned.

Orca sighs at the sight of his two subordinates.

“Wake up.”

However, both of the wardens turned their eyes upside down and made no movement.

A line of blood formed on Orca’s forehead.

“…Wake up.”

He spoke in an even quieter voice.

But perhaps because of the different weight of energy it carried, it was more effective than his previous words.

“Huh!?”

“Hugh!?”

D’Ordume and Souaré snapped out of their reverie as soon as Major General Orca’s words left their mouths.

They staggered to their feet and saluted.

“Salute! I see you, sir.”

“Forget the salutes. Who made you look like that… No, never mind. Where did he go?”

“He, he went downstairs!”

Orca sighed again.

“I’ll take care of this place on my own. You guys should chase after him and get revenge.”

“….”

“No one with dirty debts will be the next head of the prison. You know that, right?”

Under Orca’s glare, D’Ordume and Souaré flinched.

At the same time.

Ppa-ang!

The backs of D’Ordume and Souaré’s uniforms burst open at the same time, revealing their reddened, bare skin.

Major General Orca slapped them on the back with the palm of his hand to encourage them.

“Make sure you pay off your debts.”

The Major General’s plan was clear.

A man who ruined the face of the wardens and the prestige of the entire Nouvelle Vague in front of everyone.

The plan was to place all responsibility for this riot on him and execute him.

◆

Nouvelle Vague Level 10. The labor camp on the 10th floor of the underground.

Deeper than Level 9, which was the deepest and harshest.

Vikir made his way to the work pit, the lowest in the Level 10.

Lava flowed, and flames in steam hung in the air.

The hot spring water bursting out from all over the place was bubbling and then evaporated and turned into steam before it fell to the ground.

As if that weren’t bad enough, an unidentifiable sphere, engulfed in blue flames, lies in the center of the pit.

Poseidon. The ultimate goal that had driven Vikir to descend to Nouvelle Vague himself.

Aiyen asked.

“…You mean we should destroy it?”

“Something like that. We can shock it or infuse it with mana.”

Finished, Vikir gave the test.

Baskerville 8th Form. Black Sun.

Vikir unleashed the most powerful attack he could unleash on Poseidon.

Kwakwang!

Surprisingly, Poseidon didn’t break.

It simply absorbed all of Vikir’s mana, aura, and impact.

He didn’t know if it was his mood, but the sphere seemed to swell a little more.

The blue flames burning around it were also a bit more intense.

Aiyen nodded.

“Alright, I’ll give it a try.”

She picked up the bow and arrow she’d taken from one of the guards.

Beside her, Bakira was preparing to shoot a flame from his mouth as well.

Then.

“Stop, you two!”

“What do you think you’re doing!”

A voice interrupted Vikir and Aiyen from behind.

D’Ordume and Souaré. They had come to their senses and were following closely behind.

Aiyen’s expression turned sour.

“I saved your lives, and you came back without thanking me?”

“Hohoho- I’m so proud of the fact that I barely managed to get one hit in a surprise attack from the side.”

Souaré is no match for Aiyen.

D’Ordume also glared at Vikir with a tense demeanor, unlike before.

“I didn’t realize you were so powerful that you reached the Supreme Realm.”

“….”

“But I am not afraid. I’m not going to let my guard down and fall.”

But Vikir was calmly analyzing the situation.

‘They’ve already lost once, and they’re coming after us, and they don’t look scared. Does that mean…?’

After finishing his thought, Vikir shouted.

“Get back!”

Aiyen had just stopped lunging at Souaré and immediately stepped back.

And then.

Cheolpeog! Cheolpudeog!

A blob of sticky slime landed where Vikir and Aiyen had stood just moments before.

Kkulleong… kkulleong… kkulleong… kkulleong…

A huge plume of slime began to flow in front of Vikir’s eyes.

The translucent green slime grew larger and larger, until it began to extend numerous tentacles behind D’Ordume and Souaré.

As if to escort them.

“…I knew it. There was a part of me that believed in it.”

Vikir swallowed hard.

It was a hasty misjudgment to exclude it from the escape plan, assuming it lacked intelligence and reason.

Brigadier General Flubber.

A strange substance that no one can determine with certainty whether or not it is a life form, and therefore no one can estimate its combat capabilities, had entered the fray.

Chapter 412

End game (6)

◆

Flubber. Full name: Flubber J. Tarbond. Rank is Brigadier General.

Responsible for coating the outside of Nouvelle Vague’s castle with a thin layer of slime to keep water out, Flubber was one of the two great mountains that support Nouvelle Vague’s system, along with BDISSEM.

An unidentifiable substance and creature with a body made up of an enormous mass of mucus of unknown volume, a pair of eyeballs that were nothing more than hollow spheres, a mouth that was gaping open in a smiling arc, and other grotesque deformities.

This strange entity now surrounded Vikir and Aiyen with obvious hostility.

Vikir and Aiyen each said something.

“Amazing, a creature capable of thinking.”

“Indeed. It looks like Shadowless King of the Black Sea.”

This was quite a surprise, as he had assumed that it would not have intelligence or reason.

Even D’Ordume and Souaré didn’t seem to be adjusting to the situation.

“Flubber, you monster… still only moves like a sword when you think Nouvelle Vague is in danger.”

“You must be attached to this place, that’s why you’re always sweeping, cleaning, and repairing the outer walls of the castle.”

Flubber’s motives were a little different than Vikir had expected.

He hadn’t come here to help D’Ordume and Souaré, but rather had sensed something was up with Poseidon and descended.

To prevent the destruction of Nouvelle Vague.

No one knows why Flubber wanted to protect Nouvelle Vague.

The only thing he could assume was that his attachment to this place and his desire to restore it were great.

“Hehehe… Yes, even the most incomprehensible monsters have the same goal.”

“It’s creepy to work with this monster, but there’s nothing I can do about it.”

Next. D’Ordume and Souaré moved under Flubber’s cover.

Kwakwakwakwang!

The combination of D’Ordume’s attack, Souaré’s defense, and Flubber’s tentacles closing in on the entire field worked quite well.

Ujijig! Peopeopeopeopeog!

As they stepped back to avoid the slash of the ax blade swung by D’Ordume, Flubber’s slime soon covered the entire ground.

Vikir and Aiyen were forced to retreat, trudging over a limited area of ground.

Peong- ppagag!

Aiyen fired an arrow, but Souaré raised several layers of earth shields to block it.

And beyond it, D’Ordume’s attacks continued to fly.

“They’ve been very annoying.”

“It’s to be expected with three of the Five Warden in one place.”

Vikir nodded in agreement with Aiyen’s words.

This was not a phenomenon that could be explained by the formula 1+1=2.

The combination of D’Ordume in attack, Souaré in defense, and Flubber filling in all the gaps was difficult for even Vikir to deal with.

“…Good thing I took care of Black Tongue and BDISSEM beforehand.”

Vikir muttered to himself.

Aiyen, who was deflecting D’Ordume’s attacks, asked in surprise.

“I thought it was my husby that worked on BDISSEM, but Black Tongue? Is that also the warden?”

“Yeah. I got rid of it because I thought it would get in the way of my escape, and I think it will help me now.”

Vikir slipped his hand into the leather pouch at his waist and grabbed a handful of what was inside.

Chalalalalag-

Soon, black pearl-like things were scattered in the air.

“Hmm?”

“What?”

D’Ordume and Souaré paused for a moment.

They were wary of these black pearls falling down, thinking it might be explosives.

But it was something far more troublesome than explosives.

Eujijig- eujijig- eujijig-

The surface of the black pearl cracked, and what was inside crawled out.

Those are the eggs of a new type of leech that stole and killed Black Tongue!

Vikir had deliberately cut his palm, causing blood to spurt out, and the eggs, soaked in it, had hatched as soon as they smelled the scent of blood.

The tiny leeches began to cling to D’Ordume and Souaré’s bodies.

“Damn it! These are Black Tongue Leeches! They’re stolen!”

“Kyaaahhh! That perverted bastard must have betrayed us!”

D’Ordume and Souaré didn’t realize that Black Tongue had betrayed them or that the leeches had been stolen, but they did not think that he had been attacked by Vikir.

They scrabbled and scratched until their bodies bled, pulling the leeches off.

Vikir bit his lip in disappointment.

“I guess we’ll have to use them on people who don’t know about leeches in the future, at least not in Nouvelle Vague.”

D’Ordume and Souaré were aware of Black Tongue’s perverted tastes and powers, so their wariness of leeches was at an all-time high.

To add insult to injury, the leeches weren’t responding to Flubber at all, so the effect wasn’t as effective as hoped.

‘But it bought us time, and that’s enough.’

Vikir and Aiyen closed in on Poseidon, keeping their distance behind them.

“Die!”

D’Ordume spun the axe blade on his forearm again.

Death Roll.

The whirlwind of strikes that had torn countless prisoners to shreds once more revealed its terrifying presence.

Vikir and Aiyen did not meet D’Ordume’s attack head-on.

“Do as I explained.”

“Understood!”

Aiyen jerked backward.

He turned and ducked behind the blue glowing Poseidon.

Vikir, too, moved to the other side of Aiyen, using Poseidon as a shield as he guided D’Ordume’s charge.

Kwa-kwang!

Poseidon was struck by D’Ordume’s attack.

The lava roots nearby exploded with a loud noise, and the resulting shock wave was also absorbed by Poseidon.

…Flash!

The blue light emitted by the sphere became even more intense.

The vibrations emanating from its roots also became much more intense.

D’Ordume’s brow furrowed.

“What is it? There is something fishy about this. They’re not fighting back, like they’re waiting for us to use our power. And that blue sphere looks even more….”

“What are you talking about? We need to take care of this and get reinforcements upstairs, and if we don’t kill them, the Major General will kill us!”

Souaré stepped forward in frustration.

Kwakwakwakwang!

Her sledgehammer struck the ground, sending spiky rocks flying with lava.

Ujijijijijig-

Hot volcanic bombs were scorching the area.

And as it does, Poseidon’s light grew brighter and brighter.

Vikir sensed Poseidon’s vibrations transmitting through the surface, gauging the accumulated power.

[Human! The wave of mana is unusual! I think about half of the power has been accumulated?]

Vikir was convinced when he heard Decarabia shout from his chest.

‘…50%, that’s quite a charge, well, the years I spent here were a long time.’

In fact, once the power was built up to 90%, it was all a matter of time.

The explosions and aftershocks that the lava roots were constantly generating would easily fill the rest.

What would happen when it reaches 100%!

As Vikir counted down the seconds.

Rumbling-

The ominous sound got closer to his ears.

“…!”

Vikir looks up to see Flubber smiling from ear to ear.

The creature had traveled unnoticed by rats and birds alike on a stalactite that had sprouted from the ceiling.

“Tch!”

Aiyen fired an arrow, but Flubber just swallowed it whole.

As expected, it seemed to ignore any physical force.

Juleuleug- ttug- ttug- kkulleong…

Flubber turned to the rear and slid down the stalactite.

It seemed to be enough to support D’Ordume as he bombarded from the front.

“…This is bad. Flubber doesn’t use physical power, so it won’t help Poseidon. If anything, it’ll hinder it.”

Vikir bit his lip.

He hadn’t expected Flubber, whom he’d written out of the plan because he didn’t think it would be a factor, to be this much of a hindrance.

If Flubber were to enter the fray, absorb the impact and swallow everything up, it would be impossible to activate Poseidon.

However, unlike Vikir, who was feeling tense inside, Aiyen’s expression remained relaxed.

“Don’t worry, Husby. There is a part of me that believes, just as there is a part of them that believes.”

“Hmm? What does that mean….”

Suddenly, Vikir’s mind flashed back to something Aiyen had said to him before they came down here.

‘You wouldn’t have been able to do it alone. Didn’t Cindywendy stop you?’

‘She didn’t. I wasn’t alone.’

The story of the time when Aiyen attacked Donquixote, Usher, and Leviathan.

At Vikir’s questioning look, Aiyen smirked.

“I didn’t come alone, either.”

At the same time.

Kwakwang-

The stalactites on the ceiling were swept away.

Flubber’s body, which was hanging from top to bottom, was cut into pieces and burned.

O-oooooh!

Flubber let out a grotesque scream and retracted its tentacles.

At the same time, a huge storm of strikes rained down on the backs of D’Ordume and Souaré, who were still looking straight ahead.

Kwakwakwakwakwang!

With a loud shockwave, D’Ordume, Souaré, and Flubber were sent flying at the same time.

The blue flames emitted by Poseidon became even stronger.

“Ugh! Who the…!?”

As D’Ordume and Souaré looked up with bloodshot eyes, a shadowy figure was cast across the roaring flames.

Hohohohoho-

A muffled laugh, clearly mocking D’Ordume and Souaré as they lay on the ground.

“Blinded by rage, where are you looking?”

A whip crackled with flames.

The person holding it tightly was wearing black tights that covered his entire body and high heels that were over 30 centimeters high.

“…!”

For the first time since entering the Nouvelle Vague, Vikir’s eyes widened.

And rightly so, for the figure that had just entered the battlefield had a face that Vikir recognized.

Ms. Ouroboros.

Professor Sadi, whom he hadn’t seen since he dropped out of Colosseo Academy, had entered the battlefield.

Chapter 413

End game (7)

◆

Kwalkwalkwalkwalkwalkwalkwalkwal…

Water was leaking all over Nouvelle Vague.

On the first floor, in front of the Gate of Good and Evil, the guards were putting down a prisoner riot when they realized things were getting out of hand.

“Damn! The hole in the exterior wall is not being repaired!”

“Where’s Brigadier General Flubber, why does the water keep coming in?”

“It’s a big problem, the collapsed battlements section continues to flood!”

“Half the inner wall is already under water, damn it!”

The more areas Brigadier General Flubber was unable to cover, the more water rushed into the castle.

“We’re all going to die at this rate!”

Prisoner and guard were both terrified.

Unlike when BDISSEM was gone, if Flubber was gone, the castle itself would be completely submerged under 10,000 meters of water.

There was no doubt that all life would be exterminated.

“Now is not the time to fight among ourselves!”

“Uh, what should we do? Should we stop the water first?”

“Run! We have to run!”

“To where? We’re ten thousand meters below the surface anyway, it’s the same no matter where we go!”

The prisoners and guards stopped fighting and looked for a way out.

Just then, Lt. Colonel Bastille shouted.

“Major General Orca! MajorGeneral Orca must be here! Where is the warden!”

“I, I don’t know! He hasn’t been seen since some time….”

Orca, who had just moments before been on the front lines, fighting the prisoners of Level 9, was nowhere to be found.

Lt. Colonel Bastille had no choice but to give the final order.

“I have no choice. Everyone to the 5th floor, to the gulper eel kennel!”

The situation was so desperate that he had no idea what his order would lead to.

“Give up suppression! Everyone retreat!”

Lt. Colonel Bastille’s words were the beginning of a remarkable event that would later be written in a small corner of the history books of mankind.

It was the first official declaration of humanity’s intention to abandon the Nouvelle Vague.

◆

Meanwhile, on the 10th floor of the Nouvelle Vague, an entirely new figure has emerged.

Professor Sadi. She opened her mouth, looking no different than she did on the surface.

“Hello friends~ long time no see!”

She waved her hand once at D’Ordume and Souaré, who had their mouths open in disbelief.

Vikir opened his mouth to express his disbelief.

“ …You managed to come this far.”

“Ahhh- Night Hound. It’s an honor~ hohoho.”

She walked over and shook hands with Aiyen, who was standing next to Vikir.

“It’s been a while, Ms. Night Fox~”

“It is good to see you again. Ms. Ouroboros, you kept your promise.”

“Of course~ I told you I’d be right behind you, I have business here.”

Aiyen had visited Cindywendy as soon as she was free of her past, and it seemed she had introduced her to Professor Sadi.

Aiyen, who had been a sniper in the Imperial City and carried on the reputation of Akwilla the Night Fox, and Professor Sadi, who had been a terrorist under the moniker Ms. Ouroboros, had joined forces.

Aiyen and Sadi were a perfect match for each other, as they were both anti-Empire.

Vikir thought to himself.

‘It’s a good thing I had given Cindywendy orders to find Sadi before I was sent to Nouvelle Vague.’

At the time of his previous sentencing to Nouvelle Vague, Vikir had handed Cindywendy a note with his instructions.

‘…And look for Professor Sadi.’

She might be able to help him someday, he thought.

Even if he was psychotic and moody, at least they had similar goals, and it worked.

Aiyen had deliberately chosen the Nouvelle Vague to follow Vikir’s trail, and Professor Sadi had used her status and connections as a former official of the Imperial Prison Service to disguise herself as a guard and sneak down to join the ranks of the guards who happened to be above ground in the Nouvelle Vague.

“Hohoho – Warden Orca and the rest of you just happened to be on the ground, so it was easy to infiltrate the convoy as it was the largest convoy ever. Fake identities, it’s my specialty.”

Sadi acted as if he knew D’Ordume and Souaré well.

The more she did so, the more their faces crumpled like they’d chewed shit.

“You, the one who once served as an Imperial Family advisor to the arresting unit, why did you betray us? It’s disgusting that you were once considered a candidate for warden alongside us.”

“Hmph! If you’d done anything wrong, you’d have been called ‘Sixth Warden’ alongside that bitch, though she was eventually rejected for having traitorous blood in her veins.”

Despite D’Ordume and Souaré’s sour accusations, Sadi was still smiling broadly.

“Do you think I’m crazy enough to be thrown into this stuffy, damp place with you pigs? No grace.”

With that, Sadi dismissed the conversation with D’Ordume and Souaré.

Then, as if on cue, she looked back at Vikir and asked.

“Oh, by the way, have you seen the man I placed in the Nouvelle Vague? He’s from Leviathan, his name is Sakkuth… and he’s a pretty good pig.”

“ …Haven’t seen him.”

“Really? Well, he’s always been a little unstable mentally, but he said he could do a good job, so I didn’t expect much from him, but I guess it didn’t work out~”

Sadi chuckled and stepped in front of D’Ordume, Souaré, and Flubber.

“I’m going to stop them, so just do what you can.”

At the same time, Sadi’s entire body began to glow with dark mana.

Vikir realized immediately what Sadi was trying to do.

…Gurgling!

A demonic, ferocious energy exploded from Sadi’s left eye.

Demonization.

Vikir could sense the familiar aura of Sadi’s transformation into a demon.

‘Belial, the artifact from when I killed the Sixth Corpse.’

He had been wondering why no artifact had dropped when he killed Belial, who was infiltrating Bourgeois.

Sadi removed the blindfold covering her left eye.

A golden-colored artifact glimmered inside.

Tsutsutsutsutsutsutsutsuts…

A black and golden aura blazed, making Sadi’s whip even longer and thicker.

Jja-ag!

The black and golden snake slithered across the ground.

It was a fierce attack that sent D’Ordume, Souaré, and even Flubber flying.

Vikir swallowed hard as he watched the immense combat power of the demonized Sadi.

The student Underdogma, who had an average level of combat power when he was in the Hell Tree, had gained strength comparable to a Danger Class A+ monster after becoming a demon(majin).

It was hard to even estimate how powerful Sadi, who was originally strong enough to surpass the realm of the Master, would have now that she became a Majin.

[Hohohoho- technique that requires you to lie down for at least half a year after you use it!]

Unlike Underdogma, Sadi had not become a full demon, but was walking a tightrope with half of her body remaining human.

This was possible thanks to her sense of balance, which had long since surpassed the level of humans, and her innate sense of combat.

“…!”

D’Ordume and Souaré flinched back from Sadi’s assault.

Flubber, too, was powerless against the AoE whip, which burnt everything it touched.

And Sadi’s chaotic aura stretched out and swirled wildly in all directions.

It was an ineffective attack, but it worked in Vikir’s favor.

This is because Poseidon was absorbing an increasing amount of force due to the impact being transmitted towards the surface.

‘That’s it. Almost… just a little more!’

The blue light emitted by Poseidon grew stronger and stronger.

Jjeojeog- jjeog- jjeojeojeog!

The blue color of the surface began to crack with violent vibrations.

Vikir and Aiyen were drawing up mana with all their might and pouring it into Poseidon.

…Kung!

There was a being that cut off all these flows at once.

Ujijijijig!

A shockwave crashes down on the ground.

Crumbling earth, D’Ordume and Souaré falling backwards, and Flubber fidgeting.

“What?”

Sadi closed her left eye, blocking out the magic.

The instincts of a genius, the dangers that screamed at her.

Having ignored that warning once before and lost her left eyeball, Sadi wasn’t about to make the same mistake twice.

…Boom!

For the third time, Sadi flipped and fell backwards.

Still alert, she lowered her stance and kept her body close to the ground.

And then.

A figure that made even the demonized Sadi take a step back stepped out into the middle of the battlefield.

A trench coat with black fur strewn about. Gray hair and beard that rose stiffly.

Warden Orca.

He had personally walked down to Level 10.

“…Sadi?”

Orca’s brow furrowed as soon as he saw Sadi’s face, as if he’d seen something he shouldn’t have.

Sadi broke out in a cold sweat just hearing his thick, hoarse voice.

“…Don’t say my name, old man.”

Her whip flew out like a writhing viper, aiming for Orca’s face.

Pakang-

Orca raised his gaiter leg to block the whip.

Kiririririk-

The whip was unable to overcome the force of the swing and was caught in Orca’s gaiters and military boots.

Orca stamped his foot as the whip was wrapped around his foot.

…Kung!

With a single roll of his foot, Sadi almost missed the whip.

“…!”

Barely holding on to the body she was being dragged, she tightened her arms and yanked the whip back.

Kkudeudeudeudeug- kkwagigig!

But the whip crunched beneath Orca’s military boots and didn’t budge.

“….”

Orca. This seasoned veteran raised his hollow eyes and looked around.

Slowly, as if he didn’t care about Sadi in front of him.

And then.

“…!”

Orca’s eyes narrowed.

His gaze was fixed on the side of the blue orb that emitted a brilliant light, on a boy who stood awkwardly and peered down at them.

Vikir Van Baskerville, young on the outside, but a seasoned warrior who had seen many lives.

And Orca Montreuil-sur-Mer Javert. A veteran of several generations already.

“….”

“….”

The two veterans who met in one place, transcending time and space, began to sharply confront each other.

Chapter 414

End game (8)

◆

All of Nouvelle Vague’s All-Stars have gathered in the Level Ten sector.

Warden Orca.

And three of the five wardens, D’Ordume, Souaré, and Flubber, except for BDISSEM and Black Tongue, who were eliminated by Vikir.

Among them, Orca is the one who stands alone.

Orca’s eyes are fixed on Vikir.

Vikir, in turn, watches Orca.

“….”

“….”

When a war of nerves between two veterans is about to break out.

“How dare you ignore me!”

A tearing yell pierced the air.

Professor Sadi. Her bloodshot gaze flashed toward Orca.

…Kwakwang!

The whip that was under Orca’s military boots broke the ground and was pulled out.

It bared its fangs once more and wrapped around Orca’s body.

But Orca was still unmoved.

It merely clicked its tongue.

“Winston, that guy. Maybe he’s too young, but I advised him not to reap, just stomp her to death. Although it is a baby, what good is there in keeping the seed of anger alive? It will eventually come back to bite him.”

The old soldier recalled a time long ago. A long time ago.

And the reminiscences were enough to provoke someone, just by muttering them.

Such was the case with Sadi.

“Die! I’ll kill you! Aaaahhh!”

Her resentment growing thicker and hotter with each passing second, she channeled all of her aura, enhanced by her demonization, into the tip of the whip and let it explode.

Kwakwakwakwakwang!

The air ruptured, and the ground tore like paper.

Orca’s brow furrowed, and he yanked at the chain around his waist.

Jeolgeuleog-

The chain moved, and so did the handle of the club at its end.

Orca grabbed the handle of the club and swung it once, casually.

Boom-

The ripple in the air is enough to break Sadi’s whip.

Seeing this, Aiyen’s mouth dropped open.

“Is it possible to have that kind of strength at that age? Normally, He should be lying in bed and being carried around.”

“The same could be said for Chief Akwilla.”

“My mother wasn’t that old.”

Aiyen smirked at Vikir’s comment.

At the same time, she raised the bow in her hand and prepared to snipe.

The extra strength she’d gained from the stats she’d gotten from the Hell Tree allowed her to pull the bowstring even tighter.

Pow!

The sound of an arrow being released was deceptively loud as it struck Orca.

Near his throat, to be exact.

…Taaang!

Orca raised his club to block Aiyen’s arrow.

“Sniper, you’re a nuisance.”

Aiyen felt sorry for Orca when he responded indifferently.

“If only I had a better bow….”

But before Aiyen could finish her grumble, Orca made a move.

“You guys go clean up the area. I’m going to investigate that strange orb.”

At Orca’s command, D’Ordume and Souaré nodded with grim expressions.

(Even Flubber’s expression turned a bit somber next to them.)

With that, Orca approached Poseidon with his club crossed in front of him.

Standing in his way was Vikir.

“No.”

A crimson aura emanated from Beelzebub.

Orca’s brow creased.

“It’s the child of the Baskervilles. But how did you get this power? At your age?”

“Let’s not mention age.”

Young or old, these are two men with powers that don’t belong together.

The two old warriors clashed ferociously in the center of the battlefield.

…Pakang!

The atmosphere shatters into pieces.

The heavy black aura emanating from Orca’s club and the crimson light from Vikir’s Beelzebub intertwine ferociously.

The aftermath of the impact is still running through the ground, nourishing Poseidon.

The blue glow was even more intense than before.

Seeing it, Orca’s eyes turned even more sinister.

“You must have something up your sleeve, I suppose, to cause all this chaos and then sneak back here. Like a rat.”

“…I won’t deny it.”

Orca’s club comes down, and Vikir’s sword meets it.

The air cracked and the ground warped with each blow.

Vikir turned to Aiyen behind him.

“I’ll stop this one, and you focus on getting Poseidon activated.”

“Got it!”

As soon as Aiyen realized that Orca was no match for her, she began to do what she could.

“You grumpy old man….”

Sadi raised her demonized body again and tried to aim for Orca’s back, but the presence of D’Ordume, Souaré, and Flubber in front of her prevented her from doing so.

This allowed Vikir to focus solely on the opponent in front of him.

…But that doesn’t make things any easier.

Clang!

The weight of the club landing on the back of his sword was more than even the mighty Vikir could handle.

Each blow was heavy, and the slightest misstep in the center of gravity would result in an instant death.

‘…Orca. An unexpected figure.’

Indeed, the Nouvelle Vague’s signature fighting power.

Vikir stepped back, feeling a few drops of cold sweat slip away as the club swept past him.

Despite drawing upon the power of the Supreme Realm and beyond, the battle was tense.

Vikir had to admit that Orca was much stronger than he had expected.

‘I think he’s a little stronger than Nabokov I, and… a little less than Cane Corso.’

Pope Nabokov I’s combat prowess had been a surprise to him, having seen it only briefly against Amdusias.

But she was long past her prime, and as a priest, she wasn’t exactly a combat specialist.

And considering that Cane Corso was also a former human who became a Death Knight, it’s safe to say that Warden Orca in front of him is the strongest human Vikir has ever encountered.

Orca, meanwhile, is equally surprised that Vikir, who appears to be no more than twenty years old at most, has such great strength and seasoned senses.

…Kwakwang!

Once again, Orca’s club and Vikir’s sword clashed.

Their auras tangled wildly, each crushing and cutting the other.

In the aftermath of this murderous clash, the surrounding stone mountains crumbled, leaving behind a trail of steam, flame, and dust.

…Peoeog!

Vikir raised his knee to block the flying Orca’s military boots.

Ppudeudeug-

Orca turned his head away to avoid Vikir’s left fist.

The blue flames surrounding Poseidon grew stronger and stronger as Vikir and Orca fought a fierce hand-to-hand combat, using fists and feet in addition to swords and clubs.

“Husby, it’s almost time!”

Hearing Aiyen’s shout, Vikir nodded and tried to push back.

However.

Chaleuleuleug-

A chain swung from the end of the club like a whip, grabbed Vikir’s ankle and yanked.

“Where are you going? I have to see the end. Young people these days don’t have much patient.”

Orca’s eyes sparked with searing fire.

Vikir glanced away and squinted behind him.

Poseidon’s vibration is unusual.

Judging by the constant explosions near the roots, the accumulated shock must be about to cross the breaking point.

‘…Now, or a little longer? No, should we leave now?’

The timing was ambiguous enough that even Vikir couldn’t make an accurate judgment.

A little more shock, just a little more, would make it clearer, but if he stayed here and fought Orca any longer, he wouldn’t have the stamina to escape.

And above all, on the battlefield before the regression, Orca was a great hero who had helped the Human Alliance enormously, so he could not be expected to fight to the death in a place like this.

‘He was also the one who blew up the Nouvelle Vague with his own hands….’

Vikir already knew why.

The Destruction War. A growing war. The looming doom. Demons turning their attention to Nouvelle Vague. …And then there was the event that had nothing to do with any of that.

‘…The ‘Second’ 47 Man Riot.’

Vikir mentally recalled a specific event.

Kwakwang!

Orca’s club came flying down.

Vikir pushed his aura to the limit and met Orca’s blow.

Kurrrrrr!

Baskerville 8th Form, Black Sun.

Despite the fact that even the Black Tongue was sent flying in a single blow, Orca managed to hold on.

His brow crumpled slightly, but he didn’t back down.

The gaping wounds on his forehead and chin were popping open and spewing red blood, but he hadn’t taken a step back from the spot, blocking Vikir’s black sun.

“…Is this your highest power?”

“….”

“Then it’s my turn.”

Orca swiped a hand across his sweaty, bloodied face.

And then.

…Udeudeudeug!

The sound of twisting muscles and bones could be heard throughout his body.

For a moment, a piece of pre-regression common sense flashed through Vikir’s mind.

’ …They said Orca wasn’t an ordinary human either.’

That’s right. Just as the five wardens of the Nouvelle Vague were not all human, so was Orca.

Vikir had just adjusted his stance and was about to enter the second round.

Jjaag-

The sound of tough leather popping came from somewhere.

The back of Javert’s thick fur coat was torn from his shoulders, and a whip flicked across it.

Sadi. She was holding onto Orca’s back, exhausted from the aftereffects of the demonization and the battle.

Further behind them, D’Ordume and Souaré lay sprawled in a pool of blood.

Flubber doesn’t even look like it’s been blown to pieces.

“…Thank you.”

Sadi wasn’t looking at Orca, she was looking at Vikir.

Vikir tilted his head at her unexpected words.

What is she thanking me for?

Sadi continued.

“For keeping your promise.”

Suddenly, Vikir remembered a promise he’d made to her at Colosseo Academy.

He had asked her to hand over Orwell, the key to Nouvelle Vague’s front door.

‘Hand it over.’

‘Yes~ I’ll give it to you~ I really need the ‘front door key’ too, but… there are other ways.’

‘….’

‘Can you promise me one more thing in return?’

Sadi was clearly asking for a favor.

‘When you escape, if you get a chance, please bring my grandfather out with you.’

Sadi’s grandfather, the man she credits with having the greatest influence on her thinking.

“…!”

Vikir’s eyes widened and she looked around.

The terrain had already been ravaged by Vikir and Orca’s clash.

Every mountain and hill had collapsed, and countless crevasses had formed on the plains, leaving them open-mouthed.

Even Level 9 couldn’t handle it, and the aftermath had reached the areas of the beings they had isolated.

Under the circumstances, it’s no wonder.

Ujig- ujijijig!

In the distance, the cell began to crumble.

“…Ah, no.”

Souaré, who was in charge of the cell, turned white.

D’Ordume, too, was unable to speak as he was devastated.

“….”

Even the mighty Orca’s face crumpled.

His face was even more distorted than when he was facing Vikir’s 8th Form earlier.

And then.

A voice began to emanate from the crumbling cell.

“Pushishishishi….”

A hollow laugh, like the wind being let out of a balloon.

It was a sound Vikir had heard once before, when he was in solitary confinement.

Then, from among the crumbling rubble, a tall, sturdy old man pushed himself up.

His appearance was so gaunt and twisted that one might suspect he was undead.

Indeed, he had the gaunt appearance of someone who had just been released from solitary confinement.

However, his gestures and movements still have a leisurely feel.

He didn’t look like he was someone who had just come out of solitary confinement.

“…Angajumang?”

Vikir asks, and the old man nods and smiles.

“Good thing you came, I was getting tired of ‘vacation’.”

The old man looked back at Sadi on the floor and smiled warmly.

Only then was Vikir once again certain of his identity.

“Angajumang Cedric Sadi de Sade. Also known as the Marquis de Sade.”

It was the unleashing of a rare warmonger who had shaken the Empire to its core more than forty years ago with the ‘47 Man Riots’.

Chapter 416

End game (10)

◆

…Flash!

A storm erupted.

A huge crater was created, and all the dirt, dust, moisture, water, vapor, groundwater, lava, smoke, sulfurous gas, and everything else… in the vicinity was swept away.

The floor was swept so cleanly that it felt smooth.

The air was parched, without a trace of moisture, and there was no sign of the usual flames or gases.

And in the center of this pristine wasteland, two men knelt on one knee.

Their clothes tattered and torn, blood streaming from their foreheads, the weapons that had defended their masters embedded deep in the ground.

They endured it all with their eyes wide open, despite the bombardment of light and heat.

On one side, displaying a truly fearsome will, is Orca, the head warden of Nouvelle Vague.

On the other was Marquis de Sade, Nouvelle Vague’s worst prisoner.

“…What was that?”

“Oh my, my body feel ache, why you interrupt?”

The strength of the two old men who had survived the explosion and its aftermath was the same, but the source of that strength was completely different.

Major General Orca’s will to protect and defend.

The Marquis de Sade’s will to harm and destroy.

The will and purpose of these two men were so opposed to each other that they unexpectedly produced the same result.

The two old men, who had managed to hold their own in the midst of the chaos, soon straightened up and prepared to fight again.

However.

“…!”

Both old men were stunned by the scene in front of them as soon as they opened their eyes.

Kuleuleuleuleug-

Blue flames roared from the center of the crater.

A thick, gigantic pillar of fire was rising from the ground below.

It pierced through the ceilings of every floor of Nouvelle Vague, Lv. 9, Lv. 8, Lv. 7, Lv. 6, Lv. 5, Lv. 4, Lv. 3, Lv. 2, and Lv. 1, and stretched even higher.

Dededededededededer-

The Gate of Good and Evil.

The massive circular gate that served as the lid of the Nouvelle Vague kept the blue pillar of fire at bay, but the chains around it were breaking one by one, and it looked quite precarious.

The entire gate was burning brightly as the chains snapped and the pulleys around it broke.

The flubber slime was beginning to clear, and the water that had begun to rush in from outside was evaporating before it could get anywhere near the pillar of fire.

“What, what is that?”

Orca’s mouth was half open in disbelief.

But no one knew anything about this anomaly.

Even D’Ordume, Souaré, Sadi, Aiyen, and Marquis de Sade, far away in the distance, were all staring blankly at the end of the pillar of fire.

…Every single person. Except for Vikir.

Kuleuleuleug!

Vikir approached the spot where the flame sprout had germinated, where the blue egg had been.

The hot air and blue flames threatened to consume him, but Vikir was undaunted.

He thought he’d gotten used to the heat from the burns he’d suffered while trying to disguise himself as Garam’s face, but the heat he felt now… was something else entirely.

The ultra-high-temperature clear salt, which was so hot that it could not even be compared to a normal fire, was creating an enormous rising air current.

‘It’s almost burning my flesh now.’

Vikir pushed through the searing flames.

He had to cling to the ground with all his might to keep himself from floating upward.

Finally, through the flames and turbulence, he could see Poseidon’s form.

The round sphere had been split in half, and a pillar of blue fire was erupting from its center.

The roots of the pillar of fire beneath it were barely visible.

Judging by the intermittent explosions and earthquakes that were coming from very deep beneath the ground, he could only guess that it was probably touching the thermosphere of the deepest part of the Nouvelle Vague volcano.

‘So, Nouvelle Vague is not a extinct volcano.’

This volcano is not extinct.

It’s just been secretly storing up energy to explode one day in the biggest, most spectacular way possible.

And it was this blue seed, Poseidon, that had taken root in the center of that power and was sucking it up.

Technically, it was a parasite on the Nouvelle Vague.

‘No. Maybe it’s not a parasite. Maybe this place, Nouvelle Vague itself, was created by someone for the purpose of hatching Poseidon….’

…But that wasn’t what mattered now.

Vikir plunged his hand into the flames and pulled away all the scorching embers.

To his surprise, the flames seemed wary and fierce at first, but calmed down at his touch.

Like an animal that has allowed its fur to be stroked.

The heat diminished, and soon there was nothing but warmth.

Vikir pushed forward, using the basilisk’s power to regenerate his flesh.

At this point, Vikir was able to part the curtains of fire and look through them.

Inside was a small, circular space.

And there was a pair of eyes looking up at him.

[…!]

Black scales. And blue flames sizzling between them.

…The creature was maybe a little less than the size of a palm?

A strange creature that looked like a lizard, but with wings on its back, glared at Vikir.

Its entire body was engulfed in flames, as if it were a creature born of fire, fed by fire, nourished by fire, and returned to fire.

“….”

Vikir stared down at it.

It stared back at him, too.

They are seeing each other for the first time since they were born.

And then.

Hiccup.

It gave a small hiccup.

A tiny spark of blue flame flared from its tiny nostrils, and then it was gone.

“Pretty. So something like this can be born from an egg. Is it something like Salamander?”

“…No. It’s much, much higher beings than that.”

Vikir’s words were cut short by the admiring words of Aiyen, who had now caught up with him.

Vikir doesn’t know exactly what it is either.

He knows only that it is the greatest of the ancient beings that oppose the demons, and that it holds the greatest potential.

That could be guessed just by looking at Decarabia’s reaction as it trembled between his chest.

[Gosh, I can’t believe this still exists! I thought it was extinct a long, long time ago! I’ve heard that the Mage Emperor Tzersi personally exterminated them one by one! Maybe this is the last one left in the world…!?]

At the sight of Poseidon, Decarabia began to tremble with all the excitement he had been holding in.

Meanwhile.

Kkuleug- kkuleug- kuleuleug-

It moved its black and blue body and approached Vikir.

It nuzzled its cheek against the back of Vikir’s hand.

An expression of friendliness. A movement that reveals unconditional liking and affection for the being that one sees for the first time in one’s life.

But the time of communication was short.

Paang-

It spread its wings and prepared to take to the skies.

Vikir was calmly meeting its gaze as if it was begging him to take care of himself.

‘See you again.’

A message echoed in Vikir mind.

It wasn’t in the form of words, but that didn’t make it any less true, and it struck a chord in his heart.

Vikir responded in kind.

‘Human life is short. By the time you are old enough to come and see me, I will not be here. You will never see me again.’

It closed its eyes, shook its head, and looked terribly sad at Vikir’s words.

And then. It was time.

It spread its tiny wings wide.

And from beneath the ground, from the deepest, hottest part of the volcano, a plume of blue fire erupted, powering its wings.

Ku-gugugugugugugu!

The power of the volcano was condensed into its two tiny wings, creating a blinding blue light.

At any moment, it is about to break through the bottom of the abyss, penetrate the deep, dark abyss, rise above the water, pass through the distant skies, and soar into the vast expanse of heaven.

“That’s it. It’s done.”

Vikir turned his attention away from all of this.

All the work he had done was done.

All the dangers and hardships of his journey to and from this Ghost Castle in the deepest depths of the sea have been fulfilled.

“This is the end of my purpose in Nouvelle Vague. The egg has hatched, and there’s nothing more to see.”

“Really? Does that mean we can get out of here?”

“…Now that’s a new problem.”

Vikir was silent.

In truth, he’d thought about this when he’d first descended into Nouvelle Vague.

If he could find this Poseidon safely and get it up and running a few years early, he’d have done his duty, and then he doesn’t mind dying.

But now that he had gotten to this point and made it work, he had a new desire.

He want to live.

He want to survive longer.

He wants to see with his own eyes how the future of humanity plays out, how this long, terrible war ends, how it’s resolved, how it’s finished in a way that he didn’t see in his last life.

Many would die.

And many will survive.

And live on.

The future. The far future, far beyond what Vikir had seen in his previous life!

…Teoeog!

Vikir reached out and tugged at Aiyen’s wrist.

“What?”

Turning to Aiyen, who looked surprised, Vikir said briefly.

“Let’s get out of here.”

Now it was his turn to leave Nouvelle Vague for real.

The nostalgic faces swirling in his head.

It was time to return to the ground, which had changed so much in the meantime.

Chapter 419

Goodbye Nouvelle Vague (3)

◆

The Nouvelle Vague volcano has erupted.

A tremendous explosion. The momentum was such that it seemed as if the entire sea was being lifted up with it.

The pillar of fire that blew away the Gate of Good and Evil immediately turned blue, then doubled, tripled, quadrupled… hundreds of times in thickness and size.

As the pillar of fire soared, secondary and tertiary currents formed around it, and a gigantic column of water rose up to envelop it.

A tsunami so powerful that it has never been seen before in human history.

It was a major tectonic shift that would have devastating effects on the sea and all life on earth.

◆

A few minutes before the Nouvelle Vague crater erupted.

Vikir saw Nouvelle Vague’s iconic Gate of Good and Evil blown away.

The power of the explosion was evident in the way the massive mass of alloy blew off like a bottle cap.

‘…But that won’t be the end of it.’

Soon, a second, third, fourth, and hundreds of shock waves will hit this place one after another.

And then it’s all over.

‘I hope Aiyen is safe.’

Vikir glanced back.

The gulper eel was already out of sight.

The strong current created by Orca pushed its back, so it probably drifted to a safe place.

He could only hope so.

Finished with his thoughts, Vikir turned his head again.

…Uleuleung! Kwakwang!

Lightning was raging at the bottom of the deep sea.

Tsunamis raging on a scale that could easily destroy a country.

In the face of this vast maelstrom of chaos, humans were nothing more than insignificant grains of sand.

Then.

Togtog-

A hand tapped Vikir on the shoulder.

It was the Marquis de Sade, looking into Vikir’s eyes as if to ask him what he would do.

Vikir tried to think of a way to survive in this extreme situation.

Soon there was a tremendous explosion.

It will be followed by a massive upward current that will sweep away everything here.

Then.

“…!”

Suddenly, something caught Vikir’s eye.

The Gate of Good and Evil.

A giant disc, the symbol of Nouvelle Vague.

It had been struck by the full force of Poseidon’s power, and yet it remained unbroken.

It was dented in the center, but not cracked.

It just bounced off because all the chains around it were broken.

Vikir recalled the vault of the Bourgeois in his mind.

The one Belial had crafted, too, forged from mythril and orharcon alloy.

Despite its size, it had withstood an attack by the entire Pitbull Knights for two hours.

But what about the Gate of Good and Evil?

The strongest gate that no one has ever been able to break through.

Even Poseidon’s first blast had only managed to make a small dent.

Vikir moved instinctively.

‘Uhh, come with me!’

The Marquis de Sade flailed his limbs in a frenzy and followed Vikir’s lead.

Then, reaching the frantic, shaking ground, Vikir landed on the Gate of Good and Evil that hung over the walls of Nouvelle Vague.

Beside him, the pillar of fire grew blue.

It will soon rise in power and engulf everything here, sweeping everything upward.

Vikir intended to stay close to this Gate of Good and Evil then.

Like a cork on a gushing stem of champagne, he planned to cling to it and get out to the surface.

‘Are you insane?’

Even the Marquis de Sade’s mouth dropped open in disbelief.

But there was no other option.

The oxygen would soon run out, and there was no other way to get to the surface from 10,000 meters below.

‘We have to find a way to stay alive.’

Of course, the chances of survival are less than 1%, less than 0.001%.

But it’s better than zero. You have to try anything you can, right?

Vikir made his way to the hollow in the center of the Gate of Good and Evil and took a seat.

He imbued Decarabia with mana.

[…Human].

Decarabia realized Vikir’s plan.

He would hold the Gate of Good and Evil like a surfboard at the top of the blast.

‘You hold the pressure from above.’

Vikir’s strategy was simple.

Like a sandwich, the pressure would be minimized by spreading out the Gates of Good and Evil on the bottom and the protective shield of Decarabia on top.

The dome-shaped shield of Decarabia should be able to withstand the terrifying pressure from above.

The problem is, Vikir doesn’t have enough mana to maintain that level of defense.

‘If that’s the problem, I can help.’

Marquis de Sade said quickly from the side.

He seemed worried that Vikir would leave him behind.

‘I wonder how much more interesting things would be on the ground. Please take me with you!’

Marquis de Sade took Vikir’s hand and begged.

Vikir nodded, feeling the purity and quality of mana flowing through their clasped hands.

But even so, their chances of survival were slim.

Decarabia’s defenses were reliable, but even with Vikir and Marquis de Sade’s combined mana, there was no telling how long they could hold out.

…Just then.

Thud.

A palm came up over the edge of the Gate of Good and Evil.

Black webbed feet can be seen between the thick fingers that are imbued with strong power.

‘…Take me.’

A bloodied old man sprawled his upper body across the disc.

He stared at Vikir with his one eye, which had just burst from the impact.

Marquis de Sade asked in disbelief.

‘Are you insane? Did you forget we were just fighting?’

‘I am sane. I remember clearly.’

With that, Orca no longer looked at Marquis de Sade.

His gaze was fixed solely on Vikir.

‘I cannot die here.’

‘….’

Vikir felt the strong, unyielding determination in Orca’s gaze.

‘Oh no! I don’t think I’d be able to carry that old man!’

‘I would be far more trustworthy than a heinous criminal.’

Marquis de Sade and Major General Orca were still arguing sharply, even through their bloodied bodies.

Vikir looked at them and thought of the original history.

‘…Causality has been twisted.’

Marquis de Sade escaped from prison much later, during the latter stages of the War of Destruction.

Sadi, who has gathered forces from outside, uses the three works she had infiltrated in Nouvelle Vague to open the Gate of Good and Evil and rescue his grandfather, Marquis de Sade.

Intrigued by the news that the land is in flames and that the age of war has arrived, Marquis de Sade kills BDISSEM and incites all the prisoners to start a massive riot.

Orca and the guards, who were distracted by the demonic army that was coming in from outside at the time, missed Marquis de Sade’s prison escape.

Nouvelle Vague is about to fall to the demons, and the worst prisoner escapes just in time.

Faced with the possibility of defeating the demon army and allowing Sade to escape at the same time, Orca is forced to make an extreme choice.

He activates the Poseidon he’s been studying since discovering it during the construction of Level Ten.

In the process, Orca triggered the great eruption of the Nouvelle Vague, annihilating countless demonic forces and Marquis de Sade before ascending to the surface and joining the Human Alliance.

And now, Orca, covered in blood, was begging Vikir for mercy.

‘Believe me. This world has turned into hell. It’s barely a shadow of its former self, and I’ve seen it.’

Orca begged Vikir, banging his head on the Gate of Good and Evil.

‘Save me. And take me with you. I will definitely be helpful in dealing with monsters.’

Vikir stared at Orca for a long moment.

And then.

‘…Ok.’

He nodded with a short reply.

The words were barely out of his mouth before Orca was on top of the Gate of Good and Evil.

‘Ew, it’s narrow as hell, and the old distracted man is a…’

Marquis de Sade grunted in disapproval, but Major General Orca shrugged it off and took his place beside Vikir.

Vikir, Night Hound.

Marquis de Sade of the 47 Man Riot.

Orca, Warden of Nouvelle Vague.

As the three of them stood together, a red inverted pentagram was drawn above them.

Decarabia materializes in the form of a hemisphere and brings the tips of its five legs to the Gate of Good and Evil.

‘If the Gate of Good and Evil cannot hold, we will all die. If the mana that fuels Decarabia runs out, we all die.’

At Vikir’s words, both Marquis de Sade and Major General Orca, who had been infusing mana into each of his shoulders, nodded stiffly.

The symbol of Nouvelle Vague, the Gate of Good and Evil.

The only thing indestructible in this great chaos.

Vikir used it as the base, and the Wailing Dome of Decarabia as the ceiling and walls.

And now, the time of judgment has come.

O-ooooo…

The space around them began to warp and scream.

The heavy energy felt from the ground, and before they know it, it speeds up and rushes towards them.

Directly below, towards the soles of their feet!

Kkwakwang!

The first explosion, an eardrum-splitting blast, was heard by everyone.

…! …! …! …!

The second and third explosions that followed were so far beyond the range of human hearing that they seemed merely static.

Both the Marquis de Sade and Major General Orca were perplexed.

Anxiety, crisis, tension, nervousness, excitement, and climax like nothing they had ever felt before, even after a lifetime of life of gambling and war.

It was truly an unreasonable number that they haven’t seen in a long time.

And then.

The Gate of Good and Evil floated upward.

A single coin of insignificant value was swept away by a strong wind, casually and unceremoniously.

But the three people on it were literally experiencing hell.

“…!”

“…!”

“…!”

The pressure felt like his body was being crushed, the sensation of being turned alive into paste.

Vikir poured all of the mana that Marquis de Sade and Major General Orca were pumping into him into Decarabia’s shields.

At the same time, Beelzebub squeezed the basilisk’s regenerative powers to the limit.

Udeudeug-udeudeug-udeudeug-udeudeug-udeudeug-udeudeug-udeudeug-udeudeug-udeudeug-udeudeug-udeudeug-udeudeug-udeudeug-udeudeug-udeudeug-udeudeug-udeudeug-udeudeug-udeudeug-udeudeug-udeudeug-udeudeug-udeudeug-udeudeug-udeudeug-udeudeug-udeudeug-udeudeug-udeudeug-udeudeug-udeudeug-udeudeug-udeudeug-udeudeug-udeudeug-udeudeug-udeudeug-udeudeug-udeudeug-udeudeug-udeudeug-udeudeug-udeudeug-udeudeug-udeudeug-udeudeug-udeudeug-udeudeug-udeudeug-udeudeug-udeudeug-udeudeug-udeudeug-udeudeug-udeudeug-udeudeug-udeudeug-udeudeug-udeudeug-udeudeug-udeudeug-udeudeug-udeudeug-udeudeug-udeudeug-udeudeug-udeudeug-udeudeug-udeudeug-udeudeug-udeudeug-udeudeug-udeudeug-udeudeug-udeudeug-udeudeug-udeudeug-udeudeug-udeudeug-udeudeug-udeudeug-udeudeug-udeudeug-udeudeug-udeudeug-udeudeug-udeudeug-udeudeug-udeudeug-udeudeug-udeudeug-udeudeug-udeudeug-udeudeug-udeudeug-udeudeug-udeudeug-udeudeug-udeudeug-udeudeug-udeudeug-udeudeug-udeudeug-udeudeug-udeudeug-udeudeug-udeudeug-udeudeug-udeudeug-udeudeug-udeudeug-udeudeug-udeudeug…!

The bones, flesh, muscles, and blood of the entire body were being pressed to their limits by a terrifying pressure that would make even a danger level S-rank monster scream.

[…Human!]

[…Up!]

[…Here we go!]

The sound of Decarabia’s shouts echoed faintly in his ears amidst the inaudible but unmistakable roar.

Suddenly, a voice sticks in Vikir’s mind.

He doesn’t know why, but the words he’d spoken when he was promoted to Major suddenly came back to him.

‘I’m going to put everything I have on the line, and I’m going to transform Nouvelle Vague.’

A plan he’d had since he walked into Nouvelle Vague.

It was realized perfectly. It really has made a huge difference.

“….”

Vikir drew a faint arc around the corner of his mouth.

It’s called (Do your best to wait for destiny).

He had done all he could as a human being.

He’s done his best, done it perfectly.

All that remains is for the heavens to decide.

And so Vikir goes to meet the heavens.

He is shooting out to ask Sky(Heaven), whom he has not seen for nearly four years, about the future and His accomplishment.

…Toward the ground, 10,000 meters above!

Chapter 420

How to Live as a Wandering Knight (1)

◆

Above Ground. In a remote village in the southern continent, ‘Wakewack’.

This village, which had always been warm and humid and had abundant fruit crops, had been suffering from unprecedented drought and famine in recent decades, even hundreds of years.

The drought is so extreme that the ground is parched and cracked, and the trees and grasses are not only dying, but burning to a crisp.

Wildfires of epic proportions have scorched the mountains and dried up the lakes, decimating the wild animals and aquatic species.

Open dungeons everywhere are causing monster damage to explode.

Whiiiiing-

A hot, dry wind carries ash.

It blows from the opposite mountain range, which has been reduced to a pile of charcoal by a forest fire.

These pungent ash blowing in with the wind sucked up every bit of moisture that was left, further impoverishing people’s spirits.

…And.

Across the desolate wasteland, a wanderer made his way.

Dull black armor peeked out from beneath a tattered black cloak.

A plague doctor’s mask with a long stork’s beak hung below his waist, and a long object wrapped in bandages was carried on his back.

Cheolkeog- cheolkeodeog-

Every time he took a step that seemed arduous, the sound of the joints of the armor clicking together rang out faintly.

Wandering Knight. Speechless. This is a group of people that can be seen often, if not commonly, in these difficult times.

The black-armored wanderer arrived in Wakewack with weary steps.

He headed straight for the nearest tavern, pushing open the dried-out wooden door and taking a seat in a corner.

Between famine, drought, forest fires, and monster damage, the town’s food situation was not good.

It was reflected in the drinks and snacks served at the tavern.

Two handfuls of boiled beans on a bare plate, a glass of steaming beer.

At least it was a tavern, and you got what you paid for.

The Wandering Knight checked the mask strapped to his waist and drank his beer in silence.

Then.

A commotion began to emanate from the tavern’s center table.

Two men, apparently vigilantes, were having a conversation.

Since ancient times, taverns have been a hotbed of rumors, both past and present.

And many would agree that a group of men with nothing better to do than get drunk and argue about politics.

“So. Are you conservative or progressive?”

“Well, I’m always a progressive. What about you?”

“W-what are you asking? I am a conservative, a conservative!”

They argue about their views on the current state of affairs on the continent.

“Oh, of course the throne should go to the right man! Isn’t it only right that the First Prince be crowned? Donquixote and Usher and Leviathan are doing a great job!”

“I think the Second Prince is fine, and I can understand the choices of Baskerville, Morgue, Bourgeois, and Quovadis.”

“Eh- So you’re saying they were right to stage a coup?”

“No, it’s not a coup, It’s just a fight to stand in line. Since it is a political fight, it is correct to call it a civil war.”

“So. Is it right for the Seven Families of the Old Country to be fighting a civil war at this time, and the Second Prince they’re crowning as Emperor hasn’t appeared in front of the people in decades? I don’t even know if he exists anymore!”

“Ugh, you’re being disrespectful. Isn’t it the same for the First Prince’s faction to be waging a civil war in these times? Why do you blame it on the Second Prince’s faction?”

The current situation on the continent was extremely complicated.

Aside from the massive wildfires spreading across the Empire, and the devastating drought, famine, and monster damage, the political powers were engaged in a fierce civil war among themselves.

The Seven Pillars of the Empire.

Baskerville the Iron Blooded Swordsman, Morgue the Mage Sect, Quovadis the Faithful, Donquixote the Spearmaster, Usher the Archon, Leviathan the Poisonous Cancer, and Bourgeois the Tycoon.

Since the Emperor’s death, each of these Seven Families has been in bitter conflict over who should be the next Emperor.

The Old Testament factions Quovadis, Donquixote, Usher, and Leviathan were in favor of First Prince Jack Meridieu as Emperor.

The New Testament faction of Quovadis, Baskerville, Mor, and Bourgeois was supporting the Second Crown Prince, Ralph.

Both crown princes were descended from the founding emperor and possessed the power of prophecy, and were the recipients of an oracle that said, ‘One of them will destroy the world, the other will save the world’.

Therefore, who would ascend to the throne would be a matter of concern for all the people of the Empire.

If the wrong crown prince became emperor, the empire would be ruined.

“Of course the first crown prince should ascend to the throne, it is only natural that he is the legitimate eldest son and has continued to appear in front of the people of the empire over the years, leading by example in everything he does. Even in our family, the only hope is for the eldest son!”

“Haha- your ruined family is the same as the Imperial Family? And in your family, the second child is much smarter.”

“What! Why are you talking about my family!”

“Because you mentioned your family first, and I’m wondering if it’s realistically possible for the First Crown Prince to ascend to the throne. With the old faction of the Quovadis virtually collapsed, it’s generally accepted that the tide has turned in favor of the Second Crown Prince, and from what I’ve heard, Donquixote and Usher are the most talked about members of the family right now.”

“What, Donquixote and Usher? Why, is there some sort of controversy?”

“It’s not so much a controversy as a rumor… that the current head of the family is ill, and I hear it’s very serious. It could be today or tomorrow.”

“Lord Cervantes the Spear King and Lord Roderick the Archon? Nonsense! Didn’t we see them in action the last time a demon appeared in the Imperial Capital? I saw them with my own two eyes! They’re superhumans! They’re Masters! They’re not going to succumb to illness!”

“Well, I’ve heard it through the rumors. After all, they’ve been out of service for years now. From what I’ve heard, Donquixote’s younger brother is the current regent, and Usher’s younger sister is the current regent.”

“Hmm, I’ve heard that, but I’ve also heard that Donquixote and Usher don’t have many members of their own family, so they rely heavily on people from the outside of the family. Is that why?”

The argument between the two men was superficial, but it summarized the state of affairs on the continent.

1. Donquixote, Usher, Leviathan, and the Old Testament faction of the Quovadis, led by Prince Jack Meridieu.

2. Baskerville, Morgue, Bourgeois, and the New Testament faction of Quovadis, led by Prince Ralph.

Now that the Quovadis Old Testament faction was gone, the civil war was intensifying.

This confrontation, which had originally been going on for a very long time, began to flare up in earnest just a few years ago due to the ‘Night Hound’ incident.

Justification. Night Hound served its purpose to the Second Crown Prince Faction.

The fight was over whether Night Hound was evil or a righteous, if somewhat radical, man who overthrew a demon hiding among humans.

The other Families were outraged by the fact that three of the demons in the convoy happened to be members of the First Crown Prince’s faction.

Isabella of Baskerville, Banshee of Morgue, Lovebad of Bourgeois, and Mozgus of Quovadis, accused Pedro of Donquixote, Isolde of Usher, and Thomas of Leviathan of being demons.

Their statements were perfect, and they had proof.

‘I demand a retrial for Night Hound.’

But the claims of the Banshee Morgue were rejected.

Donquixote, Usher, and Leviathan immediately attempted to cover their tracks, and suddenly, even the First Prince was up front in denial.

‘To doubt them is to doubt me.’

It was the First Crown Prince’s unusually hardline stance that ultimately led to this protracted civil war.

But the Second Crown Prince’s faction was not without gains from the trial.

The second crown prince, who was rumored to have disappeared, was able to cover his lack of influence with a powerful rationale.

The Baskervilles, Morgue, Bourgeois, and Quovadis were united under a very basic, ethical code of rejection of those in league with demons.

Seven families, each rivaling the power of a kingdom, entered the civil war.

They began to tighten their grip on their territories and stopped all trade with the enemy camp.

The civil war was raging.

To add insult to injury, the people were already suffering from drought, wildfires, monster damage, and other natural disasters.

Public sentiment was at an all-time low.

However, there was also a rumor that was a ray of hope for the people.

“Let’s stop talking about this.”

“That’s right, it’s all for the high and mighty.”

“More than that, have you heard the rumor?”

“What rumor?”

“The vigilantes roaming the continent.”

“Aren’t we the vigilantes?”

“This guy! Not a lowly vigilante like us. I’m talking about Wandering Knights, who operates all over the Empire.”

“Wandering Knights? In this day and age, that’s just a rumor.”

“No! Listen!”

A hopeful rumor that soothes the hearts of people devastated by all kinds of natural disasters.

It was a story about the NIGHT WALKERS, a civilian group of vigilantes.

“They travel thousands of kilometers a day, slaying monsters, and they’re supposed to be incredibly powerful.”

“Does that make sense?”

“No! I heard they showed up and destroyed a horde of monsters when I went to the city across the street! Is that all? They offered food, water, and God’s blessing if they followed them, and they took refugees in droves. Half the city’s population followed them.”

“If there are such righteous people, why don’t they show up in our town? I’m afraid we’ll be killed by the gnolls.”

“…Well, maybe it’s because there are fewer people and the damage area is so large?”

“Yes, let’s say it is, because we need that hope to survive.”

The only force that has the support of the people.

They are the vigilantes, the Night Walkers.

A group of mysterious figures who have rallied under the slogan, “Even the strongest darkness is beaten back by the weakest light.”

They traveled across the continent under the somewhat childish nicknames of “Saint of the Night,” “Knight of the Night,” “Sniper of the Night,” “Warrior of the Night,” “Wealthy of the Night,” and “Queen of the Night,” respectively.

And like the old oral fairy tale ‘The Pied Piper,’ they whispered salvation with sweet words and took countless people to distant places.

People were scared even as they waited for them.

They were hopeful but wary.

Longing, curiosity, hope, anxiety, vigilance, fear… or just plain snorting at the sound of nothingness, they still follow them today.

And then.

…Bang!

The tavern door shattered open and a vigilante soldier rushed in.

“Raid, It’s a raid! Let’s go!”

At the same time, the horns of the monsters’ invasion began to echo throughout the village.

Tuuuuuu-

Even before the sound could be heard, the people in the tavern were on their feet.

The two soldiers who had just been arguing over politics quickly grabbed their swords and spears and ran, while the tavern owner put everything aside and took refuge in the cellar.

“Everyone, get to the underground cellar!”

The people in the tavern looked contemplative, but in a very familiar motion, they followed the tavern owner to the passageway below.

….

The tavern was silent in an instant.

Ppigeudeog-

It was at that time that the Wandering Knight, who had been sitting like a statue in the corner until now, moved.

Chapter 424

The Night Walkers (2)

◆

Dolores, Tudor, Sancho, and Pigi entered the tent.

Cindywendy, the Night Walkers’ sponsor, was sitting there with a serious expression

Cindywendy. Vikir’s appointed aide and lover of Osiris Le Baskerville.

She generously used her enormous assets to purchase enormous amounts of relief supplies.

Preserved food and water from all over the empire are still arriving.

What’s even more amazing is that Cindywendy has been doing this for years.

Vikir’s plan had been in the works for a very long time, as Fort Tochka was stockpiled with enough supplies to feed the entire Empire for months.

Even before Vikir appeared on the Imperial Capital under the guise of Night Hound.

But not even the great Cindywendy was fully aware of Vikir’s intentions.

The same was true for Chihuahua and MiniPin, who became Cindywendy’s left and right arms and took charge of all tasks.

“Why did Vikir ask us to gather the refugees here in the highlands? It’s been years, and I still don’t know.”

“Do they know? No matter how close you are to him, you can’t fully understand his true feelings because he doesn’t really show off to his side. We just have to do what we’re told, don’t we?”

As they talked, Dolores and the others from Colosseo Academy walked in, and they all turned their heads to look at Cindywendy.

She opened her closed eyes and turned to Dolores.

“How’s the myth creation coming along?”

Dolores nodded in response to her question.

“Yep. I’ve created a new concept called the ‘Ark,’ and I’m telling the people that anyone who comes to Tochka can be saved.”

But Dolores’s face was a little dark as she spoke.

In fact, the idea of salvation by coming to Tochka is not something that is found in the Book of Revelation or ancient texts.

It was a myth invented and manipulated by Dolores, Martin Luther, and other high-ranking priests of the Quovadis family, to make it easier to bring refugees to Tochka.

‘…I was honestly surprised that Pope Nabokov would allow it.’

When Dolores had told Pope Nabokov I of her plan, ready to be punished, Pope Nabokov I had smiled and nodded.

‘If there are no such myths, let’s create one. All myths are not from the beginning of time, but are created by man. God respects man’s free will, my child.’

When Nabokov I finished speaking, she patted Dolores on the head.

‘Your steps will soon become myths, written in the scriptures.’

Nabokov I gave all her remaining strength to Dolores, other than the strength needed for the civil war.

Total trust.

Thus, the Night Walkers were able to travel safely across the continent with the covert support of Quovadis temples located throughout the Empire.

…Quovadis, of course, was not the only one aiding the Night Walkers.

Morgue. Bourgeois, and, surprisingly, Baskerville, were also providing covert support.

Among the most helpful were Banshee of Morgue, Lovebad of Bourgeois, Mozgus of Quovadis, and Isabella of Baskerville.

Whether it’s sending supplies, sending people to protect the movement of supplies, or providing information about areas where battles are being fought or where demons are roaming.

It is thanks to these supporters and helpers from all walks of life that the Night Walkers are able to survive.

In addition, many figures were already working for the Night Walkers, who had tangled with Vikir in the Hell Tree, such as Gordon, Underdog, and Lovegood, whom he met in the College League.

A vigilante group that targets only the people, citizens, and the common people, regardless of the civil war.

The Night Walkers are this informal group that uses force without hesitation in situations where force is necessary.

Meanwhile, Cindywendy was studying the maps on the table.

Dolores asked.

“Is everything okay on the Western Continent?”

“Hmm? Alas, don’t worry. The Baskervilles are cooperating fully, and the Ballak tribes have reappeared, so trade should be fine.”

Cindywendy added as if she had remembered something.

“Oh, speaking of the Ballak, it seems… they’ve got a new guardian recently, and it’s quite the ‘trusty friend’.”

A trusted friend?

Everyone scratched their heads at that, but even Cindywendy didn’t seem to know the details.

Finally, she got to the point.

“Ah, the reason I requested today’s meeting is none other than… food and water.”

Vikir had ordered her to fortify Tochka before entering the Academy.

As a result, Cindywendy has spent almost all of her earnings on preserved food and water.

The stockpile of food and water was enough to feed the entire evacuee population for over three months.

But even so, Cindywendy was impatient.

“Vikir is at least 150 days. He told us to save enough to last five months, which is still a long way off.”

Food and water are increasingly hard to come by these days.

Between famine, drought, massive wildfires, and monster outbreaks, the price of food and water has skyrocketed.

“I’ve been saving money to buy supplies, but it’s getting harder and harder.”

Dolores gave her a concerned look.

“Well, I’m sure your wealth is not unlimited, and I’m both grateful and concerned.”

“What?”

Cindywendy turned to Dolores as if to ask what she was talking about.

Then she giggled.

“Ahahaha – what are you talking about, saintess? I’m Cindywendy, don’t you think too little of my wealth? I have plenty of money, don’t worry, I haven’t even spent 10% of it yet.”

“What? Then why…?”

Everyone’s eyes widened, including Dolores.

Cindywendy pointed to the map with a cautious expression and revealed the real reason.

“We can still buy food and water, we just need to double or triple the price. There’s no problem securing supplies… The problem is distribution and dissemination.”

Distribution and dissemination. This is also an important issue.

You can get food and water from far away.

The real big problem is how to get them here to Tochka, in the northern continent.

It’s a long and arduous journey, and if you encounter monsters, wildfires, or hordes of demons along the way, there’s no answer.

So Cindywendy has relied on the help of powerful mercenaries and knights from Baskerville and Morgue, to gather food and water along the way.

But lately, the amount of food and water reaching Tochka has been noticeably reduced.

“Some of my men are currently keeping large amounts of food and water in their strongholds, but there are new enemies blocking the supply routes.”

Cindywendy gestured to the X marks she’d made all over the map.

They were the secret supply routes to Fort Tochka.

“It’s intentional that they’re all blocking the only way to Tochka. Perhaps they know we’ve set up a hideout here and want to suffocate us.”

“Who are they?”

Tudor asked impatiently.

If they were any sort of demons or monsters, they would have already been crushed by the mercenaries hired by Cindywendy.

But even so, this kind of disruption to the supply meant that the obstacles were not of ordinary caliber.

Cindywendy stared at Tudor’s face without replying.

“….”

“…?”

“….”

“…!”

After a moment of silence, Tudor’s eyes widened in disbelief.

“Are you sure that this is the Donquixote family’s pursuit party?”

At Tudor’s question, Cindywendy nodded.

Tudor had turned his back on his family, and there was a group after him.

Donquixote La Mancha Passamonte.

The brother of Donquixote’s patriarch, Cervantes, and uncle to Tudor.

He was determined to get rid of Tudor once and for all.

Apparently, he had learned that Tudor had left the family and joined the Night Walkers, and was in pursuit.

Cindywendy patted the owl’s head with a green-gold ribbon.

“I hear that Donquixote’s ‘invincible cavalry’ is scouring the area.”

“…!”

“It’s only a matter of time before they track down the refugee convoys or food convoys coming to Fort Tochka, and with the myths that the Quovadis have created and distributed, it’s a miracle they haven’t been discovered before now. Is it lucky that no one has been too busy with the civil war to pay attention to this place?”

Actually, from the demons’ point of view, there’s no reason to pay attention.

It’s a place of refugees and no water, and it’s obvious that they won’t last long.

Of course, they don’t know how much food and water Cindywendy has stockpiled inside this iron fortress.

That’s the only variable.

But now that variable has been exposed.

The very presence of Tudor!

“…It’s me, after all.”

Tudor shook his head in disbelief.

“I can’t have this place being discovered prematurely because of me. I should get out of here as soon as possible and distract their attention elsewhere….”

“No. I don’t think that’s what Ms. Cindywendy called you here to say.”

Dolores interrupted Tudor.

Cindywendy nodded, too.

This shows that she believes and trusts Dolores.

Dolores took over from Cindywendy and spoke in a calm voice.

“This means that the moment of truth has arrived.”

“…!”

Tudor looked up. Dolores spoke again.

“You are our colleague, Tudor. We think of you just as you think of us.”

“….”

The corners of Tudor’s eyes moistened.

Dolores looked to her left and continued.

“The demons aren’t going to leave this place alone anyway, and since they’ve finally bared their teeth, we’re going to have to fight back. Whether we’re ready or not doesn’t matter, because we can’t sit back and take it.”

Sancho and Pigi agreed with her.

“If Donquixote sent a chase party after us… the main camp would be empty.”

“Maybe it’s an opportunity to assassinate a key figure!”

Living in a world that had become harsh and fierce, the two had become quite seasoned.

Dolores spoke with determination.

“This time, we won’t rely on Vikir, we’ll do it ourselves. We will capture Donquixote La Mancha Passamonte, or the 4th Corpses!”

Those who have inherited the will of Vikir must go on a demon hunt.

There was not a single Night Walker who disagreed.

Cindywendy spoke up.

“I’m saying this out of anger. Everyone remembers the failed attempt to assassinate the Leviathan Family patriarch in the past, and even the Night Fox and Ms. Ouroboros, who were strong enough to rival the Night Hound, were unsuccessful.”

Everyone knows this, but the mood is suddenly more cautious.

“Vikir said that demons grow stronger with time. It’s been a few years since Vikir’s demon hunting days, so they’re probably even stronger, so we need to be extremely careful….”

Just then.

Someone interrupted Cindywendy’s words.

“We’re in trouble!”

A knight rushed from outside and lifted the curtain with a contemplative face.

He was the one who stood guard on the castle wall.

“There’s Donquixote’s Cavalry out there, several kilometers ahead of us!”

Everyone’s faces stiffened at the news.

But that wasn’t the end of the bad news.

“The ‘Sniper of the Night’, who was returning to the fortress, is surrounded by them!”

Only one of the Night Walkers wears the nickname ‘Sniper of the Night’.

Usher Poe Bianca has been ambushed by Donquixote’s pursuers.

“…!”

Everyone scrambles to their feet and heads for the door.

…Kwakwang!

There was a man who broke through the wall and ran out into the distance.

His name was Tudor.

He was a man without a last name.

Chapter 425

The Night Walkers (3)

◆

Usher Poe Bianca.

A Divine Court Lady who was the next head of Usher family….

She is the only daughter of Usher Poe Roderick, the current patriarch of the Usher family.

As such, she should be the next in line for the title.

But reality is harsh.

Usher Poe Roderick, a powerful man so powerful that he was labeled a Bow Demon, has fallen from a mysterious illness, and his eldest daughter Bianca is still young.

While she was at Colosseo Academy, the family was turned upside down.

Usher Poe Madeline. Usher Poe Roderick’s only sister.

She had been ill from a young age and had not been involved in the family’s affairs, but at some point, she had taken the reins and started to dominate.

Madeline began to take control of all the family’s affairs.

It was as if she had been waiting all this time for Usher Poe Roderick to fall ill.

When Bianca returned to the family home after hearing her father’s excuses, she was treated with unspeakable slaps and pushes.

She, who had never even seen her father’s face, tried to keep Madeline’s position in check by gathering her maternal and collateral families as supporters.

But it was in vain.

Madeline had already recruited all of her maternal relatives and collateral families since Bianca had just entered Colosseo Academy, and Bianca ended up getting stabbed in the foot by the ax she trusted.

She realized that her family could no longer be her support.

In fact, she realized that it had become her greatest enemy.

From then on, Bianca turned her back on her family and went out into the world.

She traveled to the Donquixote Family, hoping to gain the favor of her only childhood friend and spiritual rival, Tudors, but they were in a similar situation.

The Spear King Cervantes, suddenly fell ill with an unidentified serious illness, like Roderick, and his younger brother, Passamonte, took over real power.

Moreover, unlike Bianca, Tudor were willing to openly fight the entire family.

So Bianca fled, taking Tudor with her.

They were pursued by two of the most powerful armies on earth, Donquixote’s invincible cavalry and Usher’s assassin snipers.

Their escape was long and difficult, but they managed to survive.

Tudor, the boy she had always thought of as a child, had grown into a man she could trust to have her back.

Or, sometimes, lean on.

And at some point, Bianca found herself watching him a little longer.

Someone she could share her childhood with. Someone who had been there for her in her wild and unprepared times. And someone who was now going through a difficult and painful time.

…Is that why? Bianca was uncharacteristically angry right now.

“Kukuku- That bitch is so cruel.”

Pedro Donquixote. The adjutant of Pasamonte. The man who escorted Vikir to Nouvelle Vague years ago.

He should have been imprisoned in the dungeons with his limbs cut off, but somehow he was still in one piece, leading the cavalry.

Bianca gritted her teeth.

No wonder the people who had brought Tudor to this point were now in front of her.

“I see you’re demons after all.”

“What new?”

Pedro shrugged. Then he said with a smirk.

“Isolde Poe Usher’s been itching to get his hands on you, which is good, because you’ll be worth a fortune to sell to him. Tudor, I went out to catch that cowardly rat, and I got an unexpected harvest.”

For a moment, Bianca’s brow rose.

“Cowardly rat? Isn’t that a word more fitting for you, who crawled under the demon’s crotch, and your father, who brought you to the world?”

Honor and reputation are in the blood of Donquixote.

Pedro’s eyes rolled back in his head as soon as he heard Bianca’s words.

“How dare you insult me!”

Pedro instinctively reaches for his gloves, and Bianca takes advantage of the opportunity to draw an arrow from her bow.

Peong!

Bianca had spent a relatively long time in the Hell Tree compared to others.

Based on her experience at that time, she trained diligently at the Academy.

A liquid aura unique to the Graduator was embedded in the arrow and shot out.

It looked like a long stream of sticky liquid falling horizontally to the ground.

And its power was immense.

Peoeog-

The arrow pierced the back of Pedro’s hand and went straight to his heart.

However.

“Hahahahaha! You’re making it so that there’s no gap? The Usher family’s archery skills are truly amazing.”

Pedro’s eyes glazed over with a murky energy.

He shatters the arrow, and new flesh immediately takes its place.

Bianca looks at it, and once again, Pedro and his master, Passamonte, are sure to be demons.

But there was something strange about it.

“Why aren’t the other knights reacting?”

Bianca cautiously turned and looked behind her.

Donquixote’s ‘Invincible Cavalry’.

Along with the ‘Invincible Armada’, they are the real power behind Donquixote’s military might.

How is it that they have become the minions of the demon, when they have a reputation for being so loyal?

“…!”

The sharp-eyed Bianca soon found the answer.

The faces of the members of the Invincible Cavalry were hidden from the public by their helmets, their faces obscured by their iron masks.

Every single one of them wore a stunned, dazed expression.

Their eyes were uncharacteristically cloudy, and some of them were even drooling.

‘They’re being controlled by the demon!’

That doesn’t explain it.

Perhaps the Usher family knights are in a similar state.

She had a vague idea of how Madeline might have manipulated Bianca’s supporters.

“Then so be it.”

Bianca gritted her teeth.

‘I don’t want to kill the innocent knights of the Donquixote family, but if we continue this way, we’re going to die.’

They had to fight with all their might.

Pow-

Bianca stomped the ground and let the arrow fly.

Fortunately, there is a steep rocky slope just a short distance ahead.

The cavalry would not be able to advance there.

…But that was the mistake of underestimating Donquixote’s Invincible Cavalry.

Du-du-du-du-du-

Surprisingly, Donquixote’s horse galloped up the steep, almost cliff-like slope.

“Cih. Why are those monstrous creatures being controlled by the demon?”

Bianca continued to fire arrows.

She wasn’t aiming for every single one of those horsemen.

Kwakwang! Kuleuleuleuleung-

Bianca’s arrows hit only the weak spots in the rocky cliffs.

As the traps of ropes and vines were destroyed by the arrows, massive amounts of earth and rubble began to pour down.

However, Donquixote’s Invincible Cavalry, which should have been annihilated by now, continued to push forward.

Kwakwakwakwakwakwang!

The lances of the knights pierced through the rocks and dirt, each one bearing the aura of the Graduator.

A truly terrifying sight.

Bianca gulped down a gust of wind.

To think that such things, capable of tearing landslides to shreds, roamed the battlefield.

How can any siege be impenetrable to them!

Bianca’s eyes squeeze shut as she realizes that she can’t run away and that she must take the brunt of those ignorant charges with her own body.

“Bianca!”

A thunderous shout came from above her.

Kwakwang!

A slash fired diagonally sent one of the knights in front flying backwards.

Tudor. He appeared wearing a black robe and was blocking Bianca’s path.

“Get up!”

Tudor said, spear outstretched and swinging.

Bianca was a little puzzled that Tudor didn’t offer her his arm, but then she quickly stood up.

Tudor is currently missing his left arm.

He lost it during his escape from Donquixote.

“Tudor, they’re coming for you…!”

“I know! Let’s just focus on getting back!”

Tudor swung his spear, rolling all the nearby rocks under him.

“Tudor! Bianca!”

They hear Dolores, Sancho, and Pigi’s voices behind them.

However, Donquixote’s knights, including Pedro, responded much faster.

“Surround!”

At Pedro’s order, the knights swarmed around and blocked the reinforcements, including Dolores.

At the same time, the remaining troops lifted their spears and started throwing them at Tudor.

Peog!

One of the spears pierced Tudor’s thigh and lodged in the ground.

“…!”

Tudor gritted his teeth, but he couldn’t block the shower of spears that followed.

Only.

“Get down.”

He put Bianca on his back and blocked every spear that came his way.

Peog! Peog! Peog! Peog!

Spears pierced his forearms, thighs, shoulders, and legs.

“Tudor!”

Bianca let out a tearing scream, but Tudor remained frozen in place, protecting her.

“Tearful chivalry, a fitting end.”

Pedro raised his spear with a mock tear in his eye.

And then.

Peopeong!

Pedro’s spear falls, emitting a dark aura.

…Ttug!

The spear that had been protecting Tudor all this time broke in half.

Covered in blood, Tudor falls to the ground.

Bianca, who was behind him, quickly picked him up.

“Tudor!?”

He had a gaping wound in his chest. If he didn’t get to the priest immediately, he would surely die.

But Dolores and the others hadn’t gotten past the wall built by Donquixote’s knights.

Pedro frowned.

“What are you going to do? If you surrender gracefully, we can take Tudor back to the family home and cure him. With you, of course.”

For some reason, Pedro didn’t want to kill Tudor right away.

“….”

Bianca bit her lip.

There was nothing she could do without thinking twice.

“Help me. I want to save Tudor.”

“Good! Excellent choice. Maybe we can put a little embarrassment on Isolde.”

Pedro chuckled and turned away.

Up above, he turned to withdraw his cavalry from Dolores and the other Night Walkers.

“Hey! That’s enough! Now withdraw…!?”

But. Pedro didn’t finish his sentence.

Eu-jig!

A heavy fist flew out and crushed him in the face.

Kwakwakwakwang!

Soon, golden fists protruding from the ground began to strike down the cavalry of the Donquixote family.

Peopeong! Kudeudeudeug! Kwang!

Rings made of earth rise above the ground, tripping the hooves of galloping cavalry horses.

“Ugh! What the….”

Someone fell in front of Pedro, who was spitting out a smashed nose, a busted lip, and a chunk of broken tooth in a stream of blood from his mouth.

A black robe and hat, and short-cut white hair visible through them.

A woman who had grown taller but still had a childlike face was standing quietly in front of Tudor and Bianca.

“Sorry. I’m a little late.”

Tick-tock – the sound of a busy pocket watch.

Sinclaire was extending her hand towards Bianca.

Chapter 427

The Night Walkers (5)

◆

Gugugug-

The heavy mace rose upward and fell down.

Dolores swung the mace and thought of the past.

She remembered how, after the incident with the Hell Tree, she had doubted her powers and had personally asked Pope Nabokov I to train her.

At the time, Nabokov I had told her.

‘A third-class healer heals their allies when they are injured.’

‘A second-class healer heals their allies immediately when they are injured.’

‘…But a first-class healer does not.’

Nabokov I’s teachings have shaped Dolores today.

“Eliminate the risk of injury to your allies before they get hurt!”

Dolores’ mace came down like a bolt of lightning.

And it smashed Pedro’s face flat.

…Thwack!

With a terrifying sound, Pedro’s body flew backwards and crashed to the ground.

Bianca asked in a dazed tone.

“…How do you carry that mace?”

“Umm. Normally, I’m supposed to slip a sack between my back muscles and use my strength to tighten it, but I don’t have that kind of muscle and strength yet, so I just sneak it on my back with a string, and cover the mace part underneath with my skirt!”

Finishing her explanation, she picked up the mace once more and began ruling out any factors that might injure her ally.

Ppeoeog-

Another mace came crashing down on Pedro’s head as he lay dazed on the ground.

“Ahh!?”

Pedro snapped back to reality.

His eyeballs felt like they were going to pop out, no they actually popped out.

He wasn’t sure if the burning in his vision was from exposure to divine power or the pain of the physical impact.

“W-what do cavalry do!?”

Pedro shouted for help, but the Invincible Cavalry was no where near.

Sinclaire’s golden wall, Bianca’s arrows, falling rocks, and Dolores’s holy shield were blocking their charge.

Furthermore, with Pedro’s mental magic weakened, the knights within the cavalry were unleashing their brainwashing one by one.

Pedro gritted his teeth.

He had made a mistake by being too greedy to capture Tudor and Bianca.

He’d made a bad decision in the first place, choosing a steep mountainous terrain that wasn’t conducive to cavalry.

“If I can just get this guy, I’ll be fine.”

Tudor’s assessment of the situation was equally quick.

Behind them, mercenaries hired by Cindywendy and reinforcements from the various Families descended to block the cavalry, while Dolores, Tudor, Sancho, Pigi, Bianca, and Sinclaire focused on Pedro.

“How dare you brats!”

Pedro shouted back, his Graduator Superlative and demonic aura radiating from him.

Demonization. Just as Pedro’s form was about to turn terrifying.

…Flash!

Dolores’s even more powerful Holy Shield crushed Pedro’s entire body.

Above him, Sinclaire summons countless golden hands to crush the demon’s body.

Tudor, Sancho, Pigi, and Bianca also used their full power to cut off Pedro’s limbs.

[Aaaaahhh!]

As a demon, Pedro wriggled violently, but he was helpless until the mercenaries sent by Cindywendy arrived and fired arrows at him.

In the end, only after the twenty-four stakes that Dolores had given divine power were driven into his torso did Pedro become quiet.

With his capture, Donquixote’s Invincible Cavalry halted.

They awoke from their dazed stupor and slowly began to recognize reality.

“Where am I?”

“Huh! Why am I in this place?”

“Tudor, Master Tudor!?”

Tudor stared at the knights of the main family who were slowly regaining their senses.

Only a few members of the Invincible Cavalry had gathered here, and most of them were probably far away in the civil war.

“What a tragedy, the proud knights of La Mancha dying in vain, brainwashed by a mere demon.”

Tudor’s hateful gaze turned to Pedro, who lay on the ground, groaning.

“You should have died long ago when you sent my friend to prison. Sweeten the death you have been granted.”

[Now, wait! Spare my life, spare my life, I’ll do anything, I’ll tell you everything, but spare my life…!]

Pedro had been in a similar situation once before, when he was escorting Vikir to Nouvelle Vague.

He had survived by selling information and begging for his life before, so everyone except Tudor decided to interrogate him a little longer.

Tudor, who had been arguing for Pedro’s execution, agreed with everyone.

“You’re going to have to tell me everything you know, honestly and completely, or I’m not sure I can guarantee your life.”

[Hiig-]

“But if you answer honestly, I will spare your life. On the honor of Donquixote.”

Behind the calmly speaking Tudor, the knights of Donquixote, who had been brainwashed, were searing with rage.

Pedro groaned in pain, but managed to answer each question.

As a result, the Night Walkers were able to learn many things.

They learned that the true name of their target was Cimeries, and that Cimeries had the power to make humans reckless and brave.

Other information included that most of Donquixote’s Invincible Cavalry had been dispatched to the conflict zone, that the Invincible Armada was at anchor far away from the family home due to the drought, and that Cimeries, who was wearing the shell of Pasamonte, was currently prioritizing the safety of Tudor.

“Why do you want to take me and Tudor alive? If you’re just going for static elimination, why not just take our heads? Wouldn’t that be a lot easier?”

[I, I don’t know! I’m serious! He didn’t tell me!]

Pedro shook his head in response to Bianca’s question.

Then, Tudor asked.

“And my father? Is he safe?”

[….]

Pedro was silent for a moment.

Then, in a stuttering tone, he said.

[Well, of course he’s fine. His health isn’t the best…]

“Really! Is my father really okay?”

[I, I’m a demon myself, but I was once a knight of Donquixote, I don’t lie!]

“Thank you, God. For protecting my father….”

Tudor closed his eyes and said a prayer of thanks.

Pedro looked up and opened his mouth.

[Now I’ve told you everything I know, I mean it. Release me. I’m so drained of magic, I have no strength to resist. Surely, a Knight of Donquixote would not break his word of honor?]

For a moment, Tudor’s eyes narrowed.

“Yes, sir. I promised my honor. As a Knight of the Donquixote family.”

[Yes. A knight of La Mancha is more honorable and dignified than anything else. I am not even worthy to speak of it. ….]

Pedro said gloomily, in a self-help tone.

But Tudor shook his head.

“Yes, you are unworthy of Donquixote’s honor, but neither am I.”

[…?]

Pedro looks up, puzzled.

In front of him, Tudor slowly raised the broken blade of his spear.

“My name is Tudor.”

The blade gleams brightly.

“No surname.”

It plunges straight down toward Pedro’s throat.

Pedro’s head was cut off without any time to shout.

Dark blood spattered the ground.

Tudor continued in a low voice.

“So the honor of Donquixote has nothing to do with me.”

◆

Deep within the interior of Fort Tochka. The meeting place of the Night Walkers.

“Let’s retreat.”

Tudor said.

The way a general from the Warring States period who appears in the historical tale usurped the country is to withdraw the army and take the throne.

“We’ll make it look like we’re returning with no earnings, march bloodlessly to Donquixote’s territory, then sneak into the castle and assassinate Pasamonte.”

Everyone nodded in agreement that it was a good plan.

Even the usually skeptical and cantankerous Cindywendy agreed for once.

“As it is, Donquixote’s army is blocking our supply routes. If we don’t get Donquixote back, we won’t have enough food and water to feed the refugees, and that’s a problem for Vikir’s plan.”

Moreover, since they know that Night Walkers are gathered at Tochka Fortress, they need to move as quickly as possible.

Advantage. If there’s going to be a fight, it’s a hundred times better to strike first.

Tudor’s body seemed to be shaking at the thought of saving his father and restoring his family name.

Dolores turned to everyone.

“Among us, Sinclaire and I are probably the only ones who have directly experienced the power of the Ten Corpse.”

Dolores had faced Dantalian, Belial, and Amdusias, and Sinclaire had faced Belial.

The power of the 10 Corpses that Dolores and Sinclaire talk about is so enormous that it cannot even be compared to someone like Pedro.

“Even now, after all this time, it’s probably even stronger, so we need to be prepared.”

Even Vikir had always been prepared when dealing with the Ten Corpses, and if that wasn’t enough, he would risk his life.

Everyone’s expressions became determined at the thought of finally going to deal with the culprit.

“I’m familiar with the troop deployments and terrain within the family.”

Tudor briefly drew a map of the family’s territory.

Everyone watched as Tudor gave a detailed briefing on where the traps were and where the secret passages were hidden.

Suddenly, Pigi muttered in a low voice.

“…I wish I had Vikir with me when this happened.”

All eyes turned to Pigi.

Pigi waved his hands in embarrassment.

“Oops! I’m sorry. I didn’t mean to sound weak….”

Dolores smiled and put a hand on Pigi’s shoulder.

“Don’t worry, Pigi. We all have those thoughts.”

“Well, I’m still… sorry. I thought I threw cold water on it.”

Pigi lowers his head in a whispering voice.

Tudor comforts him.

“I think about that sometimes, too, how happy we’d be if he miraculously appeared in front of us. But he can’t be here right now, trapped in Nouvelle Vague.”

“…That’s right.”

“What we need to do now is not vaguely dream of him being with us, but to do the homework he left us to do, and more importantly, to get him out of Nouvelle Vague.”

Tudor’s words echoed in everyone’s minds.

“Vikir is definitely alive, and we will see him again one day, but we must perform well enough to be worthy of his presence before then.”

Dolores echoed Tudor’s sentiments.

“We need to grow up too, so that Vikir doesn’t have to do it all on his own. We want to let him know that he can rely on us a little bit more.”

Sancho, Bianca, and Sinclaire nodded wordlessly.

Even if they don’t open their mouths to speak, they all know what they mean.

Only Cindywendy was fiddling under the table with a letter she had received relatively recently containing an announcement from Nouvelle Vague.

<Night Hound ‘Vikir Van Baskerville’>[ Death ].

An official report from the Nouvelle Vague.

It stated that Night Hound had died in a failed escape attempt from Nouvelle Vague.

‘I suppose I don’t need to tell them this.’

Cindywendy crumpled it up with a small sigh.

‘For those who walk the night, Vikir is an unbreakable faith.’

It was impossible to break that faith.

‘…I’m going to need a miracle, really.’

Even Cindywendy, who never believed in luck or miracles, had this thought, and everyone hoped and waited for the return of Vikir.

Chapter 429

The Lion King (2)

◆

Hwiiiing-

The sea breeze had been blowing hard for days, carrying a strange heat, as if a volcano had erupted far offshore, as the fishermen had said.

The stench from the heat makes the whole of Donquixote’s castle, built on the cliffs of the coast, shiver.

The distinctive smell of dried fish.

This is the smell that comes from the process of drying the strangely large number of large fish caught due to the warmer water temperature.

The fishermen dried the excessive catch all along the coast, and the smell spread over a wide area on the sea breeze, even reaching Donquixote’s castle.

…However.

The stench in the hallway now was of a different kind.

King of Spear ‘Cervantes Donquixote’.

Donquixote’s family patriarch and one of the seven warriors who support the empire.

The Great Emperor of the Sea (帊大帝) who ruled the blue sea with the strongest cavalry army, the Invincible Cavalry, and the strongest navy, the Armada.

And the father of one of the most promising heroes of the next generation, Tudor Donquixote.

As soon as Tudor opened the door, he saw the father he’d been longing to see.

However, Tudor’s first emotion upon seeing his father was not one of sadness or joy.

“…?”

Questioning. It’s nothing special.

It was the kind of innocent question that makes anyone scratch their head, not knowing what they’re looking at.

A bedroom with no lights on.

Something black was moving on the large, desolate bed.

It was in the shape of a human, but it was twitching and trembling, and something was wrong.

Tudor takes a step forward, not knowing what it is.

Pasasasasasag-

Sensing the presence of humans, it began to move wildly.

Countless black waves spread out in all directions around the bed.

“…!”

Only then did Tudor discover the identity of those black things. They were cockroaches, flies, ants, centipedes, and various small creatures.

Weeeeeeng-

The stench intensified and the unpleasant sound of flapping wings echoed.

A stark scene was revealed above the bed, which was teeming with an enormous number of pests.

Cervantes the Spear King.

A superhuman who had carved holes in mountains with a single thrust of his spear and parted oceans with a single swing of his spear.

The entity that owned the most extensive territory among the Seven Great Families of the Empire.

The King of the Meadows, who ruled the entirety of the sea.

He lay on his bed, nothing but a skeleton and dried skin.

His body was infested with insects, and his two bony arms, with nothing but bones left, were tightly grasping the long spear that penetrated his stomach.

That’s where the stench and insects came from.

Thud-

Tudor slumped to his knees.

“…Ah, Father.”

A voice muttered despairingly.

An attitude of disbelief at what he was seeing.

Silence. Deadly silence.

It couldn’t be more silent, even in the grave.

No one dared to speak in the face of the horror before them.

And no one dared to speak to the fallen Tudor.

Best friend, best teacher, best father.

Tudor’s pupils fluttered like a sailboat in a storm as he witnessed the miserable end of such a being.

Then.

“Wait.”

Someone covered Tudor’s eyes from behind.

It was Bianca, her voice shaking violently as she spoke pleadingly into Tudor’s ear.

“Let’s just do this for a second. Okay?”

Bianca desperately pulled Tudor into a hug. With trembling hands, she covered Tudor’s eyes.

After a long moment of silence, Tudor opened his mouth like a collapsing dam spewing water.

“…Father!”

Tudor didn’t speak for a long time after that.

Dolores, who had been standing beside him, stepped forward.

With her bare hands, she swatted the insects off the bed.

When they were gone, Dolores covered Cervantes’s bare face with her own handkerchief.

“This is my body, which I will offer for you. Ite, missa est. Rest in peace. And go to a good place.”

A saint’s mass. It was a short but heartfelt farewell.

As soon as Bianca released her hand, Tudor collapsed on top of Cervantes’ mummified body and choked back his tears.

The sound of water filling the parched furrows.

Emotions of pain, sorrow, hatred, and regret swirled through him.

“…You brought it on yourself.”

Everyone, including Dolores, could see that this was the end of Cervantes.

Cervantes’ cause of death was clear to all.

His body, weakened by poison and mental magic, had been taken by the demon, and he held the spear upside down with his own will.

And with truly superhuman will and patience that ordinary people cannot even imagine, he plunged the spear deep into his abdomen, penetrating all the way under the bed.

The whirlpool of black soot left on the bed, walls, floor, and ceiling clearly showed how hard the demon had worked to steal Cervantes’ soul and take over his body.

Dolores scanned Cervantes’ body with her holy power.

All strange residues, including miasma, were being purified.

“Even with his weakened mind, he resisted the demon to the end.”

“I know. I knew it. I expected it to some extent, but….”

Tudor replied, his voice like boiling lead.

It’s no wonder Cervantes had a strong mind.

Because he was the ruler of the sea and the ruler of the meadows.

…The question is what made his body, which was as strong as his soul, sick.

Dolores looked at the floor beneath the bed.

She could see the rotting carcasses of insects.

Dried and powdered, they must have been the first to pounce on Cervantes’ body.

“…I can feel the poison. It also carries with it the spirit of a very terrible plague.”

Dolores said as she touched the insect carcass.

The old, rotting insects must have died from gnawing on Cervantes’ body, which was tainted with poison.

Cervantes’ body still had a faint trace of the poison.

It had faded with time, but Dolores could still make out the poison that had killed him.

It was one Dolores was familiar with.

“…Red Death!”

He remembered the first time he’d met Vikir.

‘There’s a plague in the slums.’

Dolores had thought him suspicious at the time and had tried to avoid meeting him, but the matter he brought seemed so serious that she had to talk to him.

That’s when he was first introduced to the dreaded plague of the Red Death.

‘It’s good to know that I’ve dealt with the Red Death before.’

Dolores knows the plague well, having cleaned it up herself.

The Red Death is a plague caused by an extremely poisonous poison created by Leviathan Family.

The poison that had even poisoned Cervantes the Spear King seemed to be a much improved version of that.

‘It has become much more severe and demanding that even the Spear King could not do anything about it.’

Even the faded scent of the poison is enough to send chills down the spine.

Dolores remembered well the sensation of this poison in Cervantes.

Meanwhile. Tudor gritted his teeth.

“…Poisonous Leviathan!”

That was the name of the enemies who poisoned his father.

The ones who created the hateful poison and pestilence known as the Red Death.

Tudor’s gaze then turned to the spear in Cervantes’s abdomen.

‘Gungnir’, a spear symbolizing the head of the Donquixote family.

Cervantes’ spearmanship, which boasted the speed of a lightning strike and the heaviness of a tidal wave, could not be handled by an ordinary spear.

While all the spears of the most renowned masters broke, only Gungnir was strong and sturdy enough to truly embody Cervantes’ spearmanship.

Although it is heavy, it has a high mana conductivity and does not leave any residual scratches no matter how strong the impact, so there is no need to sharpen the blade.

Tudor gripped Gungnir’s polearm through bloody tears.

“I will surely avenge my father by killing Passamonte, and every last one of those involved in this affair will pay for it.”

Then something surprising happened.

Tsutsutsuts…

Gungnir began to tremble slightly and was then slowly pulled out of Cervantes’ body.

It was as if Cervantes was moving his hands on his own.

Teong-

Gungnir slipped into Tudor’s grasp, like a magnet finding its rightful place.

Tudor’s grip on Gungnir nearly caused him to fall forward under its weight, but he managed to hold on to it.

Even Cervantes was holding Gungnir with both hands, so it must have been quite heavy, but Tudor stood up without any hesitation.

And like a lie.

Tsutsutsutsutsu…pulsseog-

Cervantes’ flesh, which had maintained its posture while being eaten by countless insects, began to crumble into powder.

His remains, reduced to black and red ash, no longer smelled as foul as before.

Only the pungent aroma of his favorite cigarette could be detected.

Right at that moment.

Clap- Clap- Clap- Clap-

In the corner where the wall met the wall, in the darkness of the inner room, someone stood up, clapping.

…!

The 6 Night Walkers, who hadn’t felt any sign of human activity in the room up until this point, stood up straight.

Then, in the dim light, the faces of the uninvited guests were revealed.

A white-faced, tall man with a slender build.

“You’ve finally been picked. Gungnir.”

Donquixote La Mancha Passamonte.

No, it was the appearance of ‘Cimeries’, the 4th Corpse.

Chapter 431

The Lion King (4)

◆

…Rumbling!

Poking its head through the crumbling floor was the head of a giant horse, and its body was made up of dark tree bark.

The presence of horses was not surprising for a knight, but this one’s appearance was very familiar.

A bust that those who graduated from the Colosseo Academy cannot help but remember.

<‘The 5th Corpse’ Amdusias>

Danger Rating : S+

Size: ?

Found in: The Serpent’s Womb, deep within the Gates of Destruction.

-Also known as ‘5th Corpse’.

One of the Ten Plagues, the natural enemy of mankind, incomprehensible and unkillable.

“Take away the life of the first born that year.”

– 『The Ten Commandments』 10:Top –

‘Amdusias’, the unicorn of the abyss. 5th of the Ten Corpses.

This demon, in the form of a giant horse, roared with its mouth open at the Night Walkers.

“H-how!?”

“Didn’t Vikir exterminate that thing!”

Hearing Tudor and Bianca exclaim in horror, Passamonte chuckled and replied.

“It’s not real. It’s a remnant of Amdusias wandering the Imperial Capital. Of course, it cannot exert the same power as the main body, but it can replicate some of its powers.”

The spirit of Amdusias shattered and scattered into countless fragments.

Passamonte seemed to have picked up one of the larger pieces.

“Amdusias was a great horse that I always wanted to tame. Is there anything more honorable than taming a beast-type demon that is treated as an equal? And I owe it all to you.”

Passamonte climbed onto Amdusias’s back.

“Die, demon!”

Tudor raised his Gungnir and swung it.

“Now that I have a good horse, I must have a good body and a good weapon, right? Alas, Tudor, recklessness is the privilege of the young; You don’t know how long I’ve waited for my courage to mature before your body.”

The words only tore at Passamonte’s torn mouth even more.

At the same time.

Chararararak-!

The rough tree bark that covered Amdusias’ body began to snap like tentacles in unison.

Everyone could tell that these were no ordinary trees.

“…Tentacles!?”

Dolores exclaimed in horror.

It seemed that Passamonte had even gained Amdusias’s ability to manipulate plant power.

Though all that was here was a few roots of the Hell Tree, it was enough to create the imaginary world once again.

“The Hell Tree is perfect for destroying the minds of its prey. It is perfect for taking away the body without a scratch. Ah, you’ve experienced it, so you know it well.”

Passamonte’s voice flows smoothly.

The roots of the Hell Tree caught the current and stretched out with incredible speed, enveloping the Night Walkers.

Kiriririririririk-

Everything was as they remembered it.

The roots of the Hell Tree wrapped around Dolores and everyone else, dragging their minds down to the bottom of a deep, dark abyss.

“I can see why Amdusias was so fascinated by the souls that matured in the Hell Tree.”

Passamonte muttered in a low voice.

“I’ll let them ripen slowly, and take them out when they’re at their most tattered. Souls are like fruit, they’re sweetest and softest just before they rot.”

Only the sound of laughter, tinged with a slimy appetite, hovered in the abyss.

◆

“…Keugh.”

Tudor held his pounding head and lifted his head.

Parched soil, barren land with nothing, dark red sky.

He had awakened in the Hell Tree for the first time in nearly four years.

The good news was that he woke up in the same place, not separated from Dolores, Sancho, Pigi, Bianca, Sinclaire, and the others.

“Where am we?”

Everyone was stunned by the scene that greeted them upon awakening.

Parched black soil, gnarled dead trees, burning earth, and smoke billowing from everywhere blocked their vision.

They had all been trapped in the Hell Tree before, but this was the first time they had been thrown into such a harsh environment from the beginning.

A vague shadow loomed through the thick atmosphere.

It was a large stone statue, weathered by the winds of time and no longer in perfect shape.

There were many chipped pieces here and there, but it was still possible to make out the face of the statue.

The sharp-eyed Bianca was the first to speak.

“These are the characters of the Iron Blooded Swordsman Baskerville. I believe it’s the patriarch, Marquis Hugo Le Baskerville, and the young master, Count Osiris Le Baskerville?”

It’s not hard to guess, then, who this space, this imaginary world, might be connected to.

“Could this be a visual representation of Vikir’s inner world?”

Everyone nodded slowly at Tudor’s words.

Once upon a time, Vikir had gone alone to capture Amdusias on the Flowing River.

Later, they were told that Vikir fought his final battle with Amdusias in a space that visualized his inner self.

This is exactly how Vikir described the scene in his inner world.

A barren mountain where the leaves of every tree were burnt and crumbled, the soil dried up, the insects died, and the animals were reduced to skeletons.

There were five such mountains spread out before them.

Everyone who entered the mental world instinctively recognized them.

Each of those massive, sedimentary mountains was the embodiment of the burden and responsibility that Vikir carried in his heart.

There were many other things that struck Dolores, Tudor, Sancho, Pigi, and Sinclaire.

Mountain of Corpses and Sea of ??Blood.

A swamp of blood and flesh. A mountain of bones. Rivers, lakes, and oceans of blood.

Demon and human corpses tangled together to form hills and valleys, ravines and canyons, and everywhere boiling lava and sulfur erupted in soft explosions.

Hungry monsters compete to eat the corpse, and sorrowful screams, cries, and deathly words come from all over without end.

The Outer Demon World. Desperation and horror beyond measure.

Where on earth do the great chains of chaos, the whirlpool of hatred, and all these terrible phenomena come from?

“ …What kind of world has Vikir been living in?”

Dolores took it all in, first in amazement, then in sadness and pity.

Tudor, Bianca, Sancho, and Pigi were speechless.

“What kind of a sight does a man ever see in his life?”

“I didn’t think he was a normal guy, but… what the hell was he doing?”

“He’s been living in this kind of environment, no wonder his personality is so dull.”

“…I feel so bad for Vikir.”

“….”

Sinclaire simply held it all in her eyes with a wistful gaze.

And then.

Footsteps pounded the ground.

Over the burning horizon, a ragged horse trotted toward them.

“…!”

Dolores’s eyes widened.

Amdusias. Fifth of the Tenth.

A demon in the form of a huge, bulky horse.

But somehow, it was now walking on the ground in the form of an old, dirty donkey.

It looked precariously close to collapse, as if its strength would soon fail and it would perish.

Tudor held his spear out to stop Amdusias.

“Hey. Stop!”

Then.

…Kung!

As soon as Tudor blocked his path, Amdusias fell to the ground and bit out his tongue.

“ …Uh? What, I didn’t do anything!”

Tudor hurriedly waved his hand as Bianca narrowed her eyes next to him.

Dolores, meanwhile, looked at Amdusias’ body on the ground.

It appeared to be a tiny fraction of the many fragments of consciousness left behind by the real Amdusias.

It spoke in a weary, almost fading voice.

[…Run away. A monster is coming.].

At the words, everyone shook their heads in disbelief.

Amdusias continued, tears in his eyes.

[This is the realm of the monster who destroyed the Hell Tree and imprisoned me in his mind. I don’t know how you got here, but you’d better run away quickly, for the monster’s inner world is so desolate and devastated that even demons have mental breakdowns after being trapped inside for so long… hi-hi… hihehehehe-]

Those were the last words of Amdusias’ thought fragment.

Tsutsutsutsuts…

Amdusias’s soul fragment turns to black powder and crumbles.

It seemed that Pasamonte had gotten hold of the Amdusias inside Vikir and was manipulating him.

“I don’t really understand what’s going on, but… what you’re saying is that when we were trapped in the Hell Tree, we were trapped in a fragment of the Hell Tree that was a copy of Vikir’s mind, and now this is the landscape of Vikir’s inner world, right?”

Everyone nodded at Tudor’s summary.

Not sure if it makes sense, but it’s the way things are, so they’ll have to accept it.

“I think it’s the result of the combined powers of 5th and 4th Corpse, and we need to get out of this world first.”

No one disagreed with Dolores’ words.

Passamonte’s intention is to trap everyone here and gradually break their minds.

It was clear that humans would not last long in this harsh environment, where even demons would lose their sense of self and crumble.

“Damn it, this is the imaginary world, and I can’t even decide for myself. If I don’t get my shit together, Passamonte, will he take my body?”

Tudor broke out in a cold sweat and looked around.

But the landscape of this world, so full of enemies and nothing but blackness, was enough to drive him mad.

‘What kind of life has Vikir lived?’

This is the only thought that commonly appears in everyone’s mind.

Right then.

[…Demon].

Behind their backs. A voice that made everyone’s bodies stiffen.

But the body didn’t react in a negative way.

It was the voice they had longed for, the voice they had wanted to hear.

[…Demon].

It was the voice of an old comrade, a close friend, who had gone to a place where they would never meet again.

“Vikir!?”

Pigi was the first to turn his head.

Dolores, Sinclaire, Tudor, Sancho, and Bianca also hurriedly turned their heads to look at the place where the voice was coming from.

And there stood a figure that matched everyone’s thoughts.

Vikir.

Vikir Van Baskerville.

First year at Colosseo Academy.

A model student who had never missed a class.

And the Night Hound, the worst villain the entire Empire had ever seen.

[…Demons kill]

He remained the same, unchanged from four years ago.

In this desolate, lonely place. All this time. Alone.

Chapter 432

The Returned Hound (1)

◆

[…Demons kill]

Vikir muttered in a low voice.

Dolores and the other graduates of the Colosseo Academy were surprised to see such Vikir, but then they realized.

That’s not Vikir. It’s a fragment of the imaginary world, that were not yet disposed of when Amdusias was eliminated four years ago.

The residual thoughts remaining within it are merely imitating the image of Vikir.

“…But even so.”

“It really does look like Vikir.”

Tudor and Bianca broke out in a cold sweat.

While everyone has changed a lot in the past four years, both internally and externally, Vikir in front of them is the same person he was four years ago.

“Now that I think about it, Vikir was so young.”

“He must have been hunting those terrifying demons in his young body.”

Sancho and Pigi both groaned.

“….”

“….”

Dolores and Sinclaire remained speechless.

Their gazes were tinged with sadness, wistfulness, and longing as they stared at the residual thoughts that had once been part of Vikir’s subconscious.

But.

Then something happened that shattered all of their tender feelings.

[…Demons kill!]

Vikir’s residual thoughts.

The ego that was once a part of Vikir’s inner self began to swing its sword in their direction.

Kwa-kwakwakwakwakwang!

A terrifying blow swept across the land.

Everyone, including Dolores, hurriedly fled, feeling a sense of sadness.

That’s right. Now was not the time for them to pity Vikir.

No matter how devastated Vikir was inside, he was an absolute force at the peak of his Swordmaster powers.

“Uuuuuh- why are you attacking us!”

“Ugh, it’s because he’s been trapped in here for the past four years? He’s so aggressive.”

Tudor and Bianca were in the front, so they were the first to be attacked.

Kwagigigigigig-!

The sight of teeth flying and tearing in all directions made them feel like small herbivores being hunted by a giant beast.

Overwhelming fear. A sense of power that they couldn’t resist. Instincts screaming like crazy. Run away now!

Grumbling-

A fierce storm of teeth, an aura like a black, blazing fire.

Vikir’s eyes, tearing between them, blazing with nothing but an infernal void.

It was a terrifying glare that one could only think of avoiding, but not the will to fight back.

[…Demons kill].

A fiery hatred for the demon.

But it’s not just demons that it’s burning, it’s everything in the world.

“ …That’s right. Because there are only demons in this world, and he moves to kill everything he encounters.”

Dolores gritted her teeth.

The size of the peaks and mountain ranges that rose up behind them was an indication of the burden and responsibility Vikir carried.

Perhaps he carries more on his shoulders than any mere mortal would dare to imagine.

‘I’ve felt it since the first time I saw you, Night Hound.’

A feeling Dolores had vaguely sensed in the distance as he served the sick in the slums.

It was a feeling that Dolores was now firmly reaffirming.

Meanwhile, Sinclaire was analyzing Vikir in detail.

“I think that’s what it is.”

“That? What is that?”

“…A humanoid creature that lives only for battle. A crystallization of the residual thoughts of a noble knight blackened.”

Sinclaire answered Bianca’s question while wiping off a cold sweat.

“The Death Knight.”

At that, everyone’s heads snapped up to look at Vikir’s face.

“One. …one. …two. …three. …four. …five. …six. …seven. …eight.”

Then they counted the number of teeth Vikir was currently showing.

Vikir, who fought Amdusias with a whistle during the events of the Hell Tree.

Everyone clearly remembered the path of the teeth drawn by his sword at that time.

Eight. That was the number of teeth Vikir had drawn.

And now, in front of them, the number of teeth Vikir was drawing.

“…Nine.”

Nine.

Vikir was drawing nine teeth with the tip of his sword.

Kwa-kwakwakwakwakwakwakwakwang!

Nine streaks of teeth ripped through the earth and sky, tearing them apart.

Disorder and no rules. However, as far as destructive power goes, the swordsmanship is truly formidable.

“Ugh, this is what we have to dodge to survive in this barren world?”

“I can see why the fragment of Amdusias dried up earlier.”

Tudor and Bianca took a sharp step back.

Baskerville 9th Form.

Vikir’s remnants of consciousness, which were able to use it, spewed out terrifying killing intent and turned his head left and right.

…Udeug! …udeudeug!

No matter how they look at it, it does not belong to a living human being.

It was as if a fragment of Vikir’s self had achieved some sort of awakening after all the fighting and suffering it had endured while wandering this doomed world.

“We have no choice but to fight.”

Dolores said, biting her lip.

Paas!

Eventually, a sacred wall blocked Vikir’s path.

[…?]

Vikir’s remnants of consciousness are startled by the energy that is completely different from that of the demon.

However.

Bam!

There are no exceptions. The Death Knight destroys everything in its path.

Baskerville 4th Form. Four strands of strikes pounded Dolores’s shields.

“Brother!”

Sinclaire joined the battle.

She pulled up the gold vein from beneath the ground and added her own golden defense wall to Dolores’ sacred defense wall.

Kukung-

A terrifying impact ripped through the barrier, tearing it apart.

The moment.

“…!”

“…!”

Dolores and Sinclaire felt waves of intense emotions surging through their minds.

And Tudor, Sancho, Pigi, and Bianca, who were picking up the pieces of their auras, must have felt the same thing.

Every time the swords meet and blood splatters, a wave of emotion rushes through their heart as if it were cutting into their heart.

That is the emotional wound that Vikir has suffered throughout his life.

It wasn’t physical, but a collection of emotions: pain, solitude, hatred, loneliness, sadness, and loss.

“…!”

Everyone was focused on the visible pain, not the shadow of emotion that lay beneath.

The resolve that Vikir always carried in his heart, and the past that he relived over and over again, filled everyone’s minds.

Empathy. In the truest sense of the word.

Dolores, Tudor, Sancho, Pigi, Bianca, and Sinclaire realized.

The loneliness of being raised as hounds amidst all the discrimination.

The loss of comrades-in-arms who were the only ones who cared.

The grief of being betrayed by those you trusted.

The desolation of being abandoned and executed by your loyal master.

The helplessness of watching so many of the people you tried to protect die like trash.

Lost, tortured, fighting, biting, dying, killing, struggling.

…Yes, struggling. Always struggling.

Illegitimate son of an abandoned concubine, hence the Van middle name.

A life of loneliness and suffering, even though he had to work hundreds of times harder than his siblings because he wasn’t even born with a surname like “La” or “Le,” which were given to him.

This is the life of the Night Hound.

This was Vikir’s last life, a life of war and destruction.

Juruk-

Tears fall from his eyes without anyone knowing who came first.

His body was being torn to shreds in the maelstrom of bombardment, but it was his heart that ached more.

“Vikir has been carrying these feelings in his heart all this time.”

“…I can’t believe he’s been through this physically.”

“I can’t believe he’s survived all this.”

“What the hell, how can a human being do this?”

Tudor, Sancho, Pigi, and Bianca are deeply disturbed by their newfound companion.

Sinclaire, who is also forming a barrier, bites her lip so tightly that it bleeds.

‘I didn’t realize your past was this bad.’

To be honest, she thought she was the saddest, loneliest person in the world.

But now, feeling the sword of emotion slashing through her body, she knew.

I see it so clearly.

-‘Now is not the time to think about a relationship.’

-‘…Now?’

-‘?’

-‘Not now, right? Just not ‘now’. So you’ll have some time later, after you’ve achieved your goal?’

-‘My goal is on a very long and difficult road. It’s still a long way off…’

-‘I know. For someone of your caliber to say that, you must be very ambitious indeed. Then one day, when you’ve achieved everything you want.’

-‘….’

-‘Will you accept me then?’

She realized then how immature and foolish she sounded.

What a burden it put on him.

‘…If that day ever comes.’

And what a heavy heart, what a desperate sincerity, what an answer he had given to what he thought was just a way out of the situation.

Meanwhile.

“….”

Dolores could barely keep her hands and feet from shaking.

‘Vikir, come on, you’re a strong man!’

She shouted to herself as she faced the storm of hits raging before her.

It’s a good thing they’re aimless now, because if they were any more accurate, they’d tear these defenses apart like paper.

She carefully moved between the swords.

The sword pierced the barrier, leaving a long line of blood on her body, but Dolores was undeterred.

Then, an artifact was pulled from her chest pocket.

The Mirror of Truth. A mirror that reveals the true colors of those it reflects.

Dolores wished to show this to the remnants of Vikir’s rampaging, self-absorbed mind.

She wanted to help him see who he really was, how valuable and brilliant he was.

Then.

Like a lie, the storm of bombardment paused.

Turning to Vikir, who stood still, Dolores took out a mirror as a last resort.

Faasshh.

And there, in the mirror, was Vikir’s reflection.

No longer the pale face of four years ago, but a man’s face with thicker, darker lines, staring back at Vikir’s remnants.

Sincerity. Uprightness. Strong conviction. A face that showed something like steely determination.

Dolores smiled faintly as she felt her body relax.

“Yes, this neat and tall figure, this is who you really are.”

She spoke with sincerity.

Even if she crumbled into a handful of dust at this very moment, if she could lighten the burden of this lone man in front of her just a little bit….

….

…However.

Reality played out a little differently than Dolores had imagined.

“I know.”

The Vikir in the mirror opened his mouth to speak.

“?”

Dolores looked dumbfounded for a moment.

‘Did the Mirror of Truth even have this feature?’

But her thoughts didn’t last long.

Swoosh.

A palm silently covered the mirror.

Yes, it did. Dolores hadn’t realized she hadn’t gotten the mirror out of her hand.

…Then what is that Vikir in front of her now?

Dolores raised her head once more and looked closely in front of her.

[…Demons kill].

“I agree.”

The remnants of Vikir’s consciousness in the mire, frighteningly alive.

And another Vikir, facing his own reflection.

“Besides, it’s been a while, everyone.”

The sight of him giving a short reunion message to everyone clearly leaves no doubt about who he is.

That was the real Vikir!

Chapter 433

The Returned Hound (2)

◆

“It’s been a while, everyone..”

A low, low-pitched voice.

Dolores, Tudor, Sancho, Pigi, Bianca, and Sinclaire’s eyes widened as if they had witnessed something unbelievable.

Vikir. The Night Hound.

Their old friend, imprisoned in Nouvelle Vague more than four years ago, stood before them.

His height had increased, his chest and shoulders broadened, his jawline sharpened.

Not only had he grown into a handsome young man with a pretty boy face that made his gender seem ambiguous, but the density of his aura, which radiated from his entire body, had also changed to another level.

It was as if there was a mountain, or rather a mountain range, in front of them.

It was like he was a completely different person from the friend they had remembered, but that made it all the more real.

It was like realizing that Vikir in front of everyone was the real Vikir, four years older.

“…Ha, but how?”

Dolores and Sinclaire stare at Vikir, mouths agape.

Tudor, Sancho, Pigi, and Bianca are also stunned by the sudden reunion.

Tudor is the first to come to his senses.

“Vikir, is that you? Is that you! Are you my friend Vikir?”

“At least I think so.”

“You bastard! I was worried about you! But why are you out here? What the hell happened to you?”

“It’s a long story.”

“Then you can tell me the short story!”

“Hmm. Okay, then I’ll make it short.”

Slipping away from Tudor, who was lunging for an immediate hug, Vikir thought for a moment before summarizing.

“Trapped in Nouvelle Vague. I escaped. Came straight to assassinate Passamonte. I’ve been hovering around the castle for days, waiting for the right moment to sneak inside, but you guys went in first, so I followed.”

“…Something’s missing in front of that?”

Everyone, including Tudor, thought the same thing.

But there was no time to elaborate, as Vikir said.

[…Kill, demon].

The Death Knight, Vikir, made his move.

…Kwakwang!

The 4th Baskerville Form. Four teeth swooped down on Vikir.

Each strike was powerful enough to cut through the earth and tear the sky apart.

Moreover, his skill level has already surpassed the master level.

However, Vikir remained calm in the face of the massive maelstrom of strikes.

“Is it 4th Form? If that’s the case, I’m pretty confident.”

Vikir also deployed a Baskerville 4th Form.

The movements were as natural as breathing, as he had practiced swordsmanship his entire life.

The four teeth clawed ferociously at each other’s space.

Udeudeudeudeudeug!

A few hairs, a few drops of blood, scattered.

After an offensive and defensive battle without giving up an inch, Death Knight Vikir gritted his teeth.

…Kuoooooooooo!

The dark aura emanates even more strongly.

Death Knight Vikir has raised his swordsmanship to another level.

Baskerville 5th Form. The five teeth pressed down on Vikir.

Vikir, in turn, has raised his swordsmanship to another level.

Five against five. A storm of blows as if facing a mirror.

Pis- seogeog-

Flesh splattered and blood fountained.

A small amount of bleeding on both sides along the tiny cracks from the left-right asymmetry.

[Kills!]

Death Knight Vikir has raised his swordsmanship to another level.

Baskerville 6th Form. A ferocious onslaught of carnivores.

Vikir responds with a matching 6th.

Blade to blade, sword tip to sword tip, sparks flew, and the battle hung in the balance once more.

Baskerville’s 7th, followed by Baskerville’s 8th. The number of initiates who continue to do so.

Finally, Death Knight Vikir played his final card.

Baskerville 9th Form. The ultimate killing blow, destroys everything.

Kwa-gigigigigigig!

The dark red aura fluctuates steadily, carving away the rocks and hills around it.

Vikir, facing the net of slashes tearing apart the entire world, exclaimed in a low voice.

“ …9th Form. This is the realm after death’s threshold.”

The line between life and death is blurred, perhaps because it’s in a fantasy world.

What’s more, the fragments of his self in front of him were mixed with the experience of death he had before his regression.

Furthermore, as a being that rampages without an intelligence, it is only natural that he would be familiar with life and death.

All of this combined to create a 9th Form Baskerville by the most unlikely and coincidental of odds.

Vikir is an 8th Form Baskerville.

Even if he were to move up a level, he could no longer keep up.

That is the limit of the living, or in other words, of those who have much to lose.

“…But in the end, it is only a byproduct, a residue, left where the wheels of fate have rolled.”

With that brief assessment, Vikir drew his magic sword, Beelzebub, as long as he could.

…Flash!

Baskerville 8th Form. The eight teeth that Vikir had created swirled toward the nine teeth in front of him.

“Vikir, let me help you!”

Dolores stepped forward.

“It’s okay. I can handle myself.”

Vikir refused Dolores’s help.

It was necessary to save divine power in preparation for the battle with the Ten Corpses that would follow.

Vikir also wanted to see just how ripe his 8th Form had become.

This was fortunate, as he was about to face Baskerville 9th Form, which no one but Cane Corso had ever climbed.

…Kwakwakwakwang!

Vikir’s 8th Form and Deathknight Vikir’s 9th FForm clashed.

Their trajectories were different, but in the end, they were the same.

Teeth exist to bite and hurt others in the first place.

Ppagag-

The balance was upset.

The first to falter was, surprisingly, Death Knight Vikir’s 9th Form.

[…!]

The Death Knight Vikir, who had never been pushed before, staggered backwards for the first time.

His face contorted with embarrassment.

Seeing this, Vikir felt confident in his judgment.

‘Not even close to Cane Corso’s 9th form.’

Certainly, each of the nine swords that Death Knight Vikir unleashes is powerful and devastating.

But each one tended to play separately in different directions, roaming about with no clear intent or purpose.

Rather than nine hounds playing separately, eight hounds working together in unison can catch a much larger and stronger prey.

This was the current situation.

Ujijijijijig!

Vikir’s eight teeth spun in a round sphere.

A Black Sun.

It was the most efficient way to kill, learned indirectly from Cane Corso.

With a fierce spin, it converged into a single point, shattering the irregularly sprouting teeth and crushing them into a harsh, heavy mass.

It looked as if a hard bowling ball had been thrown with all its might into the mouth of a toothy beast.

Wagigig- ppujig- ppudeudeug- kwakwang!

All nine of Death Knight Vikir’s teeth are shattered.

Vikir’s eight teeth, on the other hand, rushed toward Death Knight Vikir, not a single one broken or missing.

[…! …! …! …! …!]

As Death Knight Vikir was sucked into the center of the Black Sun, his entire body shredded and shuddered in agony, he did not utter a single scream.

It merely glared at Vikir with burning pupils.

[…Demon].

Then, the Death Knight Vikir crawled through the gap between the blow and the blow.

[Kills!]

But.

“He who fights demons must take care not to become a demon himself.”

An even greater black sun awaited the Death Knight Vikir as he emerged through the cracks of the Black Sun.

“It is a shame that you have become a demon.”

Another black sun was placed upon the black sun.

Wajijijijijig!

Two huge black spheres interlock and rotate like clockwork.

Death Knight Vikir, crushed by the pile of slashes, finally let out a single scream.

[Gu-aaaahhh!]

His flesh writhes in agony. But worse than that, he had no outlet for the rage that burned like wildfire in his chest.

[…Demons! Die! Die! Demons! Die! Demons!]

Death Knight Vikir was struggling, scratching the ground with his bloody, rag-like body.

Determined to kill his opponent no matter what.

All those who have lived through the Age of Destruction harbor bitter anger and resentment in their hearts.

And those who were born as hounds and survived such times have a similar story to tell.

A collapsed ego, dogmatic hatred, and anger that exploded after being suppressed and repressed.

“….”

Vikir stared down at the figure, lost in thought.

Dolores studied Vikir’s sideways face and thought.

“I wonder what he’s thinking?”

Death Knight Vikir is Vikir’s alter ego, a fragment of his unconscious.

As a being who has become stronger by mulling over and over old grudges, he symbolizes and represents the hostility that Vikir originally has towards demons.

And what is Vikir thinking now as he looks at the being that is like himself?

‘…That must be sad. It must be painful.’

Dolores cried as she looked at Vikir.

How could anyone look at a self-portrait being torn to shreds and still be sane?

Is there anyone who wouldn’t be shaken even when faced with that terrible scream and that horrifying cruelty?

….

…There it was.

“It’s the best.”

Vikir smiled weakly as he watched Death Knight Vikir scrabble at the ground.

“It’s the best material. It’s worth it to come into the fragments of the Hell Tree.”

With everyone, Dolores included, looking on in confusion, Vikir untied the sack from around his waist and held it in his hand.

Hududug- hududug- hududug-

He shook out what was in it onto the ground and said.

“Eat up.”

It was something that looked like a bunch of kidney beans.

“…?”

Everyone’s eyes widened, including Dolores and Sinclaire.

The black blobs hit the floor and immediately crawled toward Death Knight Vikir in front of them.

They were clearly reacting to the strong smell of blood emanating from Death Knight Vikir’s body.

‘Black Tongue Leeches’.

Vikir’s secret weapon from Nouvelle Vague.

Chapter 436

Dreaming the Impossible Dream (2)

◆

Raw red hair that crackled like fire.

She stood tall and curved with maturity.

After four years, her face had lost a lot of fat.

“You’re here!”

Her eyes sparkled as soon as she saw Vikir and she started waving.

“Kyaah, boyfriend, it’s been a while!”

When Camus waved her hand, dark clouds gathered around her.

Pudeudeug- pudeug- pudeudeudeug-

Upon closer inspection, he realized they were black-feathered flying birds.

Countless crows and magpies had gathered and were building bridges.

Camus walked across the bridge, which must have been hundreds of meters long, to Vikir.

She walked with a haphazard gait, like a model on the runway.

“….”

Vikir was silent for a moment.

His emotionless expression faltered slightly.

Then, Camus threw herself into Vikir’s arms.

“You’ve grown so tall! Well grown, eum!”

After staring at Vikir for a long moment, Camus turns her head to look at the group behind her.

“…Uh, well, hello to you guys..”

It was a relatively more substantial greeting.

Dolores, Tudor, Sancho, Pigi, Bianca, and Sinclaire greeted Camus as well.

Camus, too, was a member of the Night Walkers, a fellow Colosseo Academy member, albeit only for a few months.

‘Why should I go to school here if Vikir isn’t here?’

The legend of Camus, who had dropped out as soon as she enrolled, had been a legend at Colosseo Academy for some time.

Dolores greeted her in a calm voice.

“It’s been a while, Queen of the Night.”

“Uh. It’s been a while for you, too. Doesn’t it get a little cringe calling me by that nickname?”

“The name comes from ‘Night Hound,’ which was Vikir’s working name.”

“Of course our Night Hound is awesome!”

Camus again grabbed Vikir’s arm who was next to her.

A thin line of blood appeared on Dolores and Sinclaire’s foreheads as they watched.

Sinclaire stepped between Vikir and Camus and asked.

“Speaking of which, how’d things go at Morgue’s place? I hear you’re bringing reinforcements….”

“Of course, I’m a delegate to the Dark Hall.”

Camus replied, her eyes shining.

Earlier, Camus had promised the Night Walkers his loyal support as head of Morgue’s Dark Hall.

…!

It was stated that the support would only be for one task, which was to track Vikir’s whereabouts, confirm his safety, and safely deliver him to a specific location.

The place where Camus herself was!

“I was informed that you had escaped, and of course I assumed that you had, of course, the method of prison escape was completely unexpected… but whatever. I’ve since unleashed the full force of Morgue’s army to search the coasts of any island of continent you might have washed up on!”

As she finished speaking, she turned and held up something toward the stiffly standing Tudor.

It was an iron skewer. A small, simple, and deadly tool that had stopped the charge of the Invincible Cavalry.

“You don’t have one of these in your house, do you?”

“…No, of course not. Why would I have such a thing?”

“You should be grateful. I could have used this thing without bending it, just to keep me upright.”

If Camus had done that, Donquixote’s Invincible Cavalry would have been a disaster.

They should be thankful that the horses and knights didn’t turn into sausages and rice cakes on skewers.

Tudor gazed at the chaos on the horizon with mixed feelings.

Normally, the Invincible Cavalry would have sidestepped such a trap with ease, but with Cimeries’s brainwashing, it was impossible to do so while riding blindly straight ahead.

Now, all eyes turned to the culprit.

Cimeries. The fourth mastermind of the Age of Destruction.

He grinds his sharp teeth into the gaping mouth in the center of his face.

[So there’s an ambush force after all. A black mage who absorbed Seere].

Cimeries seemed to sense Seere’s aura on Camus.

But demons are demons. Cimeries relaxed, as if he had already prepared for every possibility.

[I thought that you humans would surely strive to restore Donquixote’s nature. Do you think I did not anticipate this?]

At this, Cimeries lifted the face of Pasamonte, which was buried in the horse’s breastplate.

His gaze was fixed on Bianca, who stood beside Tudor.

[Usher Poe Bianca, I’ll tell you why I tried to capture you].

As soon as the words were finished, something strange happened on the outer castle and walls surrounding the spire.

Cheog-cheog-cheog-cheog-cheog-cheog!

A group of gray-cloaked snipers raised their bows and arrows in unison and pointed them in this direction.

Bianca’s face paled as she realized what was happening.

“…God Killer Sniper Squad (神殺狙擊組).”

A group of snipers composed entirely of Usher’s enemies.

A fearsome group that specializes in assassinations, especially those at extremely long range, they are monsters that make up over 90% of Usher’s power.

Their presence here represents a united front of the demons that consumed Donquixote and the demons that consumed Usher.

Why do they want to take Bianca and Tudors alive, when they could just take their heads if they wanted to get rid of them statically? Wouldn’t that be much easier?

It was now clear why Pedro wanted to capture Bianca as well as Tudor.

Bianca looked back at Vikir with an urgent expression.

“It’s bad! Usher’s sniper squad is here! Dad said if they all got together, they could kill a god!”

“….”

Vikir nodded in agreement.

The Usher Family was the smallest of the seven Great Families of the Empire, but it was precisely because of the presence of the God Killer Snipers that they had never been overpowered by the others.

Cimeries grinned from ear to ear.

[Once the Usher Family’s God Killer Sniper Squad lays an ambush, even if the best of the other six families gathered together, they would not be able to avoid annihilation! Who doesn’t know that?]

There were many obstacles blocking their view, so it was impossible to see the entirety of the God Killer Sniper Group’s ambush.

However, the sharp sensation of killing intent everywhere told everyone that this place was already completely surrounded.

Obstacles meant nothing.

There was no hiding from the sniping of the God Killer Snipers, who could pierce through centimeters of armor with ease.

Cimeries shouted loud enough to be heard by all of the Killing Squad’s assassins in ambush.

[Shoot! Kill them all!]

Wrapping his armor around himself, Cimeries didn’t hesitate to give the order to concentrate fire.

And then.

…Peong!

The first sniper shot flew in.

It shot through several layers of walls, piercing through the floor and into the floor below.

It was followed by a shower of thick arrows.

Dudududududu-

Just as the hooves of the Invincible Cavalry’s horses pounded the ground, so did the arrows of the God Killer Sniper Squad.

Jjiiing…

Vikir channels all of his mana into Decarabia.

The Red inverted pentagram’s shields blocked arrow after arrow from the God Killer Snipe.

All of the Night Walkers, including Camus, rallied around Vikir, shielding themselves with Decarabia’s shield.

Kwakwang! Kwang! Peoeong-

Each arrow from the God Killer Snipers struck the outer surface of Decarabia, causing it to vibrate with a loud explosion.

Watching the rain of sniper fire, the Night Walkers all thought the same thing.

‘…What the hell? Is it more bearable than I thought?.’

The God Killer Snipers were fast, powerful, and accurate, but their numbers were too small.

The rate of fire was slow, and the spacing between arrows was far too wide… No, it didn’t seem like one man was using that many arrows in the first place.

This was evident by the fact that once an arrow flew, it never flew back in the same direction.

With only a handful of people, the God Killer Sniper group that had made the Usher family the strongest in the Empire was so weak?

Just when everyone was questioning in their minds.

[…What is this?]

Cimeries was thinking the same thing.

He stuck his head out and scanned the outer walls.

Sure enough, there were noticeably fewer men with bows and sniping.

Even if they were a small minority, their numbers were too small to utilize the power of ambushes and focused barrages.

[This isn’t a small group, it’s just a small number! What the hell, where are they all?]

Dolores, Tudor, Sancho, Pigi, Bianca, and Sinclaire, seeing Cimeries’ confusion, were just as puzzled.

Then.

Camus’s voice was heard as she wrapped her arms around Vikir’s waist.

“But boyfriend- I’ve missed you so much, so please stop running away, I’m tired of chasing you, although it doesn’t matter because I always have a good idea where you’ll end up….”

At that, everyone looked back at Vikir with puzzled expressions.

Tudor was the first to speak.

“Vikir. Wasn’t it Camus you were talking about as a backup plan? From what I’ve heard you talking, it sounds like you’re meeting for the first time.”

“Nope. She’s just here.”

Vikir denied it in a low voice.

Camus laughed in disbelief.

“I’ve been scouring the coast and deserted islands, and I don’t have anything in mind.”

Whatever. Vikir hadn’t been talking about a secret plan.

‘Then what?’

The same question pops into everyone’s head.

…Kwakwakwakwang!

A loud explosion erupted from the ramparts outside.

A wave of aura that fluctuates like crazy.

The corner of the castle wall collapsing and the God Killer Sniper Squad falling down.

It was a scene that made Cimeries’ jaw drop.

“Pushishishi- it’s dusty. Get over there and play, old man.”

“Shut up or I’ll have to arrest you once more, you old, raggedy escapee.”

A skinny old man with a whip in his hand, smirking.

Next to him is a big old man with a heavy club.

Two old men were walking up the ramparts, making small talk.

But what they were about to accomplish was anything but small talk.

Jjaag- kwakwang!

With a single stroke of the whip, the assassins of the God Killer Sniper Squad were sent scrambling out of the way, and with a single strike of the club, the sturdy walls crumbled to the ground.

“So many Imperial guards and spearmen have been killed~ This is why the revolution at that time should have been successful”

“What kind of revolution is that? It’s a riot. Cut the crap and do what you were asked to do.”

“Anyone would think you ordered me to do this, Drew.”

“I’m not like you. I’ll pay for my food.”

Two old men walked up, blowing away the elite of the Usher family.

Marquis de Sade, the mastermind of the 47 Men’s Riot.

And Orca, the head warden of Nouvelle Vague.

They stood side by side, looking up at Vikir.

Chapter 437

Dreaming the Impossible Dream (3)

◆

Marquis de Sade and Major General Orca.

Two figures who were said to have the combat power of a single fortress joined hands.

“Pushishishi- The Ushers who chased me in the past were a little spicier, but this one is bland, so I like it.”

“Cut the chit-chat, prison escapee. There’s still plenty left.”

Marquis de Sade and Major General Orca were strolling through the Ushers’ God Killer Sniper Squad like it was a walk in the park.

But the changes that were taking place around them were staggering.

Chararararak-

Sade’s whip moves like a giant snake, slicing through the assassins on the ramparts.

The bizarrely twisting and contorting whip slashes and slashes at everything it touches, sending a gale of blood around it.

Kwang! Kwa-ang! Kung-

Orca’s club brushed aside the flying arrows with such ease that when they weren’t flying, it swung like a drumstick toward the ground.

Each time it struck the ramparts, it sent out a tremendous seismic wave, sending enemies tumbling down the walls.

Sade on offense and Orca on defense.

Their combination was a strange supercomposition of D’Ordume and Souaré’s back in Nouvelle Vague.

Moreover, Sade is not only good at attacking, and Orca is not only good at defense.

Sade’s whip moved like a monster’s tongue, twisting and clamping down on flying arrows, while Orca’s clubs turned any assassin who got too close into a bloody mess with a single blow.

It was a perfect display, a circle of dozens of meters in radius centered on the two old men, and no one was allowed to enter it.

Bianca’s jaw dropped at the sight of it all.

“Who are those people, my family’s God Killer Sniper Squad….”

No wonder she was surprised.

The God Killer Snipers, belonging to one of the Seven Great Families, are the core power of Usher.

But when Cimeries recognized the faces of Marquis de Sade and Major General Orca, his expression crumpled into a grimace.

[Aren’t they the remnants of the 47-man riots? Why are they gathered here?]

Sade and Orca’s gazes turned in unison, as if in agreement.

“Remnants’? Is that what you just said to me?”

“Maybe it’s because you’re a demon, but you don’t understand the world. Come here.”

At the same time, Sade’s whip and Orca’s club flew into the air.

Buuuung-

A serpentine aura and a tidal wave of auras swept over Cimeries at once.

It was a shockwave powerful enough to bring down an entire spire.

[…Keugh!?]

Cimeries leapt into the air to escape the storm of auras that crumbled beneath his feet.

“Who says remnant?”

He gasped at the eerie voice from above.

Sade was hovering over Cimeries’s head, laughing a menacing laugh.

Peo-eog!

A bundle of whips, rolled short in several layers, crashed down like a thunderbolt over Cimeries’s head.

Unable to scream, Cimeries tumbled toward the ground.

And below, an Orca holding a club was waiting.

Jjeoeog!

The club hits Cimeries, sending him flying through the city walls.

Charalarak-!

Sade’s whip struck again as Cimeries flew.

This time, the long lash tightens around Cimeries’s waist, and Sade spins it around like a clockwork.

Kwa-kwakwakwakwakwakwakwakwang!

Cimeries spun in a circle, still bound to the whip, and began to smash every bump in the ramparts, tearing up the ground around him.

[Kuaaaaaaaaaaghhh-]

When Cimeries, who had barely escaped the whip, staggered out of the collapse.

Kwagig-

Eight teeth sank into the nape of Cimeries’ neck again.

It was Vikir, casting a shadow like that of the Grim Reaper upon Cimeries’s back.

“Demons kill.”

[How dare you, human…!]

Cimeries had just opened his mouth.

Peog-peog-peog-peog-peog!

Countless iron skewers protruded from the ground and pierced Cimeries’s body.

Behind Vikir, Camus was smirking.

“A perfect reunion gift for my boyfriend.”

Over the shoulder of the cheerful Camus, Seere looked very small and sulky.

[Se, Seere… you dare betray us?]

[Huh-huh- I’m not doing this because I like it either.]

[Shut up! If he finds out about this, you bitch…!]

But Cimeries didn’t get to finish his sentence.

…Quack!

Sancho’s axe, Pigi’s sword, and Bianca’s arrows came crashing down on him.

Kkwadeudeudeudeug-

A golden grip emerged from the ground, pinning Cimeries to the ground, unable to budge.

Sinclaire’s magic followed.

[Kuaggghh!]

Cimeries turned to black smoke and tried to escape, but it was impossible.

Paas-

Dolores’ white shroud had imprisoned Cimeries.

“Lengthen your neck.”

Vikir’s 8 teeth sliced ferociously across Cimeries’ body.

Cimeries stretched out his spear to strike back, but it was blocked by Decarabia.

“Pushishishi….”

“This side is clear.”

Where Vikir looked up, he saw Sade and Orca standing.

In the center of a pile of broken spears and arrows, the two old men stared down at Donquixote and Usher as they held their attackers by the throat and head.

Vikir knew it was time to end it all.

[Kuhughhh- Kuhugghhh- Blood, if it weren’t for that ‘blood’, damn it! I was wondering why Amdusias got killed!]

Cimeries cried out in frustration.

But Vikir left him no chance.

Having cut off Cimeries’ ankles and wrists, Vikir prepared for the final blow.

He was going to destroy his heart cleanly.

Then.

“Vikir. Wait.”

A voice interrupted Vikir.

Tudor. Tudor Donquixote.

He approached, his eyes fixed on Vikir.

His one arm gripped Gungnir, the spear of the Spear King, firmly.

“Let me do this.”

Tudor’s gaze was hard and determined.

But Vikir refused.

“No.”

“…Why?”

Tudor’s voice was filled with frustration.

But Vikir was adamant.

“If you bathe in the demon’s last drops of blood, fate will change. Causality will be twisted.”

No matter how lucky you are, it can’t end well as long as you’re with the demon’s end.

A twisted and warped causality leads the Demon Hunter’s path to a bad place.

So the end of a Demon Hunter’s fate is usually dark and lonely.

However.

“It’s okay, this is what I choose to do.”

Tudor chose to become a Demon Hunter himself.

It’s no wonder he’s so adamant about it.

Also, Tudor’s past destinies have left him covered in demon blood, so perhaps this is what he was meant to do.

“….”

After a short silence, Vikir quietly took a step back.

It was a gesture of trust.

“Thank you.”

Tudor bowed his head toward Vikir.

Then he turned to Pigi next to him and asked.

“Pigi, do you think I could get some of your blood? For some reason, your blood seems to be poisonous to demons.”

“Sure!”

Pigi nodded at Tudor’s request and slashed his arm with the sword.

The dark red blood that flowed from his body stained the blade of Tudor’s spear, Gungnir.

“….”

Tudor lowered his gaze to look at Cimeries crawling on the floor.

Beneath Cimeries’s gaping mouth, at the base of his face, across his chest, was still the face of Pasamonte.

A heart peeked out from beneath the flesh around the gaping wound, The heart is visible through the surrounding wounds and black flesh that were split and torn by Vikir.

Passamonte’s face was distorted, wrapped around the heart of Cimeries.

Then, from between Tudor lips, a dry voice spoke.

“To dream the impossible dream (So?ar lo imposible so?ar).”

Gungnir, the double-bladed spear, raised its head.

“To overcome the unbeatable rival (Vencer al invicto rival).”

Tears of blood trickle from his blood-red eyes.

“To endure the unbearable pain (Sufrir el dolor insufrible).”

His heart, pounding as if it were about to burst, squeezed out the strength that had been his at the beginning of his life.

“To die for a noble ideal (Morir por un noble ideal).”

All this to fulfill a true knight’s duty and obligation.

…No.

“It is not a duty, but a privilege (Su deber no Su privilegio).”

With Tudor’s last words, the King’s Spear Gungnir pierced the air.

Peo-eog!

The sound of torn leather and the destruction of the vile mass of flesh that lurked within.

The veins of malice coursing through the creature’s veins were severed, spewing out all the foul things it contained.

Cimeries struggled hard, scratching at the ground, but Tudor’s spear, pierced through his heart and embedded in the ground, did not budge.

[The Great… Gate went… The Era of the Demons…]

Cimeries muttered something in a fading voice, and then fell back in a heap.

He never moved again.

The fourth protagonist, who was leading the world to destruction, left the stage.

And the focus shifts to the newcomer to the stage.

Black blood. Demonic blood.

Covered in it, Tudor boldly embraces it, never taking a step back.

Tudor’s eyes shine through the demon’s black blood, clear and pure and righteous.

Vikir had seen it before.

In the world before the Regression, in the Age of Destruction, when mortal fate, when all things burned and died.

The eyes of a hero who lived and died at the forefront of his time, fiercest and hottest.

Tudor Donquixote, King of the Spears.

The will of a great hero who would lead the coming era.

Chapter 439

The Fall of Usher (1)

◆

The Night Walkers traveled through the night to Usher’s territory.

A land filled with desolate wastelands, swamps, and tall rocks.

On an island in the center of a deep swamp, you see Usher’s great mansion standing tall.

‘Masyaf’, a mansion that resembles a citadel.

The Gothic castle looks eerie, shrouded in a mist of water rising from the swamp.

The walls and windows, carved out of the stone, looked like they had cracks in them, with countless dried ivy vines clinging to them.

The windows, which have turned cloudy and gray like the eyes of a blue-blind eye, seem to be staring blankly into space.

The sticky, dismal humidity rising from the swamp was everywhere.

Moreover, the black-red aura that spreads like a demonic spirit through the mist of the water is something that makes every Night Walker frown.

“…Red Death. It’s even worse than before.”

Dolores said, swallowing hard.

A horrible plague, or rather, an extreme poison that even caused the death of Cervantes, the Spear King.

This is what has cast the shadow of death over the Usher mansion.

“I wonder if my father is safe….”

“….”

Bianca bit her lip until it bled, fighting back tears.

Tudor is silent while putting his hand on Bianca’s shoulder.

Cervantes, Lord of the Donquixote family, and Roderick, Lord of the Usher family, were longtime friends and enemies.

Now that Cervantes has met a tragic end in the Red Death, it’s a luxury to hope for Roderick’s safety.

But even knowing this reality was one thing, speaking it out loud was another.

Even Camus, who was known for her bluntness and sarcasm, and who was not particularly close to Bianca, had not said a word out of respect for her mood.

However. Marquis de Sade, the only one who was completely oblivious to the stares of others, was still speaking in his usual manner.

“What kind of foul air is that, I’m sure everything in the mansion has long since been destroyed.”

“Please shut that mouth of yours, you old prison escapee, before I crush you with my club.”

Orca cautioned, but Sade kept talking.

“Look, Vikir, I doubt there’s much point in repairing the Usher at this point. With that much poison in it, there’s probably already a bunch of skeletons inside.”

“You don’t know that.”

Vikir’s answer was surprisingly hopeful.

Normally a cynic and a pessimist who defaults to negative predictions, Vikir was unusually positive this time.

Bianca asked impatiently.

“So, you’re saying there’s hope, huh?”

“Yes.”

Vikir nodded.

He turned to his left and opened his mouth.

“The Usher family was originally an official family of an enemy nation before the unification of the Empire. They were once a very famous family of assassins. After the unification of the Empire, they were only able to become one of the Seven Great Families with a small number of people. It’s because of the skill of their members.”

Is there any other family for which the term “small elite” fits so well?

Sinclaire, who is also an intelligent person, recites some legendary Usher family anecdotes.

“It’s said that when the Emperor went to visit the Usher family in the past, the Usher family wanted all of their entourage behind them so that the Emperor and the patriarch of the family could talk to each other one-on-one, and the Emperor said he could put everyone back, but not the two generals he really trusted.”

The rest of the story was common knowledge.

The Usher family patriarch asked the emperor, ‘Are you sure you don’t want to send them away?’ The emperor replied, ‘These two men are like my brothers. They are like my alter egos, and they cannot be separated.’

At this, the patriarch of the Usher family laughed without saying a word, but then he opened his mouth and asked the two generals standing behind the Emperor, ‘Can you kill the emperor right now?’

The two generals standing firmly behind the Emperor immediately drew their swords and pointed them at the emperor’s throat.

As if they had been waiting for this command all this time.

“…This incident enhanced the reputation of the Usher family, and the Emperor himself treated them generously, as they were strong and had secret power.”

Bianca nodded at Sinclaire’s words.

She had always been proud of her family, and the mention of past glories seemed to ease her sting a bit.

But the reality is harsh.

The once great Usher family has been eroded by demons and is on the brink of extinction.

Vikir analyzed the situation soberly.

“The people of Usher are strong individually. They may be few in number, but their individual skills are, on average, superior, which means that there should be more of them who can resist the demon’s power. Moreover, Usher’s castle, Masyaf, has many environmental conditions that can be fortified in the future, and its strategic value is comparable to Tochka. It is a place that must be restored before a great war.”

“I know the geography of the grounds and the structure of the mansion inside out. I’ll show you around.”

Bianca said with determination.

It was fortunate that both Tudor and Bianca were so knowledgeable about the inner workings of the family, and much more than the average young master.

Many young master didn’t know much about their own families.

But Vikir shook his head.

“The Usher mansion is full of mazes and traps, and the poison is so thick now that it’s impossible for many to enter. Once a small group enters, we must lure the demons out and meet them outside the mansion.”

That leaves the question of who will go inside the poisonous mansion.

Normally, Vikir would lead the way.

“I can’t go in.”

Not this time.

Vikir shook his head.

“Because I need to make other arrangements, in case I succeed in attracting the demon.”

The number of people who can enter the Usher mansion is limited, then.

Dolores spoke with difficulty.

“If it’s holy water that can break through that poisonous fog, I think we can make enough for two people.”

Even with all of her divine power, that was the limit.

Two people to infiltrate the Usher mansion and lure the demon out.

It was obvious who one of them would be. It was Bianca.

She knows the geography of the mansion inside out, and she’s the target of Usher Poe Madeline, the one who’s currently in control of the family.

“Aunt Madeline was said to have been exceptionally weak as a child, even to the point of being thought dead when she collapsed after a seizure and was buried alive. Now that I think about it, she probably died then, and the demon took over her body while she was buried.”

Bianca muttered, then looked up with a look of determination.

“Perhaps the demon is after my body, young and fresh, and if I were to enter the mansion on my own and escape, it would surely turn and chase after me.”

Hearing Bianca’s words, nearly all of the Night Walkers raised their hands.

“I’ll go with you.”

“I want to help.”

“Come with me, Bianca.”

Sancho, Pigi, and Sinclaire opened their mouths.

But then all eyes turned to one place.

Tudor stepped forward.

“Allow me to come with you.”

“….”

“You owe me from the day before.”

Tudor chuckled as he lifted the spear with his one arm.

Bianca also laughed with reddened eyes.

“Still reckless.”

“One must be reckless in the presence of a lady. That is chivalry.”

Tudor and Bianca turn to face each other, smiling bitterly.

In that strange atmosphere, everyone had no choice but to give them the benefit of the doubt.

But Vikir, always calm and cool, broke the mood before anyone could say anything.

“Are you sure you can do this? It’s not just about love. The odds of dying are much higher than the odds of living.”

“What, what’s love!”

“Wha- If someone hears it, they’ll misunderstand it! This is loyalty! It’s friendship!”

Looking at Bianca and Tudor’s stunned denial, Vikir shook his head.

Then he spoke again.

“Very well. You seem motivated, so I’ll give you the benefit of the doubt. But I’ll tell you what you must do.”

Vikir’s instructions were both simple and difficult.

1. Go inside the castle and lure the demon out.

2. Make sure the patriarch, Roderick Usher, is alive or dead.

Just two tasks.

But whether they succeeded or failed, the odds were stacked against them.

“The Red Death has evolved even more, and it seems to be very specialized. Even with my divine power, I won’t be able to hold out for very long, an hour at most….”

Dolores said in an unconfident voice.

But Bianca shook her head as she held Dolores’ hand tightly.

“That’s more than enough, thank you very much.”

“Bianca….”

Bianca forced a smile at Dolores’ tearful face.

Then. Vikir called to her.

“Take this with you.”

“…?”

Bianca shook her head.

Vikir placed a heart-shaped hairpin on Bianca’s palm.

Before Bianca could ask what it was, Vikir turned his head and looked at Tudor beside him.

“Take this, too.”

Vikir handed Tudor two firecrackers.

One red, the other black.

Vikir spoke in a serious voice.

“Determine if Roderick, the patriarch of the Usher family, is alive and able to get out with you, then set off the red firecrackers, and if he’s dead or unable to move even if he is alive, then set off the black firecrackers.”

This had a lot to do with the vague strategy that Vikir was preparing outside.

On behalf of everyone, Bianca cautiously asked.

“Why are the colors of firecrackers differentiated? What does it mean…?”

Vikir’s answer was short.

“It’s better if you don’t listen.”

It was an answer that sent chills down everyone’s spine and renewed their determination.

Chapter 443

The Fall of Usher (5)

◆

Usher Poe Madeline.

She gathered the remnants of the Killing God Squad and set out in pursuit of Tudor and Bianca.

Leading her horse across a bridge over a swamp, she soon found herself at the foot of a steeply sloping mountain.

[Abandon your horses and climb the mountain; you may kill Tudor, but Bianca must be captured].

Madeline had lost her reason in her rage and no longer thought to hide her voice.

From her mouth, which has been torn open from ear to ear, comes a sound like the howl of a trapped animal.

Her eyes, arrowed in the brow and turned in strange directions, were set vertically in a reptilian pupil.

The leader of the Demon Army, who had once led the Age of Destruction from the forefront and had done so much to spearhead the destruction of mankind, was slowly revealing her true colors.

Pudeudeug-

Every time Madeline moved the hem of her loose dress, it made a sound like a bird’s feathers rubbing together.

[The smell of young, fresh meat…]

Madeline was climbing the mountain faster than anyone else.

The smell dotted over rocks, piles of leaves, and the tips of sharp branches.

Madeline was following the trail of blood that Bianca had spilled as she fled.

[Hohohoho- she must have been in a hurry, if she couldn’t even get the scent off herself].

The prey’s increasingly sluggish pace was evident in the growing trail.

Sweat, saliva, and snot on the ground.

But the most unmistakable odor of all is blood.

Not only was the blood spilled not covered with leaves or soil, but there were unmistakable traces of footprints and hair everywhere.

Broken branches and disheveled grasses also gave a clear indication of the direction in which the prey had fled.

[Finally goodbye to this rotting bitch, hohoho – as soon as I change bodies, the first thing I’m going to do is whip her little squeaky body to smithereens, it’s been so frustrating and tiresome].

Madeline reached the ridge with a big smile on her face.

She could see the lake on the other side of the mountain.

Lakedog Lake.

It’s the largest lake in the area, along with the swampy land surrounding Usher’s mansion.

Madeline and Usher’s pursuers made their way out of the forest and toward Lakedog Lake.

What they saw was a rather unexpected sight.

[…?]

It was a pile of stones and mud piled high on the shore of a lake that had been turned into a barren field.

Where there should have been a lake, there was no water.

The water had been wiped out by the ongoing wildfires and drought.

[But was the drought really this bad?]

The bottom of the lake was strangely dry.

She could understand if the water level was dropping, but it’s not normal for the lake to be so dry.

There were some pools of stagnant water in various places, and there were large fish clustered in them.

…Puddle, puddle, puddle!

Madeline stuck her hand down into the pool and pulled out a large catfish, which she chewed up and swallowed whole.

[Strange. Even in the most severe droughts, the waters of Lakedog never dried up… hohohoho- could it be that the coming Age of Destruction is that harsh?]

Madeline tossed the catfish she was chewing on to the ground and turned her head to look at the blazing red flames on the horizon.

The wildfire burning in the distance was obviously no ordinary natural disaster.

Droughts, wildfires, monster outbreaks, and all other natural disasters are merely precursors.

It was a flow of magic power condensed to open a huge portal in the sky and a natural phenomenon that followed.

[…Gate. The gates of destruction are about to open!]

The demons, impatient with the continued loss of their allies, have decided to open the gates to the Demon Realm a little earlier than they would have otherwise, after decades of delay.

It was for this reason that the Empire’s civil war broke out earlier than planned.

[For that, I must change my body into something young and fresh].

Madeline felt her body heat up as she thought of the many plans she had for Bianca’s body.

[Alas, first I must make many children, how delicious they will be made from my blood and flesh, my mouth is watering already].

She quickly descended to the bottom of the lake and made her way toward the center.

She made her way through the towering stones and mounds of dirt, and the desolate landscape inside came into view.

Whiiiiing-

Suddenly, a humid breeze blew in from nowhere.

[…!]

Madeline’s expression changed as she turned her head to look for something.

She has an ominous feeling in the back of her mind.

Looking back at the rubble she had just passed, she realized that the path had changed slightly.

Madeline’s eyes narrowed.

[Oh my. You’re going to use a ‘formation’ against me?

Yes.

These stones piled up on the bottom of the lake are the walls of a maze.

And the paths between them form strange shapes throughout.

As visitors walk along these paths, they are plagued by hallucinations and visions, and eventually become completely disoriented and trapped within them.

It was similar to the formation inside the Usher mansion where Bianca’s brainwashing was triggered, but in a much more complex way.

[Hohohoho- I’m an Usher myself, so I’m in the formation. It’s cute.]

Madeline was quite relaxed despite being caught in a trap.

As she looked around, she saw monstrous rocks rising up like swords and a wall of dirt and rocks that completely surrounded her.

Madeline’s eyes glittered with an evil light.

[Hehe… That’s good. This is the work of Belial and Dantalian, right? Did they betray us and join the human side?]

But that’s not possible.

Weren’t Belial and Dantalian long gone in the first place?

But the formation in front of her was clearly a trap that Belial and Dantalian used to wage war on a large scale.

How a mere mortal has managed to recreate it is beyond comprehension.

[Who is it? Is it Bianca? No, there’s no way a human could imitate a demonic formation so well. Hmmm…]

Madeline was a little troubled, but then she laughed softly.

[Well, whatever. This body isn’t affected by the formation method, and I’ve already told Belial and Dantalian about the structure of this formation in the first place. Then why don’t we try to break it in an instant?]

The other side must have set this trap to buy time.

However, Madeline thought to herself, having absorbed all of Usher’s knowledge of the formation, as well as having mastered the formation of the demons, there was no way she could fall for such a lowly trap.

[I’ll make it all for naught].

Madeline shook her head in triumph.

[Rest(休), Life(生), Injury(傷), Stop(杜), Enlightenment(景), Death(死), Surprise(驚), Open(開). Of the Eightfold Diagram Formation, If you go into life(生), Enlightenment(景), and Open(開), you will live. If you go through injury(傷), Surprise(驚), and rest(休), you will get hurt, and if you go to Stop (杜) and Death (死), you will die, right?]

Madeline knew well which was the live path and which was the dead path.

It was a well-known truth among demons.

[Hohoho- A truth is like a scribble on the pavement, of great effect to the unknowing, but nothing to those who know it well. Your efforts are imaginary, but useless!]

Madeline strode forward, breaking through the path of the Formation Method.

…But at that moment.

[Huh?]

Madeline spotted the remains of head lying on the ground.

It was a catfish from the puddle that Madeline had caught near the beginning of the dungeon.

Somehow, she had found herself back in the area where the maze had started.

With the exit still out of sight, of course.

[Well, how could it be?]

Madeline moved immediately.

She tried the Life Gate(生門), the Enlightenment Gate(景門), and the Open Gate(開門), which she knew to be the live path, but the scene was still the same.

She even went out through the Injury Gate(傷門), the Surprise Gate(驚門), and the Rest Gate(休門), just in case she got hurt, but the result was the same.

Instead, confusion, as if the heavens and earth were turning upside down, filled her head.

Still, she didn’t have the courage to enter the Stop Gate(杜門) and the Death Gate(死門), where the path to death was certain.

[What? This isn’t even Eightfold Diagram Formation? If it is, this is the right way to leave? Huh?]

The black blood on the floor was distracting Madeline.

All around her, she could see nothing but more dense walls, with no way out.

[…At this rate, I have no choice but to advance toward the center of the lake? Hmmm. Someone knows the demon’s tricks. Who could this be, the demon hunter who’s been killing my friends, but I thought he was imprisoned in Nouvelle Vague?]

But the more she ponders, the more she ponders, the more she moves forward, the darker her vision grows.

Madeline was dragged into the deepest part of the formation, half willingly and half unwillingly.

There stood a tall tree with a small torch hanging from it, and at its base she could see words written in black blood.

Madeline fought back her rising anger and impatience and walked toward the tree.

Suddenly, the words on the ground in the center of the formation caught her eye.

-Demons die under this tree.

The moment she saw it, Madeline gritted her teeth.

[How dare these bastards use cheap provocation…!]

But. It wasn’t just a provocation to spoil the mood.

Madeline was quick to realize that.

…Cheolsseog!

The sound of something heavy crashing in and hitting a huge boulder.

Deudeudeudeudeudeu-

The dry, cracked ground trembled violently, sending up shards of stone and dried muddy dust.

[…!?]

Madeline’s face crumpled into a grimace.

Now she understood why the bottom of Lakedog was so dry.

Chaaaaaah!

Water Attack.

An enormous wave of water was rushing in from the distance.

Chapter 444

The Fall of Ushers (6)

◆

-Demons die under this tree-.

Vikir stood on the far bank.

[How dare these bastards use cheap provocation…!]

The moment he heard the demon’s cry from the center of the lake, Vikir immediately gave the order.

“Open the floodgates.”

The members of the Night Walkers and Donquixote’s knights each raised their spears, cut the ropes, and pierced the earthen wall.

Tudor and Bianca turned to face each other and let out a powerful burst of mana.

…Peoeong!

The mud and wood pillars collapsed, and the waters of Lakedog burst out from the imprisonment beyond.

Even though the drought and wildfires have lowered the water level significantly, Lakedog Lake naturally holds a tremendous amount of water.

Kwakwakwakwakwakwa-

The water rushing out of the breach created countless currents and rushed toward the bottom of the lake.

In the distance, we can see the demon flailing about.

Madeline has broken through the Life Gate(生門), the Enlightenment Gate(景門), and the Open Gate(開門), as per the Eightfold Formation, but that doesn’t mean she’ll get to the way out.

She also tried the Injury Gate(傷門), the Surprise Gate(驚門), and the Rest Gate(休門), with the same result.

However, this does not prevent her from entering Stop Gate(杜門) and the Death Gate(死門), which are obvious death routes, so there must be some information about the Eightfold Diagram Formation.

“…Certainly. It’s the path that Belial and Dantalian used to wreak havoc on the Human Alliance during the Age of Destruction, so she should be familiar with it.”

Vikir is giving back to the demons exactly what the Human Alliance suffered at the hands of the demons in the past.

….

Vikir’s version of the Eightfold Diagram Formation was a slightly improved version of what Belial and Dantalian had used.

This was possible because….

“Pushishishi- look at that. It’s better if you do as I say.”

It was thanks to Marquis de Sade, smiling beside Vikir.

He shouldn’t be here if he was meant to be.

He was supposed to have failed to break out of Nouvelle Vague and become fodder for deep-sea monsters 10,000 meters below.

But Vikir changed his fate and rescued him from the depths.

The result. Marquis de Sade was able to put his skills as a tactician and military strategist to good use, something the Human Alliance had been lacking during the Age of Destruction.

‘An interesting plan, but I can see a few holes in it, and I think I can make it even more vicious if I combine it with the Eight Trigrams(Bagua) I used during the 47 Man Riot. Puspushishishi-‘

Marquis de Sade, who has a devious, even diabolical, talent for bullying others into trouble.

‘Add the elements of Jin (震), Son (巽), Lee (離), Gon (坤), Tae (兌), Geon (乾), Gam (坎), Gan (艮). Add the elements of thunder, wind, fire, earth, pond, sky, water, and mountains, and no demon can escape as long as it has two feet on the ground. I can’t wait to see how the one who falls into it will struggle in agony-‘

He was interrupted by a voice that was far more cunning and evil than anything the demons had ever put their heads together.

“Pushishishi! Even the demons can’t get out of it, scurrying away like bugs!”

“It’s still a bad taste.”

Marquis de Sade was delighted, and beside him, Major General Orca, who was giving him a scold, looked as if they were relieved as they collapsed the dam they had built so far.

Building the dam wasn’t difficult for Vikir, who had once built a massive dam to keep out the Red Death when he was in Ballak’s village.

Once released, the water rushed over the ridge with unstoppable momentum.

The drought-strained ground gave way, releasing massive amounts of sediment, and the resulting earthquake shook the entire ridge.

Soon afterward, massive amounts of water from Lakedog began to sweep down the hillside and pour into the swampy area where the Usher’ mansion was located.

“Aah! The mansion!”

Bianca exclaimed in surprise.

The current was already swirling around the swampy area surrounding Usher Castle.

A vortex that circled and carved away at the ground beneath the castle, eroding it.

The island in the center of the swamp where the Usher family’s mansion had stood was sinking lower and lower.

“Dad!”

Bianca screamed as she leapt forward, but Tudor stopped her.

“Bianca, wake up, you saw the condition of the mansion!”

“…Aaaah!”

Bianca’s legs gave out and she fell to the ground.

If Tudor hadn’t held her tightly, she would have tumbled down the cliff and been caught in the rushing water.

Dolores, Sinclaire, Sancho, and Pigi could see now why Vikir had made the fireworks so color-coded.

“Determine whether Roderick, the patriarch of Usher Family, is alive or dead, and if he is alive and able to escape with you, set off red firecrackers, and if he is dead or unable to move even if he is alive, set off black firecrackers.”

‘Why are the firecrackers color-coded? What do they mean…?’

‘You’re better off not listening.’

He was right.

If the red firecrackers had gone off, Vikir might have considered a different plan, but once the black firecrackers went off, the choice was clear.

The moment Vikir saw the black firecrackers, he made his decision.

To wipe out the Usher family mansion, completely eroded by the Red Death.

“…Dad.”

Bianca looked down at the rushing torrent below the cliff.

The Fall of the House of Usher.

Bianca’s tears filled her eyes as the mansion collapsed into the center of the swamp.

The stately home she had lived in all her life, the proud family name, was disappearing in real time, buried in the shifting sands of history.

Just then.

[Kuaaaaaaaggghhhh!]

A tearing scream rose from the maelstrom of crumbling earth and swirling mud.

Vikir and everyone else looked up to see several shadowy shapes breaking through the torrent and emerging into the water.

Hands disappeared, and in their place were giant wings.

Razor-sharp teeth bared from snouts that jutted out like beaks.

Claws that looked like a mix of blades and hooks, and grotesquely bulging chest muscles.

Giant face birds break through the water current and crawl out onto the ground.

Bianca immediately recognized one of them, the largest and broadest of the monstrosities, with the longest body and wings.

“Isolde!”

How could she forget, the one who betrayed her family and joined the demons.

The one who not only unleashed the poison into the swamp and left Roderick for dead, but also relentlessly chased Bianca and scratched her body and mind.

As a demon, Isolde raised his blood-red eyes to look at Bianca.

[You planned this well. I almost drowned during the chase.]

“Die!”

Bianca immediately drew her arrow.

A thunderbolt of a shot!

Peoeong!

But Isolde, who had turned into a demon, stretched out his huge wings and knocked the arrow away.

[Kkkkk… You’re going to take on a demon with the mere strength of a human? You still have no sense of reality at all.]

The wound healed quickly.

Isolde smirked, showing off his newfound bulk and muscle.

Just then.

“…It’s been a long time.”

Vikir took a step forward.

Vikir had met Isolde once before, when he was a convoy escort on the way to Nouvelle Vague.

[…!]

Bianca’s anger hadn’t fazed him, but Vikir’s call had made him flinch.

He had been punished for mutiny on board a ship before.

But then a genuine smile appeared on his face.

[I was alone then, but not now, and with my minions with me, I have no reason to fear you!]

True to Isolde’s words, the demons that had crawled out of the vortex were gathering behind him, one after another.

“Pushishishi- what is it? Why are there so many birds? He doesn’t seem that serious, but it strangely bothers me.”

“Don’t let your guard down, prison escapee. They self-destruct when cornered.”

The minions were fierce enough to make Marquis de Sade and Major General Orca wary.

Camus, who was demolishing the steel frame inside the dam, clicked her tongue as if it was a waste.

“Alas, the drought has lowered the water level. If it wasn’t for that, I could have wiped them clean.”

The prolonged drought and wildfires had reduced the water in Lakedog.

Despite the powerful mudflows, currents, and landslides, many of the minions managed to survive, and the Usher family’s mansion foundation was halfway eroded away.

Isolde chuckled.

[This is Madeline. Not like a fool like Passamonte. While Passamonte was preoccupied with some random Hell Tree he picked up, Madeline trained an army of demons as usual. Look! The result!]

Among the knights of the House of Usher, those who had become the demon’s servants not through brainwashing but through their own will shook off the water from their feathers and roared fiercely.

[Since we are alive, Madeline must be as well, and now you are doomed!]

Even now, the number of demons crawling up from the water continued to grow.

Isolde’s confidence was well founded.

However.

“Well. In terms of the number of sides, I’m guessing we’re on top?”

Isolde’s eyes widened at Vikir’s casual remark.

[W-what nonsense are you talking about…?]

As far as he can see, there are no other troops around.

There are only the Night Walkers and a few knights from Donquixote’s house.

[Cut the bluff! Attack!]

Ishred shouted, and the minions behind him spread their wings in unison.

Bats, eagles, owls, hawks, and other birds of prey… soared into the air in unison.

…But.

They soon realized what Vikir meant.

Shurororororock-

It leapt to the surface and grabbed the minions by the ankles.

No, it had been hanging on to their ankles since they first came out of the water.

Vines. Long and tough.

As they flew through the air, they felt a powerful force pulling at their ankles.

[What, what is this?]

Isolde looked at the vines wrapped around his ankles.

A vine with a terrifying power. The source of that power was desire, or rather, appetite.

[…?]

Desperate for something, he followed the tip of the vine and soon saw water at the end of his gaze.

The vine went all the way down to the water.

Then, a giant face emerged from beneath the surface, connected to the vine.

Chwaaaaag-

A giant circular face emerges from the churning water.

Jjeo-eog!

The face is bare, with no eyes, nose, or ears, except for its gaping maw and the teeth that fill it.

The Daylily of Blood Tree.

Countless demonic beast seeds were germinating beneath the water.

Chapter 445

The Fall of Usher (7)

◆

A giant face emerged from beneath the surface.

Sharp teeth peeking out of a gaping mouth, the corners of its mouth torn upward as if it was enjoying something.

It had no eyes or nose, so its expression was unreadable, but still recognizable.

The horrible feeling of hunger and thirst, the appetite, the gluttony, and the joy and elation that it was all about to be relieved.

The Daylilies of the Blood Tree waited beneath the water with their mouths open, waiting for the demons.

[Uuuuh?]

[Hey, what is this!?]

[Kuaaghh! What kind of power does it have!?]

[…Help me!]

The demon transformed into their bird of prey forms and took flight, only to be dragged back to the water’s surface by the tough vines that were about to wrap around their ankles, or had already wrapped around them.

Wahzak-.

The mouth of a Daylily closed.

One of the demons had gotten stuck in it and bled to death.

[…]

The demon shuddered as he looked down at his mashed up lower half, like meat for a haggis.

Crushed flesh, shattered bones, and dark blood dripped down in a puddle.

As its prey watched in horror and despair, Daylily shook itself with delight, stretching out its vines again and again.

Shurorororock-

Once again, the demons that had ascended to the sky are pulled down.

[When did these vines get around my ankles!?]

[Water! It got wrapped around me when I fell in the water!]

[I can’t get it off! Damn, it’s so tough!]

[Ouch! I’m being dragged again! Aaaaaaah… kahg!?]

The countless daylilies soon formed a colony and swallowed up the demons.

Cheombeong- cheombeong- cheombeong- cheombeong-

The river quickly turned black with the blood of the demons.

Seeing this disaster situation, Isolde could only gape.

His ankles, wings, and torso were covered with daylily vines as he struggled to hold on.

[No way! Where did these things…!?]

Isolde stared at Vikir with shaky pupils.

But Vikir didn’t bother to answer.

Before Madeline and her legion of demons had pursued Bianca, he had planted the seeds of the blood daylily on the shores of Lakedog, which had been drained for the construction of the dam.

‘No matter how bad the drought, the bottom of Lakedog Lake never cracks.’

Lakedog Lake hasn’t run dry in thousands of years.

When someone sees a lake like that, not only bare, but cracked and dry, they should be suspicious.

It’s because the daylily seeds have sprouted and sucked all the moisture from the bottom of the lake.

And now, with the water in full force, the daylilies are in full bloom.

They ate the demons in droves.

“You lacked attention.”

Isolde’s eyes widened at Vikir’s words.

[You bastard, don’t pretend to be so relaxed! You think you can escape these demonic beasts just because you’re a human!]

The Daylily of the Blood Tree were obviously very fond of humans.

The size of its maw and the way its teeth were packed into it made it look like a 100% carnivore.

However.

-Twees!

A surprise happened.

One of Donquixote’s soldiers, who had stumbled and fallen into the river, had been captured by the Daylily.

As Daylily wrapped the soldier in its vines and was about to take him into its mouth, it paused for a moment and stuck out its tongue to lick him once.

Then, as if touching something inedible, it threw the soldier back into the water.

[…? …? …? …?]

Isoled, who saw the soldier who had survived his life hurriedly crawling up to land, only blinked in bewilderment.

He can barely speak as he struggles against the tug of the vines.

“Well improved.”

Vikir nodded as the Daylily spat out the human.

Then, behind him, a figure stood, puffing out his chest with a smug expression.

MiniPin. MiniPin Baskerville.

His voice was full of pride as he spoke, familiar with the ecology of the monsters.

“Ah, I’ve been working hard to modify their diet. I’ve completely ripped out their taste buds to make them taste disgusting to humans, and sweet and savory to demons. In doing so, they’ve lost a lot of their size, but this is something that can be made up considerably as generations go by. Oh, and again…..”

MiniPin went on at length about his painstaking efforts, but Vikir filtered out the essentials.

Using the daylilies from Vikir, MiniPin conducted many experiments in the safety of Tochka’s underground facility.

Even Banshee Morgue, an authority on the subject, sent his own team of researchers to assist in the experiments.

As a result, MiniPin was able to identify and select individuals among the daylilies that were unusually unthirsty for human blood, and he continued to breed them, refining the breed to become less aggressive toward humans with each passing generation.

In addition, by mixing human blood with a foul-tasting substance when feeding them, and by feeding them demon blood along with small amounts of other foods that the daylilies might like, the daylilies began to be tamed in an acquired way.

In this way, the daylilies, both genetically and acquired, were transformed from seed.

Twe-es!

The daylilies shied away from humans as if they lost their appetite.

But when they see the blood of the demons, they rush at them with madness in their eyes.

[… Ughhhhhh!]

Isolde flapped his wings furiously, four vines wrapped around his body.

He broke free of the vines with the immense strength of a demon.

Shurorororock!

Despite two more vines wrapping around him and strangling him, Isolde didn’t give up.

[I, I am the last vassal to serve Madeline, the one who will rule over the lesser mankind in submission! I will not die in this place, I will never die, this is my world now, this is my opportunity, I have waited so long for this day, for this time, for this age!]

But.

“A opportunity?”

There was a cold voice standing in front of Isolde.

Bianca. The last heir to the House of Usher.

She stood before Isolde, bow and arrow raised.

“Opportunity does not come by waiting.”

[…?]

Isolde’s wavering pupils turn toward Bianca below.

Bianca raised her arrow and pointed it at him.

“Shoot, like this.”

At the same time, Bianca squeezed out all of her remaining mana.

Peong-

The arrow flew through the air, tearing a hole in the atmosphere.

It soared in a fluid parabolic motion, piercing precisely between Isolde’s two eyebrows.

Peo-eog!

The skull shatters, and all that’s inside falls out in a heap.

[Euegh! Keughhh!]

But even so, Isolde held on.

Even when his head is shattered and everything inside is spilled out, he survives with the supernatural vitality of a demon.

…However.

Bianca’s anger at the betrayal of her family was not of a short-lived nature.

…Peong-

After the first hit, the second hit came.

…Peoeog!

And the third hit.

…Peoeog! …peoeog! …peoeog! …peoeog! …peoeog! …peoeog!

Arrow after arrow, all aimed at the same place.

Eventually.

[Aaaaahhhhh! No!]

Even Isolde, who had six vines wrapped around him, falls to the ground.

Underneath him, countless daylilies are gathered and smiling.

Wajig- wajig- wajijijig!

There was only one body, but so many mouths chewing, tearing, and savoring it.

The end of Isolde became the starting point.

The demons began to be cleaned out in earnest.

The daylilies danced and swayed as they wrapped their vines around the pieces of the demons’ bodies.

The water turned black and even more murky.

Vikir looked at the colony of daylilies and asked.

“How should I collect them? Should I handle it myself?”

“There is nothing to collect. The reformed daylilies are short-lived, withering away within a month without a supply of demon blood.”

“Are they likely to spread their seeds and disrupt the surrounding ecosystem?”

“No. They are all seedless individuals. To use a man’s analogy, they are Nutless.”

“….”

For some reason, Vikir thought, that wasn’t a very good analogy.

Well, whatever. The demons hiding in Usher began to be cleaned out.

Those of the brainwashed knights of Usher who were unable to escape and were swept away by the current were able to cling to the roots and vines of the daylilies that filled the stream below.

However.

[This doesn’t feel very good].

Decarabia at Vikir’s chest began to roll its eyes.

“What is it?”

[It seems like almost all the demons have been wiped out… The most core source of demonic energy has not been purified at all.]

Almost simultaneously, Camus, who was standing beside Vikir with a bored expression on her face, also glanced over at Seere, who was patting her shoulder.

“What the hell, asshole, do you want to die?”

Camus’s words instantly make Seere cringe, but she musters up the courage to say what she needs to say, no matter how much she’s being bullied.

Vikir and Camus’s gazes snap back to the river.

The water current was raging there.

Some of the larger daylilies, as if they’d found something that smelled unusually tasty, stretched out their vines and gills and moved toward the center of the whirlpool.

Just then.

Kwakwakwakwakwang!

The daylilies that had been clustered together were torn apart.

Falling flowers in full bloom.

Even the largest ones were torn to shreds, and something shot up into the sky like a beam of light.

[Hohohoho- it’s the rottenness of her body that makes it take so long for me to return to my true form].

Usher Poe Madeline.

The man responsible for the downfall of the Usher family.

A usurper who covets Bianca’s body.

And in the past, one of the key protagonists who led the Age of Destruction.

<‘Third Corpse’ Andrealphus>

Danger Rating : S+

Size: ?

Found in: ‘Serpent’s Womb’, deep within the Gates of Destruction

-Also known as ‘Third Corpse’.

One of the Ten Plagues, natural enemies of mankind, incomprehensible and unkillable.

“Hail will be poured down.”

– The Ten Commandments 10: Top –

Andrealphus, the ‘Ice Duke’.

The third of the Ten Corpses finally reveals itself.

Chapter 450

Declaration of War (3)

◆

“They will come to Tochka. Because my son is there.”

Hugo replied to the skepticism everyone was expressing toward Tochka.

His assurance, so full of conviction that it seemed almost self-righteous, drew chatter from those around him.

“Tochka is a well-defended fortress, but it has no strategic value because there is no place to get drinking water, right?”

“There was a lanky warlord who encamped there during the Warring States Period and was defeated because there was no water.”

“That’s why it’s called ‘Crying Castle.’.”

“The Leviathan Family are so sneaky and cunning, they would never target such a place.”

The evaluations of those around him were generally negative.

…But Baskerville patriarch Hugo isn’t one to let the stares and comments get to him.

“So what are you saying?”

That’s his way. No one can open their mouths to Hugo’s rebuttal.

The iron-blooded swordsman’s name, Baskerville, was heavy and sharp.

Hugo spoke, his tone unwavering.

“My son is there. He’s there, and he’s not fooling around. Our enemies must have realized that by now.”

And surprisingly, Hugo’s hardline demeanor was met with a few sneaky nods of agreement.

“Hmmm. Come to think of it, one of my daughters is there. She’s a little girl, she’s so obsessed with men….”

Matriarch Raspane of Morgue said in a low voice.

“Our saintess is there, too.”

“Hmmm… I hate to say it, but our own Gaju seems to have been there recently as well.”

Martin Luther of the Quovadis and Damian of the Bourgeois nodded in agreement.

Camus Morgue, Dolores L. Quovadis, and Sinclaire J Bourgeois are also known to be in Tochka at the moment.

They hadn’t exactly reported their whereabouts, but it was information the trio had gleaned in secret.

‘The Night Walkers’.

The heads of the Houses knew that Dolores and Camus, along with many others, had gathered there and were hosting refugees.

Some held their tongues.

“So the Night Hound was a scion of House Baskerville, was he?”

“I thought he was imprisoned in Nouvelle Vague, but how did he get to Tochka?”

“No, I’m pretty sure he was reported dead in Nouvelle Vague….”

To those questions, Hugo surprisingly readily opened his mouth and answered them.

“I heard he escaped not long ago.”

At that, everyone’s mouths dropped open.

What is Nouvelle Vague like? Isn’t it the worst prison in the world, where once you’re locked up, not even your soul can escape? And he’s escaped from such a ridiculous place?

Hugo, feeling everyone’s eyes on him, shrugged.

“That guy is a genius.”

This isn’t the kind of bragging that goes along with, ‘Look what school my son got into this time~’ or ‘I heard he got first in his class there~’.

It’s only natural that Hugo would be met with a look of disbelief when he calls someone who escaped from Nouvelle Vague, the worst prison in the world, a genius.

“Whatever. My son’s judgment always had a reason. I will go to Tochka to honor it.”

Hugo’s argument was clear and forceful.

Adolf, a Mage who knew a bit about Vikir, nodded in agreement.

“Certainly, the fellow is trustworthy, and while he must have had something in mind when he made that place his hideout… I think support is necessary as people may suffer without drinking water for a while. So you mean the Baskervilles are sending an army to Fort Tochka?”

“No. I’m going alone.”

“…?”

Adolf shook his head, and Hugo answered as if it were obvious.

“This is not as a Baskervilles patriarch, but as a father. There’s a difference between state and private.”

“…I didn’t know you loved your children so much, did you?”

“Do you want to be my son? Why should you know how much I love my children?”

“….”

Hugo replied grimly, touching his chin as if his shaved beard was missing.

It’s the patriarch’s move in the first place, so it’s only natural that the entire House would be behind it, but since the whole point is that the father is going to see his son in private, there’s no room for other powers to interfere.

Well, whatever.

The first time they saw Hugo making such a strong assertion, they all had a lot to say.

Under the circumstances.

“I’ll go with you, Father. I also have a lover there.”

“I’ll join you too!”

“I’ll join you!”

“I’ll join!”

Osiris Le Baskerville, the young patriarch of the Baskerville, said the same thing behind Hugo’s back.

So did the three brothers next to him, Highbro, Middlebro, and Lowbro.

The idea of moving to Fort Tochka seemed to be viewed positively by the Morgue.

“She’s my daughter, but I’m worried about her because she’s a bit too naive.”

“Why don’t you come with us and see for yourself?”

“Please take us with you too.”

“After the war is over, they’re going to harass you and tell you that you’re hiding somewhere and not even bothering to prick your nose.”

“Ugh… I’m so scared just thinking about being ripped to shreds. I’d rather die fighting in front of him.”

Raspane and Adolf. And the three sisters, Highsis, Middlesis, and Lowsis, agree.

“Our saintess is there, too. We’ve always wanted to visit her, so we might as well.”

“I’ll go too. We must protect our lord.”

Martin Luther of the Quovadis and Damian of the Bourgeois nodded in agreement.

With so many people talking seriously about reinforcements to Fort Tochka, or even moving their camps, public opinion began to tilt toward skepticism.

Just then.

“You can’t go that way! There’s an important meeting right now…!”

A panicked shout from a guard comes from outside the conference room door.

An urgent tone, like he’s trying to stop someone.

BANG!

Soon, the door suddenly burst open.

Jeobeog- jeobeog- jeobeog- jeobeog-

Five figures stormed into the conference room.

“…!?”

The atmosphere in the room changed drastically.

Everyone’s posture and facial expressions show their shock at seeing these unexpected faces.

Some characters have sullen expressions, as if they don’t even know who they are.

A few, however, seemed to already know about the unauthorized intruders in the room.

“…What brings the all-stars of Nouvelle Vague here?”

Figures so formidable that even Banshee Morgue, the Principal of Colosseo Academy, had to adjust his posture.

Colonel D’Ordume. Colonel Souaré. Brigadier General BDISSEM. Brigadier General Flubber.

…And Black Tongue.

They are the five great wardens of Nouvelle Vague.

Even behind them were a large number of Nouvelle Vague guards, known for their ferocity and skill.

D’Ordume was the first to step forward.

“The Nouvelle Vague is gone. A volcanic eruption wiped it out without a trace, and the guards who were lucky enough to survive were all unemployed. Just like us.”

Souaré was the next to speak.

Her gaze had been fixed on Hugo since earlier.

“It’s thanks to your son’s splendid behavior.”

“…My son?”

Hugo rolled his eyes slightly, and Souaré quickly averted her gaze, trying to distract him.

BDISSEM. followed Souaré’s lead and said stiffly.

“For now, we… Because I am a civil servant belonging to the imperial family… I need to find a place to stay… I guess I was following the current captain’s orders… I came here…”

After finishing her sentence, BDISSEM glanced at the man he called ‘the current captain’.

Flubber, who was cowering on the floor, was also looking at him.

“….”

“….”

Surprisingly, D’Ordume and Souaré don’t say anything.

Their faces showed that they agreed with BDISSEM.

This should have surprised everyone in the room.

A leader recognized even by D’Ordume and Souaré, who were fiercely fighting over the position of head of Nouvelle Vague.

Had there ever been anyone like this before, except for the Major General Orca Montreuil-sur-Mer Javert?

All eyes in the room turned toward the figure at the back of the room.

Then the last of the wardens stepped forward.

Black Tongue.

The current leader of Nouvelle Vague’s five wardens.

He opened his mouth with bright red eyes.

“We’re going to Tochka, and everyone here should go there, too. As many people as possible, all together!”

Many expressed their displeasure at Black Tongue’s harsh, almost imperative tone.

“What does that mean, coming out of nowhere?”

“Do you even know what you’re talking about?”

“How dare you order me around, guards. Do you know how many high-ranking nobles are here?”

“More than that. Colonel Black Tongue, did you… originally look like that?”

“I think my appearance has changed a lot.”

However, Nouvelle Vague’s five wardens were completely unmoved despite such criticism.

Black Tongue continued to speak in a chilling voice.

“…So much for nice words.”

To several rather shocked-looking figures, Black Tongue drew his own sword.

Jjeog-

‘Asmodeus’, a magic sword that splits the table in the center of the conference hall in half.

It is truly bizarre to see the small pieces joined together to resemble a whip.

Everyone’s faces stiffened.

The atmosphere in the room is frozen, and the tension between the people is palpable.

Only then did Black Tongue drive in another wedge.

“If you don’t want to get fucked, you should all go to Tochka.”

Chapter 451

Declaration of War (4)

◆

…Udeudeug!

The battlefield was filled with smoke.

The Night Hound stares coldly at his freshly killed prey.

Except for the broken neck, it looks like a normal human.

However, judging from the bright red color of its eyes and the red spots on its skin, it was definitely not in a normal state.

Poisonous Man (毒人).

An unintelligent and extremely fierce creature that lunges at humans with a luminescent glow.

Their bites and prolonged exposure to the red energy emanating from their skin can also turn normal humans into Poisonous Man.

Overall, it was similar to a zombie, a low-level undead, but its physical abilities and the amount of poison it emitted were incomparably dangerous.

“Hmph. It must be even more dangerous than him.”

Vikir thought of Sakkuth de Leviathan, a fellow prisoner of the Nouvelle Vague.

Formerly known as the Leviathan’s scoundrel, he was permanently expelled from the family, taking sole responsibility for the ‘First Red Death Incident’.

But.

‘How did you know? There is actually no plague poison in my blood.’

The Sakkuth he met in Nouvelle Vague was strong and fierce, but unsteadily sane, and did not carry the plague.

No one had been infected with the plague until he was eaten by Brigadier Flubber.

But the venomous creatures you just encountered were not only strong and vicious, they seemed to be faithfully carrying out the orders of some entity.

They’re also spreading the Red Death, which has been modified to be more contagious, making them even more dangerous.

“How they managed to create all these Poisonous Man is a mystery. Surely there must be a limit to the amount of poison they can produce….”

These poisonous beings had been around before Vikir’s regression.

But even then, the mystery of how Leviathan had managed to produce so many of them had never been solved.

“I can’t help but say that I’m glad that Dolores is her….”

Even if you are bitten by a poisonous person or exposed to poison for a long time, there is no problem as long as you receive the priest’s protection at the right time.

It was also fortunate that the Red Death could not penetrate the space where the Saintess resided, radiating holy power.

Vikir thought to himself.

It was a good thing he’d recruited Dolores in the first place, and that he’d been there to help her develop her skills.

…Peog! …peog! …peog! …peog! …peoeog!

Vikir turned his head only after he had finished making sure the ground was covered with the corpses of the Poisonous Man.

Huge craters had formed in the ground where the poisonous creatures had been lying.

The ground had been torn fiercely.

They were the marks of eight teeth.

Vikir thought for a moment.

‘My proficiency with the Eight has certainly increased since Nouvelle Vague.’

Little did Vikir know that after Hell Tree, there was still room for improvement in the Eight Form, which he thought he had already mastered.

With a newfound sense of humility, Vikir reevaluated his swordsmanship.

There is a wall up there, a wall of the 9th Form that cannot be crossed in one’s lifetime, as Cane Corso said.

[You will probably not reach it in your lifetime, for the realm of the 9th Form lies beyond the threshold of death].

[To reach the 10th Form, you must die and awaken. I don’t understand what that means, so I’m still stuck at the 9th Form. How am I supposed to awaken when I’m already dead, and I may never reach the 10th Form?]

Like a legendary island that appears only on stormy nights, or like a rainbow after rain.

The 9th Form that is visible to the eye but can never be reached, but it is definitely there.

Is it really possible to cross that threshold only after death?

Even at the highest level, there are different levels.

Also, in the deep world, there clearly exists something called ‘ultimate intention.’

Vikir has been struggling to grasp a clue to this ever since he was imprisoned in Nouvelle Vague.

Right then.

[Kyaaahhh-]

A scream shatters Vikir’s reverie.

A girl crawled out of the pile of bodies.

Her face couldn’t have been more than ten years old.

When he turned his head, he saw a red-spotted, poisonous creature with a mist of pestilence spewing from its entire body.

“….”

Vikir’s mouth falls open for a moment as he sees the girl charging at him, tooth and nail.

The face bears a striking resemblance to the one he remembers.

‘Nymphet.’ Remembering a small encounter he’d had while volunteering at the orphanage long ago, Vikir reached out and brought his hand to the girl’s throat.

…Ttug!

The limbs, which had been struggling roughly like a demon, began to droop helplessly.

The girl, who had been writhing in agony even after death, was finally at peace.

Vikir has been traveling from battlefield to battle, eliminating countless Poisonous Man.

The girl before him was the last of his kills.

Vikir nodded, looking at the wheel tracks, half-wrecked carriages, and broken drinking water bottles near the Poisonous People.

“…Same. Were they targeting the supply route to Tochka?”

Poisonous people lined the roads where the wagons carrying drinking water traveled.

Perhaps the Leviathan Family had begun pressuring Tochka from this side in earnest.

There is already something suspicious about Poisonous Man disappearing from various parts of the civil war zone these days.

“Perhaps there will be an all-out war soon.”

The scale and intensity of the battle in Tochka may be small in comparison to the larger wars raging across the Empire’s vast territory.

However, that was just the general public’s view, and the demons probably quickly realized that Tochka was a gathering place for dangerous elements.

A seedy backwater where no one cares and no one supports.

But who could have guessed that this is where the final battle for humanity’s existence would begin?

Vikir closed his eyes and remembered the days before his regression.

Leviathan had once laid siege to Tochka with an army of countless poisoners.

Claiming that it was the duty and right of the Great House to take control of the land on behalf of the family that had lost the ability to manage it.

Ever since then, a feudal war has raged.

It was a war of such magnitude that it was thought of as a war of nations against nations.

At the beginning of the war, the Allies clearly had the upper hand.

At the forefront of the battlefield, the Swordsmen of Baskerville and the Mages of Morgue crushed the Poisonous Man with terrifying force.

The Seven Counts of Baskerville, who were said to spend their lives solely in battle, and the Seven Knights, as well as the old and seasoned beasts of the Senate, who were thought to be old men in the backroom, came forward, the Poisonous Man went out like candles before the wind.

The synergy between Morgue’s core power, the Light Hall, and the Dark Hall, the secret power that is not revealed, joined hands, the synergy effect was also enormous.

Even Leviathan, who had absorbed Donquixote and Usher, seemed to falter under their onslaught.

The tide was tipping in their favor.

‘…And then it happened.’

The Rainy Season of Fire.

Showers of fire, a deluge of flames that never stopped for 150 days.

A long rainy season that wiped out 98% of humanity. A season of disaster.

The final weapon of the demons that inflicted the greatest and most horrific damage on the Human Alliance.

Cold sweat broke out on Vikir’s forehead as he recalled the scene of that day when countless dead bodies formed a dark red horizon and the entire sky was ablaze.

…Kkwaleuleung!

The distant sky was darkening.

The clouds had an unnerving reddish tint, and even the thunder crackled with something sinister.

The place where the original home of Leviathan, a Poisonous Dark Master, is located.

Beneath those ominous clouds, Poisonous Man must be gathering. The Poisonous armies are returning from the various battles of the Civil War.

“….”

Vikir looked around the Leviathan family’s main home, but was unable to find a way to infiltrate the tight perimeter, so he had no choice but to turn back.

He tried to figure out what had produced so many Poisonous Man, but was unsuccessful.

“Still, it is a great harvest to find out that Poisonous Man are gathering in one place.”

Now it was time to return to their home base and prepare for the next big attack.

“With Dolores, we can put off worrying about the Red Death itself for a bit, but… mere combat power is a problem.”

The defense of Tochka Fortress, where a single soldier can easily hold off a hundred, is a matter of faith.

Outside the strong fortress of Tochka, the evil spirits of the Red Death will be performing a mad masquerade.

In a land where infectious diseases are rampant, the inside and outside of the fortress have now become a completely different world.

Now everyone, centered around Saintess Dolores, is locked inside the castle and must never go out.

Vikir also planned to close the gates and stage a sit-in once he returned to Tochka after completing this secret mission.

“….”

Vikir stared down at the girl’s cold, motionless body for a long moment before taking a step forward.

How many more of these innocent lives will die, he wondered.

When the time of destruction comes, it will be faster to count the living than the dying.

So many more innocent, unknowing, sinless, pure people will die.

No, Rather, the absolute majority of small citizens who are moderately calculating, moderately mean, moderately good, and moderately conscientious will all perish.

Hwaleuleug-

Vikir threw a match over the bodies of the Poisonous, including the girl who had just died.

Soon, an acrid smell spreads.

A small flame that bloomed on a land marred by drought and famine soon spread into a rage that seemed to burn the whole world down.

Seeing the burning corpses of so many Poisonous Man, Vikir turned his back completely.

The Night Hound turned back.

Back to his fortress, a natural fortress that specializes in defense and protection.

To Tochka, where his allies await.

And to the final battlefield.

Chapter 454

Infiltration of the Water Source (3)

◆

Major General Orca, a master of defensive warfare, has come to the forefront, and the siege has slowed the Leviathan’s momentum.

And there was a master of offense who didn’t miss a beat.

“Pushishishi….”

Sade. The former Marquis de Sade, Cédric de Sade, Ang-gajumang.

His eyes twinkled with amusement.

“I suppose it’s my turn from here.”

Marquis de Sade looked back at Major General Orca.

“You had trouble with my attack about forty years ago right? I think I’ll use that tactic.”

“Hung. Wasn’t it ultimately blocked by my defense at that time? So you were captured.”

“That’s because we were vastly outnumbered, you old man.”

After a lifetime of fierce battles, the two enemies joined hands.

Marquis de Sade was a man with a genius for tormenting and making others suffer.

Master of mercenary warfare who, forty years earlier, had challenged the entire empire with a coalition of only forty-seven families and had come close to decapitating the Emperor.

Marquis de Sade is also a descendant of the prestigious House of Sade, a family that has been prominent for generations.

He was also a man who received overwhelming support from survivors and successors from defeated countries that fell or were forcibly merged.

“Marquis de Sade, I will follow you!”

“Just give me the command!”

“We will be with you even in death!”

“Ooh! The glory of the past is being recreated!”

The soldiers from the former defeated nations, who didn’t mix like water and oil despite being part of the same alliance, threw their full support behind Marquis de Sade in his name.

Vikir nodded at the sight.

‘It’s worth saving ….’

Before he regressed, he had heard Major General Orca, a fierce defender in the last days of the war, mutter.

‘Sade, if only he were alive, the Human Alliance wouldn’t have been pushed so far.’

A demonic brain that rivaled Dantalian in military strategy and Belial in mercenary skill.

If Marquis de Sade had been alive to fight the War of Destruction, he would have been the perfect complement to Orca’s weaknesses in specializing in defense.

If even his lifelong nemesis, Major General Orca, lamented this, he would have been a great addition.

Vikir decided to take him out alive when he escaped from Nouvelle Vague.

“Pushishishi- I thought the Warring States Period was over and we’d never see such a fun war again, but here we are again, and it’s so wonderful, I’ll live long to see it!”

‘The Strong Survive,’ which was the spirit of the times throughout the Warring States Period, and the Marquis de Sade, who can be said to be the embodiment of the spirit of the strong survive, was smiling maniacally at the demon and his minions.

“Come, brave young men, follow me!”

Sade raised his whip, and a maniacal cheer erupted from behind him.

The post-war generation, the resentment and sense of defeat of being from a defeated nation, prisoners and prisoners of war from all corners of the country, united under the banner of Marquis de Sade.

Kwakwang!

The gates of Tochka opened and Marquis de Sade led his soldiers out to sweep away the poisoners.

Peo-peopeopeopeopeopeopeopeong!

The whip, which started moving like a giant snake, cut all the poisonous people in half within a few dozen meters in front of it.

“Pushishishi! Kill them all!”

Sade divided the men who followed him into eight groups.

The Eightfold Formation, which wiped out the demons of the Usher family at once, has been transformed again.

The Life Gate(生門), the Enlightenment Gate(景門), and the Open Gate(開門) that kept them alive.

The Injury Gate(傷門), the Surprise Gate(驚門), and the Rest Gate(休門) that cause serious injury.

The Stop Gate(杜門) and the Death Gate(死門), where you will surely die.

…But in Marquis de Sade’s maniacally laughing reimagining, there was no sign of a live path.

Every gate is a death gate. A jar of malice with no way out.

Marquis de Sade’s whip had driven the poisonous people thoroughly into the pit of death.

The spearmen moving according to the formation, the shieldmen behind them, and the archers at the rear changed their formation according to the whip and pushed the poisonous people.

Tudor, Pigi, Sancho, and Bianca watched from the ramparts, their jaws dropped.

“Wow, you can use soldiers like that.”

“It seems very different from typical tactics.”

“It is. I can’t believe you can push your soldiers to such desperate lengths.”

“…Why is he more poisonous than the poisonous people?”

Basically, a typical local war begins with a fight for cause.

After a bitter argument, the warriors declare war, agree on a time and place for the battle, and fight only while the sun is shining, returning to their camps at night.

The warriors would fight one-on-one, or they would divide their armies into two wings, with offensive forces on the right and defensive forces on the left, with the victory decided by whoever could destroy the other’s left wing first.

The ethics and unwritten rules of warfare were to take as few casualties as possible and not go to the other extreme, as captives would later be enslaved or ransomed.

…Of course, all of this was completely foreign to Marquis de Sade here.

“Kill them all! And you too die! Pushishishi! If you fight too shyly, I will cut off your head myself!”

Sade’s maniacal mercenary style was pushing his soldiers to the edge of lethality.

Chalalag- peopeopeopeopeopeopeog!

Watching him on the front lines, wielding a single whip and slaughtering poisonous army left, right, and center into hundreds of pieces of flesh, one could not help but think that even the demon himself would not fight so brutally.

Watching Marquis de Sade in action, all of the Night Walkers learned that the old ethics of warfare must be abandoned when dealing with Leviathan, or even demons.

The enemy is not human.

This realization was fresh in the minds of the younger warriors.

Marquis de Sade had thoroughly re-established the mindset, a seemingly simple but crucial element of warfare.

“ …You’re still a crazy old man, no, you’ve become even crazier in solitary confinement.”

Looking at Marquis de Sade, Orca clicked his tongue and said.

“I wish the old man had been killed by the poisonous people at this point, but he’s more human than demon, so it’s right to help him. Rear guard, support!”

Orca, too, took up his club and raced out the gate.

Soon, troops and vigilantes from each of the Houses began to gather outside the gates to drive the poisonous people back.

Pupupupupupupug!

Countless skewers rose up from Marquis de Sade’s side.

A red-haired woman smiles over the skewered poisonous people.

“Old man. I like your fighting style, would you care to teach me?”

Camus Morgue. She was showing great interest in Marquis de Sade’s tactics.

…Kwakwang!

An entire vein of gold was pulled out of the ground.

A giant golden hand struck the poisonous people on the other side.

“Let’s use our momentum to strike deeper!”

Sinclaire. She, too, was on the other side of Camus, helping Marquis de Sade.

And even now, flaming arrows were flying everywhere, burning away the plague fog, and countless arrows and longspears were destroying the Poisonous People.

“Pushishishi- That’s it, they’re retreating. If we chase them any further, we’ll be overrun by reinforcements, so retreat!”

Marquis de Sade called his soldiers back with eerie timing.

Camus retrieved the skewers with a sad look.

Sinclaire also pulled her magic back with sword-like timing and retreated.

More poisonous people arrived as reinforcements, but by then all the Allied soldiers were back inside the gates of Fortress Tochka.

◆

The outpost at Leviathan was a victory for the Allied forces at Tochka, thanks to the division of forces between Major General Orca and Marquis de Sade.

Major General Orca’s meticulous preparation and experience in countless maritime battles, coupled with Marquis de Sade’s ghastly counterattacks and retreats, resulted in a victory for the Tochka Alliance.

…But the real war had not yet begun.

The siege against the poisonous people has completely exhausted all of the priests who exuded holy power.

It was doubtful that they would be able to hold off the Red Death tomorrow.

The soldiers had also been moving around vigorously, consuming more water than usual.

Tomorrow, they would indeed run out of drinking water and holy power.

There was no way to stop the second and third wave of the poisonous people attack.

Dolores said after taking a walk around the castle.

“I think they’re going to try to dry us out. They’ve got layers and layers of siege nets outside the walls, and they’re going to pick a day when the sun is shining.”

At this rate, they might not last three days, let alone a week.

Eventually, Vikir had to make a decision.

“We’ll go to the water source and draw water.”

Leaving Tochka’s security to Major General Orca and Marquis de Sade, Vikir himself would go to the water source and build a waterway.

MiniPin marked a few X’s on his map and handed it over to Vikir.

“This is the terrain of the water source I predicted. If you blow up the area I marked, the water will probably fill up to the moat at Tochka.”

But Chihuahua seemed uneasy that Vikir was going to such a dangerous place.

“There are poisonous people of the Leviathan family out there, and it would be impossible to break through their siege lines. With the way things have changed, shouldn’t we just give up on the water source….”

“No, we can’t. We don’t know, but the average refugee can’t afford it anymore. We need to secure the water source.”

Vikir knows he has no choice now that all-out war with Leviathan has begun.

Soon, an expedition to the water source is organized.

With the exception of Major General Orca and Marquis de Sade, who must defend the fortress, Vikir’s supporters have gathered together.

Camus Morgue.

Dolores L. Quovadis.

Bourgeois Ju Sinclaire.

Tudor Donquixote.

Usher Poe Bianca.

Sancho Barataria.

Pigi.

A group of eight people, led by Vikir Van Baskerville, organized the expedition.

The goal: to draw water from a volcanic lake on the opposite peak.

“It would be suicide to lead an army. We can’t afford to leave the fortress unguarded, so we’ll take a small group of trusted friends to break the siege.”

Everyone nodded at Vikir’s words.

The plan is to sneak past the Leviathan’s surveillance under cover of night.

Tudor, who was wearing an explosive belt on his stomach, asked with a very nervous expression.

“So. When are we going?”

Everyone looks at Vikir with a common question.

Vikir, gazing out into the night sky, replied with his usual casual demeanor.

“Now. Right now.”

Chapter 456

Infiltration of the Water Source (5)

◆

The ground shakes.

A cloud of dust rose up along with the sound of horses’ hooves.

Late at night, it was Viscount Baldini who drove his horse to the rear guard post.

[Where is she! Where has she gone! Find her quickly!]

He barked orders at his men in an urgent tone.

Viscount Baldini, still feeling bad about granting a pass to a stranger with no identification, galloped his horse in pursuit.

But he found nothing all the way to the rear post.

In the poisonous archives in the back, he could find no record of the high-ranking demon’s visit.

All he could see were corpses, the byproducts of war.

[Damn it. I hope nothing happened…]

In the end, Viscount Baldini had no choice but to turn his horse around and head back to his post.

….

Soon afterward, Viscount Baldini heard a noise in the wasteland where he had driven his horse back.

A few shadows stirred over the wasteland where only a few corpses of poisonous people were strewn about.

“Huu… that was the most unpleasant blanket in the world.”

Tudor pushed himself to his feet, tossing aside the corpse of the poisonous people he’d been carrying.

“My body is soaked with cold sweat, I’d be in trouble if I were caught.”

“I, I feel like my heart is the size of a pea.”

“Euhhh… It’s heavy and unpleasant”

Beside them, Sancho, Pigi, and Bianca also rose from the dead bodies of the poisonous people.

As the pursuers closed in, the Night Walkers, all of whom had been instructed by Vikir to do so, lay down on the ground, each with a few bodies on top of the others, to avoid eye contact.

“…That was dangerous.”

Vikir pushed off the poisonous people bodies covering and stood up.

Then three others followed him to their feet.

The first to poke her head out from under Vikir’s armpit was Camus.

She narrowed her eyes at Vikir’s waistband on the other side.

“You’re usually so slow, but you’re so fast at times like this.”

“I, I what?”

It was Dolores who poked her head up from Vikir’s side.

This was where she’d jumped in at the last minute.

Camus glared at Dolores.

“They say a well-behaved cat enters the kitchen first… There is nothing wrong with the old saying.”

“Well, it’s not like that, because the bodies of the poisonous people were only here, and something similar happened to me once upon a time during a drinking game in the dormitory, so I did it unknowingly….”

“What? Dormitory? Drinking game? What happened, boyfriend?”

“Who’s your boyfriend!?”

Camus and Dolores glared at each other in the middle of Vikir.

A voice intervened to stop them.

“We’re in enemy territory, so let’s be careful~ Do you really want to do that under a pile of corpses?”

Sinclaire lifted her head with a meek expression.

But her head is still stuck between Vikir’s legs.

“Hey, why are you sticking your head out of there, you’re making this look even more innocent!”

“ …I don’t think that’s your place to say, Sinclaire.”

Camus, Dolores, and Sinclaire began to engage in a subtle nervous war of words over Vikir.

“….”

But Vikir paid no attention to their bickering, his eyes fixed on the road ahead.

Soon, through the red haze, the poisonous people became visible.

The poisonous people inside the wooden fence stood idly by, doing nothing, or hovering around them.

“We’re going to infiltrate the barracks now.”

“We’re going to break through the center?”

“Yes. We could just walk right past them, but the size of the poisonous people is alarming.”

Vikir nodded in response to Tudor’s question.

“These are probably the forces that will be mobilized for tomorrow’s siege. If we can reduce them a bit, it will ease the hands of those left in the castle.”

At Vikir’s words, everyone’s expressions became determined once more.

Now, if they could only break the siege, they could reach the water source.

Vikir and the others scrambled to the mound of dirt that had risen upward, crouched down, and peered through the gap.

‘Baby Madam, it would have been nice if that creature had been there….’

Vikir thought back to his days as a Night Hound.

He would have been able to move much more freely with his partner, but alas, he could not duplicate those movements now.

Then.

“How about digging a hole?”

Camus stepped forward.

Before Vikir could open his mouth in disbelief, she pulled out an object from her bosom and slipped it over her face.

It was a picaresque mask, a mask that could turn a man into a dog.

It was Dantalian artifact that Vikir had given to Camus before traveling to Nouvelle Vague.

Hack-Hack-Hack

Camus instantly transformed into a red-furred dog.

“C-cute….”

Dolores reached out with a twinkle in her eye, but Camus swatted it away.

Then, as a dog, Camus began digging a burrow in the high mound of dirt.

Papapapapag-

In no time at all, the mound of dirt was high and the underground passage equally deep.

Camus burrowed all the way through the wooden fence and barked loudly at Vikir with her tail flicking.

Camus’s blatant gesture of petting prompted Vikir to stroke her head.

“You’re putting the mask to good use, aren’t you?”

“Of course.”

Camus, now back in her human form, glared at Vikir.

Soon, the eight-member death squad came inside through a tunnel under the fence.

A dense red mist makes it difficult to see ahead.

But they can sense the occasional black and red shadows moving about.

Swoosh.

The Night Hound bared its teeth.

The heads of several poisonous people wandering around the tunnel rolled on the floor without a sound.

Vikir nodded as he saw the poison oozing from the cut side of the neck.

“…That’s certainly a lot of poison in there. How on earth did they produce so much poison?”

The number of poisoners people is staggering, as is the amount of poison each one of them has stored in their bodies.

It would take a lot of effort to create such a large number of poisonous people.

‘They’re not that weak compared to the poisonous people I saw before the regression. They were only seen in the latter stages of the War of Destruction.’

Vikir couldn’t help but think back to the question he’d had before the Tochka Destruction War began.

‘How did they create all these poisonous people? Surely there must be a limit to the amount of poison that can be produced….’

Even before Vikir’s regression, the mystery of how Leviathan had managed to produce so much poison had never been solved.

…But.

Something was different in this life.

“Brother. Excuse me-”

Sinclaire poked Vikir in the shoulder with a deft touch.

Sinclaire’s eyes spotted the black barracks beyond the red mist.

Vikir strained his eyes and stared into the fog for a long moment.

Only then did the landscape beyond slowly reveal itself.

Tsutsutsutsutsuts…

The sparse figures of the poisonous people peeking through the fountain-like mist were like charcoal left behind in a burned forest.

They were lined up in a row, and one by one, they were entering the black barracks.

And on the other side of the barracks, the same poisonous people who had just entered were coming out, one by one, twisting into even more grotesque forms, their bodies growing larger and their limbs even longer.

‘…Are they charging up their poison in there, and even their strength seems to be increasing?’

Vikir turned his attention to a large poisonous man who was just entering the barracks.

[Grrrr-grrrr…]

The poisonous man was covered in stab wounds and burn marks, possibly from the Tochka annihilation battle today.

After entering the barracks, it disappeared for a long time, but after a few minutes it crawled out through an exit on the other side of the barracks.

The long limbs were twisted and bent like those of an insect, and the originally hideous face was distorted into something horrifying.

[Geeeeeeek-]

The sword marks that had tattered its body were gone.

As if boasting of its overflowing poison and vitality, it creaked and twisted, disappearing into the red mist.

“Judging by the tension in my Money Hat, there must be some sort of artifact, a very strong one. I think it’s charging the poisonous people with it.”

Vikir nodded at Sinclaire’s words.

Sinclaire was a new character, one who was not here in the original history, and what she had discovered and speculated might hold the key to reversing the original fate.

“Although we’re not far from the water source,… we’ll need to destroy some of this facility in preparation for tomorrow’s defense.”

It was necessary to put the brakes on so that Leviathan could no longer charge the Poisonous People.

For the sake of their allies who would face them tomorrow inside Fort Tochka.

Paralyzing the facility here was not exactly at odds with heading for the water source, so the group nodded in agreement.

“But how do we destroy the poisonous people factory? It seems like it’s hard enough to just break through?”

Tudor asked.

Apparently, the black barracks high up in the dirt mountains housed the highest ranking members of Leviathan House.

Furthermore, the sheer number of poisonous people gathered there would mean death for anyone who trespassed.

To think that they would even destroy a place that seems so difficult to pass through.

But Vikir spoke with a confident voice.

“I have a secret weapon that I have reserved for this moment.”

And then.

Swoosh.

Vikir drew out what he had been hiding deep within the thick fog of blood.

“Vikir! When did you get so big…!?”

It was enough to make everyone in the group’s eyes widen.

Chapter 457

Infiltration of the Water Source (6)

◆

A black barracks sits atop an dirt mountain.

In the center of the barracks was a giant pot, and two giant snakes were coiling inside.

The two snakes circled around each other, biting each other’s tails.

Each time the snakes circled the pot, a pool of poisonous fluid would pool in the center.

The poison is then heated by the wood fire burning beneath the pot, bringing it to a boil and releasing a thick cloud of red vapor.

[Grrrrrrr…]

[Gyaaaaaagh-]

[Kiiiik! Kkeueugh!]

The poisonous people are lined up one by one inside the barracks, smoked by the red steam rising from the pot.

Udeudeug! Udeug! Ppagagag!

The poisonous people, who were about to die, are instantly energized by the red vapor.

Some were so energized that their bodies became bizarrely shaped.

And there is one figure sitting on a throne at the top, watching all of this.

“….”

He wears a black robe that covers his entire body, and a large scythe on his back.

He is known as the Harvester to the Night Walkers.

A mysterious person who stands at the forefront of this Tochka annihilation battle, and especially at the forefront.

The Harvester silently watched as countless poisonous people were reborn from the red mist of death.

Just then.

…Kwakwang!

Something happened.

One side of the barracks was torn to shreds, and a strange figure broke in from outside.

Peopeopeopeog!

As soon as he entered, he immediately cut off the heads of the poisonous people around him.

Dozens of poisonous people were left with their heads rolling on the ground, unable to resist.

“…!”

Harvester jumped to his feet.

The amount of poison, manpower, and time that went into making a single proper poisonous soldier was staggering.

They shouldn’t have to die like this.

The Harvester came down the stairs as if he was flying, and immediately swung his scythe and slashed at the assailant.

…Kkang!

A strange man blocks the Harvester’s scythe with a ragged iron sword that looks like he picked it up somewhere.

For a moment, the Harvester flinched.

He instantly recognized the intruder.

Vikir Van Baskerville, Night Hound. The greatest villain of all time, imprisoned in Nouvelle Vague long ago.

…, So why would he appear here at this moment?

Vikir’s red eyes flashed at the Harvester before him.

Ttaang- kkadeudeudeudeug!

The iron sword pushes away the scythe, creating a pile of sparks.

The cheap iron sword lost countless of its teeth just by colliding with the scythe once, turning it into a lump.

But Vikir continued to swing his iron sword.

Kkang! Kkaang- ttang! Ttaang-

The recklessness of the attack was enough to make even the Harvester cringe.

But this was the headquarters of the Leviathan Family, a place with countless poisonous people.

Chachachachachag!

The giant poisonous people reached out toward Vikir.

Each one of them is a monster with a grip that can distort even a cast iron pot.

Vikir swung his iron sword, which was now almost like a saw blade, and cut off their limbs.

Ppudeudeug- ppudeug- ppagagag! Udeug!

Pieces of flesh and bone fragments with uneven cut edges scatter here and there in the air.

There was even a sense of madness in Vikir’s sword slashing.

…But in the end, he’s outnumbered.

Even Vikir had no choice but to succumb to the onslaught of the poisonous people, who used the corpses of their comrades as shields.

Peoeog!

The palm of one of the poisonous people slammed into Vikir’s face.

Peoeog! Peoeog!

Another palm on top of it.

Peoeog! Peoeog! Peoeog! Peoeog! Peoeog! Peoeog…!

Above it, More and more palms covered Vikir’s face.

Crushed by countless poisonous hands, Vikir finally died, his entire body horribly mutilated.

The poisonous people tore Vikir’s body to shreds in a frenzy.

And then.

…Tug!

Vikir’s body was reduced to its upper half, rolling across the floor like garbage.

The Harvester looked down at Vikir’s body on the ground.

“….”

Then, he reached out with a pale hand and gently brushed a hand across Vikir’s empty eyes.

….

Just then.

Kwadeug!

The upper half of Vikir’s body, which had been thought to be dead, jerked up and bit down on the Harvester’s hand with his teeth.

“!?”

The moment the Harvester is startled and puts his hands back.

…Kwakwang!

The wall right behind the Harvester’s back was torn apart.

The barracks shook once, and again, countless poisonous people died in a torrent.

“…!”

Harvester quickly turned his head.

There was an unbelievable sight.

Vikir. Vikir Van Baskerville.

The man who had been killed by the poisonous people just moments before was alive and well.

Flutter.

With a fluttering sound, Vikir began to destroy the poisonous people, wielding a spear that seemed to have been picked up from nowhere.

Precise, powerful thrusts ripped open vital organs, including the faces and chests of the poisonous people.

Another splash of blood and flesh rippled through the barracks.

The Harvester hesitated for a moment, then threw himself forward to block Vikir.

Taang-!

A winding scythe flew out from the hilt, knocking Vikir’s spear out of his hand.

The poisonous palms of the poisonous people followed through on Vikir’s now-empty abdomen.

Pupupupupupug!

Once again, Vikir was slain by a combined assault of the Poisonous People and Scythe of the Harvester.

…However.

Kwakwang!

The wall of the barracks tore open again, and beyond it, Vikir appeared.

Vikir. Vikir. Vikir. Another Vikir.

More Vikir appeared, tearing apart the poisonous people.

They ravaged the barracks, and the moonlight shining through the dark clouds illuminated the interior.

It was only then that the Harvester noticed something strange about the vikirs who tore through the curtain.

Black hair, red eyes. But their skin color is different.

All of the Vikir’s skin is as black as obsidian.

The barracks was dark, and the glow of the dark red mist rising from the center of the barracks made it hard to see.

Peopeong! Kwakwakwang! Ujijig!

Each of the Vikirs was fierce and vicious, and they could manipulate their weapons like limbs.

Before their inhuman combat power, a violence that questioned whether they were even living creatures at all, the poisonous people were being torn apart like wet leaves.

…Kwang!

In the end, the rampage of countless Vikirs destroyed the pot in the center of the barracks.

The two snakes inside scurried back into the corners, and the thick red mist that had been rising was cut off.

Jjeoeog- peog! Deng-geong-

The Harvester, who had been swinging his scythe to slice and dice the bodies of the Vikirs, was greatly embarrassed when he saw that the pot had been broken.

So were the poisonous people gathered outside the barracks.

Hwaeg-

The Harvester rushed out of the barracks and looked around, but there was no sign of Vikir’s true form.

Peopeong! Kwang! Kuleuleuleug!

All he could hear was the flames raging throughout the barracks, and the noise of the black Vikir rushing about.

◆

Hours ago.

Vikir opened Andromalius’ barrier beneath the Bloodstorm.

What poured out from within were tiny creatures that looked exactly like Vikir.

Doppelganger leeches.

The leeches Vikir had taken from Black Tongue when he left Nouvelle Vague had grown.

“Oh, my, how cute. What are they?”

“Mmmm- definitely, they look like something I’d want to take home and raise.”

“…Brother, where did you get your children from? Isn’t it?”

“Dude, are these really leeches? They look so much like you.”

“Even though I saw it once in Hell Tree last time, I still can’t get used to it.”

“Maybe it’s because he grew up drinking Vikir’s blood, but he looks exactly like Vikir. Just put on the clothes I brought and it’ll be perfect!”

“Wow, now that you’ve dressed him up, he looks exactly the same. That must be very confusing for the enemies….”

Camus, Dolores, Sinclaire, Tudor, Sancho, Pigi, and Bianca, all of them, at one point or another, admired Vikir’s look-alike miniatures.

Except for one thing: skin color.

“Here, eat.”

Vikir fed the leeches a large amount of blood, more than he had ever given them before.

The leeches grow strong after drinking the blood shed by Vikir.

Vikir then set the leeches loose in the center of the poisonous barracks.

The leeches, viciously modified by Black Tongue, went on a mad rampage, began to run wild, attracted by the smell of blood and death coming from everywhere.

“…Well, it was worth the effort.”

Vikir nodded as he watched a significant number of the leeches charge toward the barracks on the dirt mountain.

“Boyfriend, ignition complete!”

In the distance, he could see Camus waving.

Vikir also nodded his head and gave a signal.

Camus understood Vikir’s signal and unleashed her mana.

Kwakwakwakwakwang!

Flames and iron skewers erupted from beneath the dirt mountain.

The poisonous soldiers descending the slope were halted in their tracks, their feet and stomachs pierced by a succession of iron skewers.

The flames began to spread in all directions, using the barracks and the struggling poisonous people as firewood.

…Hwaleuleug!

Vikir turned his head to see that the flames had even reached the storehouses of rations for the common soldiers.

Tudor, Sancho, Pigi, Bianca, Sinclaire, and Dolores, who had succeeded in moving the fire from the front, were also signaling that their mission was complete.

Vikir and Camus quickly joined them.

“We’re headed straight for the water source.”

If they could just get to the peak behind them, blow up one side of the lake, and divert the water, everything would be fine.

Not only would they have water, but they’d be able to wipe out Leviathan’s forces in one fell swoop.

‘Perhaps this will be the last mission.’

Vikir ran quickly towards the shadow of the ridge in front of him.

It was the final finish line, where the fate of Tochka lay.

Chapter 458

Infiltration of the Water Source (7)

◆

Jjeoeog!

One of the giant poisonous people opened its mouth wide.

The gaping mouth was immediately pulled back, and it fell off its jaw and plummeted to the ground.

…Cheolpeodeog!

After slashing at the face of the poisonous people in his way, Vikir landed lightly on the ground.

However, there were still a few poisonous people on the slope leading up to the mountain peak in front of him.

[Grrrrrrr-]

[Kiik- Kiiik-]

[Hiss- Hiss!]

The poisonous soldiers are larger and more powerful than normal poisonous people.

And the poisonous people here are even larger and more grotesque than the average soldier.

Those with three or five heads belong to the ordinary axis.

Their long, twisted bodies were dotted with grotesque appendages that could not possibly have once been human.

Mutants.

An extremely rare creature that is born when a normal poisonous people crosses the line of fire time and time again, accumulating experience and refining their poisons.

The poison and stench emanating from its body were causing the surrounding grass to turn black.

And then one of the larger and more hideous of the poisonous peoples blocking the peak began to appear.

[Gaggak… gaggaggak… gaggaggak… gaggaggak!]

Vikir recognized the creature.

‘Hmm. That’s the one who went into the barracks earlier.’

The one that had just crawled out of the poison charging station he’d seen in the distance.

It was a large, powerful mutant, with no idea why it was stationed so far back.

[Geugilg- a… Beoji… Youngest… ya… gagyagyalg-]

The mutant muttered unintelligible words through its bizarrely altered mouth structure, and Vikir quickly assessed the situation.

‘This is going to be a pain in the ass tomorrow if he’s going to be on the siege. I’ll have to take him down beforehand.’

The Night Hound was just about to bare his teeth at the giant poisonous mutant in front of him.

“Vikir!”

Tudor’s voice came from behind him.

Vikir spun around to see Tudor with a determined look on his face.

“You go first. We’ll take care of this place.”

“….”

“It’s more important to get the waterways open. We’ll do something about the poison mutants, so don’t worry….”

“Got it.”

Tudor had barely finished speaking before Vikir was gone.

Clearly, it would be more efficient that way.

Tudor sighed as he watched Vikir rush off without a backward glance.

“Boy~ At least say no.”

“Now that’s proof that Vikir trusts us as much as he does.”

“I know, and I’m kind of flattered.”

Tudor smirked at Sancho’s axe-raised back, and readjusted his spear.

Soon, the group began to move forward, sending Vikir first and began to block the poisonous people behind him.

“Come on, you scum, let me show you something hot!”

Camus waved her hands, drawing a large magic circle in the air.

Her signature octa-casting, the ability to manipulate eight elemental magics simultaneously.

Eight rains of fire and iron began to fall.

…Peopeopeopeopeopeopeopeong!

The iron skewers that rose up from the ground immediately pierced into the bodies of the poisonous people, melting from the heat and burning their bodies.

“Eeh…If this happens, my gold will melt too. Well, it doesn’t matter?”

Sinclaire drew up her mana and brought it to the ground.

Then, she pulled out the entire gold vein that was sleeping under the stratum.

Ujijijijijig-

A huge golden golem tears up the ground, crawls up to the ground, and throws a massive fist.

The molten gold bubbled and boiled from the flame magic that Camus had created, scattering the liquid in all directions, burning the poisonous people to death.

“Everyone, take a deep breath as much as possible! Don’t go away from me!”

Dolores cast a divine shield as wide as she could, keeping the red death spirits at bay.

Chiiiiiig-

The blood and pus that the poisonous peoples emit as they struggle are evaporated into ordinary vapor as soon as they come in contact with the white light emitted from Dolores’ body.

Tudor, Sancho, Pigi, and Bianca are also emitting auras of their own, blocking the poisonous people’s advances.

“Vikir, can you see anything up there?”

Tudor shouted as he pierced a hole with his spear in the center of the poisonous people’s large palm.

See- see- see- see-

Tudor’s strained voice echoes through the layers of trees and cliffs.

Vikir, who had just climbed over the peak, recognized the faint but clear sound of Tudor’s voice.

But it was

“….”

Vikir had no answer to Tudor’s plea.

No food. No water.

No matter how hard he peered down into the crater, he could see no water.

“….”

Vikir took a few deep breaths and then looked carefully at the scenery below the crater.

He could see a hillside of dry dirt rolling away from the overgrown vegetation below.

As he followed the line of sight, he saw nothing but an empty wasteland.

There was no sign of water in the crater, just dry dirt and hard rocks.

Only a few dried tumbleweeds rolled around in the grass.

MiniPin’s information had been wrong.

Vikir gritted his teeth.

It was information he hadn’t known before the regression, and he doubted it.

The uncertainty he’d leaned on had turned out to be a fatal hand.

Kwakwakwang!

Vikir struck a blow, collapsing part of the peak.

But there was still no water.

‘…This is dangerous.’

At this point, they should change course and return to Tochka as soon as possible.

But the rear was already surrounded by the poisonous people.

Vikir flew down the rock face to rejoin the front.

The chaos at the Poison Charging Station hadn’t been completely cleaned up yet, and the poisonous people were still spread out, but it looked like they could put out the immediate fire.

‘After clearing out the poisonous people here, we’ll take advantage of the distraction and head for Tochka. Perhaps by moving in reverse, the siege network will be less vigilant… and all that remains is to hope that the leeches will hold out as long as possible.’

Vikir scrambled down the cliff, planning this and that.

The moment.

“…!”

An unexpected event occurred that made Vikir’s plans and judgments go to waste in an instant.

“Hohohoho… I see all the troublemakers of Tochka have gathered here.”

A face with a sharp hooked nose, tightly closed lips, and a dark shadow beneath deep, sunken eyelids beneath black hair.

A grim-looking, middle-aged man dressed in black priestly robes stepped through the crowd of poisonous people.

There was not a member of the group who did not recognize his face.

A genius who knows how to combine all the poisons and medicines in the world.

A fearsome figure that not even Hugo of Baskerville is reluctant to deal with.

Duke Hobbes de Leviathan.

He is the patriarch of the extremely poisonous House Leviathan and a key player in the current civil war in the Empire.

Vikir has to grit his teeth when Hobbes shows up much earlier than expected.

Meanwhile.

“Hmm. I can see what brought you here.”

Hobbes scanned the faces of the Night Walkers once more, smiled grimly, and thrust his long spear forward.

A spear blade that looks like two long snakes entwined around a hard, dried wooden handle.

“Go, ‘Ouroboros’.”

Hobbes’s command dropped.

Hiss-

The spear began to wriggle as if it were alive.

Every time the spear swings, the evil spirits of the Red Death run wild and swirl around Hobbes.

Huge, hideous, poisonous mutants were standing behind Hobbes along the red mist, spewing out terrifying killing intent.

When Vikir saw his companions and Hobbes facing each other across the mountainside, he accelerated his steps even more.

‘…That guy is dangerous.’

The Second Corpses.

During the Age of Destruction, the Demon King was never defeated in many-to-one, one-to-one, or many-to-many battles.

The most vicious and wicked of the ten demons.

If Vikir was a seasoned demon hunter, he was a seasoned human hunter.

“Don’t fight him! You don’t stand a chance against him…!?”

However, Vikir’s shouts to his companions were short-lived.

Peo-eong!

A thunderbolt of fire came out of nowhere and hit Hobbes.

As soon as he appeared, Hobbes’ head turned and he was thrown backwards, spouting out blood.

“…?”

As Vikir’s mouth dropped open in surprise, a series of fearsome pillars of fire rained down on the pit where Hobbes lay.

Wa-jijijijijig! Kwakwakwakwakwakwang! …kkwaleuleung!

It was a thunderbolt of fire, each with huge, red-hot iron skewers built into them like pencil lead.

“Hohohoho- I guess I’ll just have to hunt demons until Vikir comes. It worked, because I can start with the king.”

Camus, who had been controlling her pace up until this point, let loose her limits for the first time in a long time.

Tsutsutsutsutsutsutsuts…

A huge, black tree began to grow above the red-hot flames created by Camus.

The Wraith Tree.

It had fully bloomed and become a mature tree, and before we knew it, it was bearing fruit.

Chapter 459

Infiltration of the Water Source (8)

◆

Camus has begun to show her full power.

“I’ve been holding back a bit of my power for fear of intimidating the others…!”

She fired her mana and the Wraith Tree began to shake its branches in response.

The skull-shaped branches moved ominously.

The hanging corpses swayed like clockwork.

Each and every one of them was a vicious criminal or demon during their lifetime.

Ooooooooooooo…

Even in death, they were unable to fulfill their destiny and became a source of energy for Camus, squeezing them to their limits.

They let out blood-curdling cries.

“Let me show you something cool!”

Camus drew dozens of magic circles in the air at once.

Each and every one of them were powerful fire and iron magic.

…Peopeopeopeopeong!

A ground-to-air missile that pursues its target until the end.

Rising from the ground, the giant iron skewers were engulfed in flames and shot up into the sky in a fiery trajectory before plummeting toward their targets.

Kwa-kwakwakwakwakwakwakwakwang!

The earth’s axis ripped and twisted, and countless pillars of fire erupted.

A mushroom-shaped cloud of dirt rises with a massive tremor.

But Camus wasn’t the only one in action.

“I’m going to show you demons the horrors of man-made capitalism.”

Sinclaire. A woman who became the world’s number one in place by ascending to the position of the head of the Bourgeois family of the tycoons.

She took off the ‘Rich Hat’ she was wearing.

Then the hat awakens and reveals its unique abilities, which have been hidden until now.

Jjalgeurang- jjalgeurang- jjalgeurang- jjalgeurang- jjalgeurang- jjalgeurang- jjalgeurang- jjalgeurang-jjalgeurang- jjalgeurang- jjalgeurang- jjalgeurang-jjalgeurang- jjalgeurang- jjalgeurang- jjalgeurang-jjalgeurang- jjalgeurang- jjalgeurang- jjalgeurang-

A huge amount of gold coins began to pour out of the hat.

This was the inventory ability to store an infinite quantity of money.

“Remember this money? It’s Belial’s inheritance.”

Money is power. Wasn’t that Belial’s slogan?

As Sinclaire drew on the mana amplified by her vast wealth, the gold coins that popped out of her hat clumped together and changed her appearance.

[Uh-oooooooohh!]

A giant golem of gold coins rose up behind Sinclaire’s back.

It was as large as a fairly large building and began to imitate Sinclaire’s body movements.

…Kwakwang! Kung! Ujijijig!

The golden golem also raised its heavy fist and began punching its target.

It was a sight as if the fear of golden omnipotence was being expressed with the whole body.

“Wow- they really are another class.”

“I can’t believe they’re so motivated.”

“Ewww, I’ll find something I can do and do it too!”

“I guess the only way to catch up is to train like hell.”

Tudor, Pigi, Sancho, and Bianca clucked their tongues as they watched Camus and Sinclaire explode with destructive force in the distance.

Dolores, meanwhile, was expanding the Holy Shield further, pushing back the poisonous people behind her.

‘We must hold out until Vikir arrives!’

There was hope, as Camus and Sinclaire were currently fighting beyond expectations.

Watching the ground explode and tear apart in real time before their eyes, it’s almost tempting to think that maybe they can hunt demons without Vikir.

…But that soon proved to be too much to hope for.

[Hohoho- the youngsters are lively these days, no time for old men to wear masks].

A figure emerges from a thick cloud of mushrooms.

He was no longer Hobbes de Leviathan.

A face transformed into that of a wild beast, a black mane, eyes burning yellow like fire brimstone, and a long spear in his hand.

<‘The Second Corpse’ Flauros>

Danger Rating : S

Size: ?

Found in: The Serpent’s Womb, deep within the Gate of Destruction

-Also known as ‘Second Corpse’.

One of the Ten Plagues, natural enemies of mankind, incomprehensible and unkillable.

“I will turn the water into blood.”

– 『Ten Commandments』10: Top –

Second Corpse. Among the protagonists who led the Age of Destruction.

Flauros brushed the flames from his skin and said.

[Wraith Tree, I haven’t seen one in a while, it would be perfect for the hilt of my spear].

As he spoke, Flauros raised the spear in his hand.

Two snakes, both of them alive, became the blade.

The shaft of the spear was made of dried tree trunk, and Dolores recognized the material at a glance.

“Hell Tree!”

[Hohoho- yes, that’s right, Amdusias’s beloved tree].

Flauros grabbed his spear and swung it once, clearing away all the golden waves.

At the tip of the demon’s spear, two snakes tangled together.

It was the snake that created the Red Death.

“…Is that the artifact that produces the Red Death?”

Tudor’s eyes widened, having lost his father to the plague.

Bang!

Slamming the ground with all his might, Tudor stretched Gungnir forward.

A tidal wave of blows washed over Flauros.

Flauros whistled and turned his head to the side.

[Oh- so this is the flesh Cimeries was looking for, not bad].

Tudor’s charge had missed by a single sheet of paper.

And the cost would not end with the weight of a piece of paper.

Thud.

The spear Ouroboros struck the spear Gungnir, forcing it off its path.

And through the gap, two snakes slithered in like ghosts and pressed Tudor’s neck into the ground.

“Keoheog!?”

Tudor spat up blood and fell to the ground.

It happened in a single blow.

“Tudor!”

Bianca immediately raised her bow.

Running forward, she fired a powerful sniper shot, aiming for Flauros’s head.

Ppeoeog-

As soon as the dull noise of an arrow hitting the center of Flauros’ face erupts, Bianca grabbed Tudor and lifted him up.

But Tudor’s complexion was pale blue.

“Bianca! Back!”

“!?”

It was a misjudgment to think that the arrow hit the target just by seeing it hit the face.

Where Bianca turned, she saw Flauros grinning, biting the arrowhead with his teeth.

[So this is the body Andrealphus wanted. Why was it so rushed…]

Then, Flauros stretched out his hands and brought them to Tudor and Bianca.

[I’ll turn you both into Corpses, in keeping with the will of my comrades… Hmm!?]

But Flauros was cut off mid-sentence.

Pis-

A thin slash flew past Flauros’ cheek.

[….]

For some reason, Flauros, who had remained nonchalant in the face of Camus and Dolores’ combined attack, took two steps backwards.

And in front of him stood an unexpected figure.

Pigi.

A man who stood up for his friends even as his legs shook.

“Get away from my friends!”

Pigi swung his sword and emitted an aura.

His aura had grown stronger over the course of his time at Colosseo Academy and his survival in the harsh world.

But there was something special about Pigi’s attack.

He had his own blood on the tip of his sword.

[…! …! …!]

Flauros frowned as he saw numerous small scars forming on his forearms.

[So, it’s an heteromorphic body, It is also a closed form, This is why he was so disgusting.]

Flauros’s expression, which had been relaxed until now, changed.

[I never thought I’d encounter a ‘homogeneous anomaly’ ahead of my great work. Is it worthwhile to abandon the civil war and come this far?]

Then, the demon’s fearsome eyeballs locked onto Pigi.

“Hic!”

Pigi shuddered, but didn’t back away.

Flauros’s hand was slowly moving toward Pigi.

Then.

“Back off, buddy!”

“Get out! Something is suspicious!”

Tudor and Bianca grabbed Pigi by both arms and pulled him backwards.

Tudor’s spear and Bianca’s snipe bounced off Flauros’s arm.

Tudor and Bianca, with Pigi far behind them, said.

“By the looks of it, he’s got his sights set on you.”

“Yeah, I’ve been sensing it since the Hell Tree. There’s definitely something about you.”

Tudor and Bianca, who were quick-witted, were protecting Pigi early on.

“Huh? Guys – I’m not that special….”

“Back off!”

A giant axe flew from behind, slicing through Flauros.

Sancho hugged Tudor, Bianca, and Pigi all at once and stepped back.

Before them, Camus and Sinclaire’s barrage fell.

…Kwakwakwakwang!

Flauros stretched out his spear as if it was a nuisance and blocked the combined attack of Camus and Sinclaire.

[Nuisances].

However, Flauros could not afford to relax.

…Bam!

The power of Camus and Sinclaire’s combined attack had a different kind of energy.

It was the holy white heat! It was a blessing from Dolores herself.

Buffed by the saintess, Camus and Sinclaire unleashed a torrent of holy flames to burn away the Red Death.

Only then did Flauros’ expression harden.

[How annoying. Since we don’t know what will happen in the future, it is right to organize things in advance.]

The first direction Flauros’s spear pointed was in the direction of Camus.

[First, starting with the four most annoying…]

The two snakeheads pointed at Camus exuded a level of malice that no normal human could stand.

Kwakwakwakwakwang!

A dark red storm arises and sweeps away the surroundings.

Fragments of aura and poison scatter like powder, tearing and burning everything around.

“Keueug!?”

Camus gritted her teeth as she saw the wraith tree shake violently.

Was it because it hadn’t yet deeply rooted itself into the Mental World?

It would need a little more time to become a giant tree.

Patsutsut- Tsutsutsutsu-

A shield was hastily created and deployed, but it was unable to block the entire aftermath.

The thick coat of blood she wore began to burn and reveal her bare skin.

Despite maximizing her mana, she was unable to fend off Flauros’ power, which was focused solely in her direction.

“Camus!”

Her companions rushed forward, only to be blocked by the poisonous people.

In a moment of desperation, Camus gritted her teeth.

They had traveled all the way to the water source, but there was no water.

In fact, from that moment on, she knew she was going to die.

From that moment on, death was looming in the distance.

‘…Is this the end?’

Camus thought to herself as she swallowed hard against the rising tide of blood.

Slowly, her strength was slipping away, her body slowly collapsing.

Just as she was about to collapse.

Flutter-

Camus’ body, which was almost half naked, was covered with a black layer of blood.

“It’s a memorable one.”

And a single black knight stood in her way.

“…Aah.”

Camus let out a weak groan.

Even as her vision blurred, she could somehow see the man’s face clearly.

Vikir. Night Hound.

He was facing Flauros.

Chapter 463

The Prelude to a Counterattack (1)

◆

This is the first time Flauros has been hit.

Black Tongue. Considered the most dangerous man in Nouvelle Vague, he was the one who stabbed Flauros in the back.

…However.

Black Tongue’s appearance was quite different from the one Vikir remembered.

For one thing, it was much shorter and more petite.

His eyes, which had been clouded with flavor, now glowed with a straightforward firearm.

The black veins that covered his body like armor were the same as before, but the form was unmistakably female.

Kirko. Captain Kirko Grimm was standing there, staring at Vikir.

…Peoeog!

Then, the magic sword Asmodeus was pulled out of Flauros’s back.

The entire hilt of the sword was greatly expanded from the amount of blood it had already absorbed.

[What kind of nonsense…!?]

The moment an enraged Flauros turns his head with red death in his mouth, a green substance is seen covering his vision.

Cheolpeog!

Not only does the poison spew out from Flauros’ mouth, but it is also a liquid monster that completely covers the entire body.

The dense body of Flubber stretched out from Kirko’s back and engulfed Flauros.

Tsutsutsutsutsuts…

The red death spirit that Flauros was emitting was absorbed by the Flubber.

Seeing this, Vikir opened his mouth.

“…You.”

Kirko. She had surely seen the last of the Nouvelle Vague.

But now she was here, on the ground, in front of Vikir’s eyes.

With BDISSEM chains, Asmodeus the Magic Sword, and even Flubber!

Then, Kirko’s lips moved in a small smile.

“…It was you, wasn’t it? You saved my life.”

“….”

Vikir didn’t exactly deny it.

He had done one thing to save Kirko’s life just before they escaped Nouvelle Vague.

It was something he had arranged during the elimination of BDISSEM just before the escape.

‘Please let me live… I’ll do anything.’

‘Normally, it’s faster to just kill you.’

‘Hic!’

‘…But there’s one more thing I want. If you do it right, I might have a way to save your life.’

‘What, what is it? What is that?’

‘I want two things. First, the original purpose. And the second…’

Vikir, who had used BDISSEM to orchestrate a massive prison break, had last seen to Kirko’s safety.

‘If you wait outside the window of the fifth floor kennel, a person will come out. You must bring that person back to the ground alive. This person’s name is Kirko Grimm, rank is Captain, and gender is female.’

This is because, If she survived, she could make a great contribution to the Human Alliance in the future.

And Vikir’s actions would eventually lead to Kirko’s current placement on the surface.

Someone who, according to fate, should have been dead by this point.

“…Why did you become ‘Black Tongue’?”

Vikir asked, and Kirko gave a very brief explanation.

“When the Nouvelle Vague collapsed and I was being swept away by the sea, I heard a voice calling to me.”

It was the shard of a sword that was on its way to sinking into the depths of the sea.

It was the voice of Asmodeus, broken into nine pieces.

Faintly but clearly audible, the sword’s call was of an indescribable nature.

Asmodeus. A sword that, along with Beelzebub, belongs to the Seven Demon Swords.

It was broken into nine pieces by Vikir and sunk to the depths of the ocean.

As it should have been, no one should have found it for all eternity.

…But the sword spoke up and found a new owner.

What it wanted was clear.

It wanted blood, and to get it, it needed a symbiotic host.

Kirko, who was destined to die from being crushed by the heavy water pressure in the cold sea water, unconsciously accepted the sword’s offer.

And fate took a turn for the worse.

Chosen by the sword, Kirko was given the superhuman body of a vampire, just as Black Tongue had once been.

A body that could withstand the terrible pressure of the deep. The mobility to move even after holding her breath for days.

At that time, she was rescued by BDISSEM and brought to the surface, along with several other guards who were also being swept away by the tide.

It’s no surprise that most of the guards saved by Kirko bowed before her power.

Kirko glanced back at Flubber, who was crawling up her shoulder.

“I rescued this one along there, too. I think it’s because it has a strong attachment to the place called Nouvelle Vague.”

For some reason, Flubber hadn’t left Nouvelle Vague until now.

Its strong attachment and obsession with the place is documented in ancient texts.

Kirko’s decision to stay and share her last moments with Nouvelle Vague despite its collapse must have impressed the liquid creature greatly.

As a result, Flubber stays by Kirko’s side, acting very friendly.

As for Kirko, its body’s acidic ability is not particularly evident, so it appears that she can control it.

Vikir looked at Kirko and thought for a moment.

‘So much talent, so much potential, and so much luck to sweep all the odds in your favor.’

Maybe he had rescued an absurd butterfly from under the wheel of fate.

And the butterfly effect was a wonderful one.

Kwakwang!

Kirko, who can wield the power of the BDISSEM chain, the magic sword Asmodeus, and Flubber at the same time, is truly Nouvelle Vague itself.

She blocked Flauros, who was spouting red death, very easily.

While Flauros, wrapped in the BDISSEM chain, panicked at the sudden interruption of his mana flow, Flubber ate the red death, and Asmodeus slipped through the gap.

Peoeog!

Asmodeus once again sucked blood into Flauros mouth.

[Ugh!? Where do these things come from…!?]

The Nouvelle Vague’s extraordinary powers, hidden at the farthest reaches of the depths, were foreign even to Flauros, who had carefully studied all aspects of the human world.

Kwakwakwakwang!

Kirko’s attack was cut short as Flauros swung his Original Ouroboros.

But it was enough to buy time.

Kirko stepped back and said.

“Since then, I’ve met Aiyen and traveled here with her, and I’ve heard a bit about you.”

“I gave her a lot of advice, since she seemed to be quite confused about her identity, that the surface is a good place to live. Hmm- even if it’s like this, I’m a woman with quite a warm heart, Husby.”

Aiyen said, jumping down beside Kirko.

The Ballak’s attitude toward nature must have been a great lesson to Kirko, who was new to the surface.

“I searched for you as soon as I came to the surface. You forced me to live when I didn’t want to, so you’re to blame.”

Kirko stared at Vikir, her gaze unwavering and proud.

Then, there were hands on Vikir’s shoulders.

“…You need to talk to me privately later, boyfriend.”

“I’m a little bit curious about the responsibility… It’s a responsibility.”

“Bro, brother, who’s that uniform girl, and where did you get into trouble?”

Camus, Dolores, and Sinclaire surrounded Vikir, giving off an odd aura.

At that moment.

[Hohoho- I don’t think now is the time to leisurely talk about the latest news~]

The demonized Sadi interrupted.

She swung her whip at the swarming poisonous people.

Kirko and Aiyen stiffened as well.

They went out to sea and made a raft out of corpses, were attacked by a swarm of sharks on the way, fought a naval battle with a mysterious ghost ship, and so much more… there’s a lot more to the story, but that’s for another time!

Later, after slaying the demon, it would be enough to solve the story all night long.

[You’ve brought some pretty troublesome stuff with you, but it’s not a game changer just because it’s unusual].

Flauros glared at Vikir and opened his mouth.

His repaired Original Ouroboros was ready to spew red death again.

Vikir lowered his stance and faced Flauros.

Certainly, the addition of Aiyen and Kirko would be a great boost to the battle, but they alone would not be able to hunt down the Flauros in front of them.

Vikir was planning what to do next.

“U-waaaaaaaah!”

Tudor’s cheer came from behind.

Tudor running around looking backwards.

Soon, Sancho, Pigi, and Bianca join in, their voices rising in excitement.

“…!”

Vikir jerked his head back.

He could feel the ground vibrating slightly.

Dudeudeug- dudeudeug- dudeudeug- dudeudeug-

The sound of hooves shaking the earth. A roar of triumph.

U-waaaaaaaah!

An army with four banners was approaching at incredible speed toward them.

The barracks of the poisonous people crumble. The poisonous soldiers were trampled like rotten leaves.

Mage Master Family Morgue.

Faithful Saint Family Quovadis.

Tycoon Family Bourgeois.

…And the Iron-Blooded Swordsmen, the Baskervilles.

All four allied Houses were sending reinforcements here, each with their most elite troops!

Kirko wiped off her cold sweat and smiled slightly.

“Well, it was worth to gain some time.”

They could see the Salvation Army coming.

The expressions of the group members present became determined again.

Vikir also raised his head and looked at Flauros in front of him.

[….]

Flauros’ expression was crumpled, as if he hadn’t expected such a situation.

Now the stage was slowly approaching its conclusion.

Chapter 466

The Prelude to a Counterattack (4)

◆

“…Miracles are sure to happen to those who believe.”

Dolores covered her mouth with her hands and muttered in a low voice.

Anyone who saw what was happening in front of their eyes could say that, even if they were not members of the Lun Church.

A horde of giant spiders, and the single largest spider of them all.

Time has passed so quickly that the Baby Madam, who was once as small as a lump of dust, has now become a mother with a gigantic body.

A huge mother with a bunch of small(?) children who look exactly like her!

“…I can’t believe it.”

“You’re much bigger than Madam Eight-Legs.”

The Madame cub was so huge that even Camus and Aiyen, who had seen the mother before, could not hide their surprise.

It was like a mountain moving.

Kwalkwalkwalkwalkwalkwalkwalkwal…

A wall of spiders blocks the stream of water polluted by the Red Death.

A spider monster from the world.

For a creature that thrives on poison, the Red Death was like the first fatty meal they’d had in a long time.

The power, size, and gluttony of the spiders, which even demons were reluctant to confront, blocked even the seemingly unstoppable wave of red death.

Gulp, gulp, gulp, gulp, gulp, gulp, gulp, gulp-

The streams that the spiders touched became clear and transparent again.

The red death aura was being cleansed away by the countless spiders.

The priests on one side, the spiders on the other, hold the Red Death at bay.

Flubber, too, was devouring the poisonous people, growing in size and inhaling more and more of the Red Death.

Camus and Aiyen were beside him, draping an arm over Dolores’ shoulders.

“Hey, Holy Water Vending Machine. You and my boyfriend were having such a good time earlier. What should I do now that I’m sad that I have less work to do?”

“Ah, that’s a shame!? And who’s the vending machine! It is blasphemy! And why is Vikir your boyfriend in the first place?”

“Oh- I also benefited from this saintly juice a long time ago. Hahaha-”

“J-juice!”

Behind him, Sinclaire was barely holding back her laughter, and Kirko was just standing there with a sullen expression on her face.

Then. In front of everyone, Madame cub bowed her head.

Ku-gugugugugu…

The cub slowly lowered her face to where Vikir stood.

The sound of the carapace rubbing against the carapace surrounding the joint was transmitted like an earthquake through the ground.

It’s a bit strange to see a fully grown adult.

Vikir looked at her with some wariness.

However.

Ppangsis-

Madame cub lowered her head in front of Vikir and smiled brightly.

Back in the days in the dormitory of the Colosseo Academy, she would wait alone in his room while Vikir was out for class, and when Vikir would open the door and come back, she would always look like that.

[Hack-hack-hack-]

The cub tilted her head toward Vikir.

A fierce hug, seemingly oblivious to her own size.

“…Mmm. Well, yeah. You’ve grown a lot, really.”

[Kkiing- kkeung-]

When Vikir strokes her, she wags her tail and burrows into his arms like she used to.

She may have gotten bigger, but she’s still a baby.

Just then, a familiar voice rang out above the cub’s head.

“Hunting Leader!”

“Brother! I’ve come to help!”

How could he forget those voices?

Vikir looked up and saw the faces of those he had bonded with in the jungle.

Aheul, whom he had met in the Hell Tree, and Ahun, whom he hadn’t known alive since, stared at him with a bow in hand.

Behind them, the warriors of Ballak, all of whom Vikir had thought dead, smile at him, revealing their white teeth.

[Grrrr!]

A roar erupted from behind Vikir, who was just about to wave.

Bakira, the returning spirit of Aiyen, roars toward the sky.

An answering roar came from the gathering of Ballak’s warriors.

A wolf, identical to Bakira’s, reared its head.

Viola, Aheul’s partner. Bakira’s daughter.

The wolf father and daughter also share a long-overdue reunion.

And then.

Peopeong! Peog! Peo-eog!

The fearsome archery of Ballak’s warriors began to push the poisonous people back.

Aheul’s performance, in particular, was almost unrivaled.

Based on the stats she had gained from the Hell Tree, she was overwhelming the strength of even the most elderly Ballak warriors.

“You’ve improved a lot, Aheul.”

“…Hunting leader!”

Aiyen patted Aheul’s head roughly.

Aheul’s eyes filled with tears as soon as she saw Aiyen’s face.

Meanwhile, Vikir landed on his side and asked Ahun.

“What about the chieftain?”

“She was attacked by a demon in the form of a horse. She still suffered from the effects of her battle with Adonai, but she broke the tip of the demon’s horn…..”

Vikir nodded silently at Ahun’s words.

Perhaps the reason he was able to defeat Amdusias so soon after emerging from the Hell Tree was because of Akwilla’s previous battle.

Amdusias hadn’t been able to overcome the aftereffects of Akwilla’s power.

Then, a hand tapped Vikir on the shoulder.

Kirko. She said with her eyes shining.

“Now is your chance. It’s time to strike back.”

Vikir nodded his head in agreement.

Soon, all the reinforcements began to push toward the peak.

“Capture Leviathan’s lord!”

Baskerville, Morgue, Quovadis, Bourgeois, Tochka reinforcements, and even Ballak and the spiders.

Flauros became the target of all who gathered here.

[…Huh.]

Flauros shakes his head in disbelief.

But the tide of battle has definitely turned.

Even his secret weapon, poison release, has been neutralized by the priests of Quovadis and the spiders of the Jungle, making things quite difficult for the demon.

Furthermore, the warriors of Baskerville and Morgue were now tearing through the poisonous people with terrifying force, and the battle could be over in a matter of moments.

Flauros looked back at Vikir and smirked.

[Yes, I admit it, I guess I saw your world too easily.]

A declaration of defeat came from the demon’s mouth.

But Vikir knew better than anyone that a victory was not a victory unless the enemy’s life was ended.

Especially not against a demon.

Kwang!

At the same time as Vikir stomped on the ground and charged out, Flauros also jumped back.

“…Here’s where we need to catch him.”

Flauros was a strong and cunning being.

All demons were, but among them, Flauros was far more dangerous.

Vikir raced up the mountain peak, intent on killing him.

The poisonous people tried to stop him, but the five behind him blew away the obstacles and cleared the way.

Camus, Aiyen, Dolores, Sinclaire, and Kirko.

Blazing flames, iron skewers, powerful arrows, holy protection, golden giants, and vampiric creatures overwhelmed the wall of poisonous people who tried to protect Flauros from Vikir.

Then Vikir broke through the crumbling wall of poisonous people and grabbed Flauros from behind.

“Demon.”

Black Sun. Eight ferocious teeth bared.

“Kill.”

The hound had a strong killing intent.

Just then.

[…Oh, my son!]

Flauros suddenly turned his face over.

A black shadow flashed in front of Flauros as he pulled back the leopard skin, revealing the facial hide of Hobbes, the head of House Leviathan.

At the same time.

…Kkaang!

Vikir had to lift Beelzebub to block the heavy scythe falling on the top of his head.

Flutter-!

The black scythe, tattered from countless battles, swung around.

The Harvester, who breathes out a thick fog of poison, blocking Vikir’s path.

Kwagigigig!

Sword and scythe clash, creating countless sparks of fire.

But the Harvester was no match for Vikir.

The more teeth there were, and the more dizzy the sword strike, the more the Harvester was being pushed away by Vikir mercilessly.

“Some poisons don’t work on me.”

After speaking, Vikir removed the scythe with his sword and at the same time struck the Harvester’s chest with his palm.

Thwack!

A heavy crack sounded from the Harvester’s breastplate as it cracked open.

But Flauros was unperturbed.

[Hang in there, son, the Movement Magic Circle will be activated soon].

The words were spoken more to mock Vikir than to encourage the Harvester.

Flauros turned back to Vikir with a mocking look on his face.

[Now, write ‘it’].

Hearing Flauros’s command, the Harvester immediately pulled a handful of something from his bosom.

A black sphere, with many barbed spikes sprouting from it.

Vikir recognized it at a glance.

“The seed of the Hell Tree!”

[Yes! It comes out when it’s bored, doesn’t it?]

Flauros answered on his behalf.

Around them, the rumbling poisonous clouds were gathering once more.

It wasn’t just the Hell Tree Seed that was distorting space.

“It’s space movement magic!”

“It’s quite high class, brother!”

Camus and Sinclaire’s urgent voices came from behind.

Vikir gritted his teeth and picked up his pace, but he couldn’t seem to keep up with the countless Hell Tree Seeds flying in front of him.

‘If I get hit by one of those, I don’t know what will happen.’

‘If I’m dragged into the Illusionary World again, I have no answer.’

If he were to be dragged into the Hell Tree once more in such a desperate time of war, it would be a terrible thing indeed.

Vikir had no choice but to give up on the frontal assault.

…But at that very moment.

“Vikir, go!”

A voice called out, clearing the way for Vikir.

…Peopeopeog!

Vikir’s path was cleared by a being who blocked the seeds of the Hell Tree with his entire body.

Vikir’s eyes widened at the unexpected help.

Pigi.

He gritted his teeth, his body covered in blood.

Chapter 467

The Prelude to a Counterattack (5)

◆

‘Get out.’

Into the darkness.

Once again, Pigi found himself in the same environment.

The only difference was that this time Pigi knew it was an illusion.

‘…Ah, is this a childhood memory?’

Pigi looked at his younger self and the middle-aged man standing in front of him.

The face was familiar, but strangely unrecognizable, a face that was shrouded in a haze.

‘This scum is not my blood.’

A memory from the distant past, one that even Pigi himself couldn’t remember, played.

It was the same vision he’d had when he was a freshman at Colosseo Academy, when he’d nearly died during a midterm exam.

‘I seem to be unusually good at seeing visions.’

It was true at the Academy, it was true when he was trapped in the Hell Tree, and it was true now.

He’d gotten used to having strange visions and hallucinations whenever his life was in danger.

…But the sound of his mother’s cries that followed was always hard to get used to, and made his heart sink.

And the contempt and hatred that follows.

‘How dare you be so lowly, you don’t even know the subject.’

‘Get him out of here now.’

‘…Get rid of him.’

The chatter around him swirls and follows the sobs.

Pigi’s vision shifts several times after that.

Fleeing mothers, forests and mountains, pursuers, steep cliffs, raging rivers, hungry wolves, and the startled faces of passing merchants and mercenaries.

Time passes, and so do memories.

His mother, who never smiled and always looked at him with a sad expression.

His stepfather, who was always there to comfort her and give his son the love he deserved, becoming a strong pillar of the family.

In the face of his father’s devoted efforts, her mother gradually began to smile.

And then came the entrance ceremony. Colosseo Academy, the best university in the empire.

Pigi wanted to show his mother, who was full of unhappiness, and his father, who had dedicated his life to making her happy.

…But it wasn’t all smooth sailing.

At Peggy’s first school, he was bullied. This was due to his timid nature.

His relatively frail body, as opposed to his brilliant brain, caused him to fail various tests.

The scenery of Hell Tree continuing after the academy days. Motives who brutally kill each other.

The next scene is a world in flames.

Monsters run rampant, civil wars rage, and the world becomes increasingly desolate.

…However.

Pigi was bravely overcoming all of this.

Despite all the hardships and adversity, Pigi was able to hold on to life and persevere.

‘It’s okay now.’

It was the voices of his friends who always stood behind him.

It was Pigi’s relationships with his friends that always had his back, even when he could have easily lost sight of the world.

The blunt but warm voice behind him made Pigi smile and murmur to himself.

“He’s a good guy.”

A moment.

‘Huh? Come to think of it…’

It was the same voice he’d heard when he’d fought Amdusias the 5th, Cimeries the 4th, and Andrealphus the 3rd.

‘A good man.’

An auditory hallucination that embarrassed countless demons.

That was what he heard every time his blood flowed into the demons.

A moment.

…Huug!

A face popped up in front of Pigi.

‘Can’t you hear me? I said get out!’

That was….

◆

“…Huh!?”

Pigi opened his eyes.

The first thing that came into view was a face.

Vikir.

Vikir was looking down into Pigi’s face.

“It’s okay now, Pigi.”

The voice sounded exactly like the one he’d heard in the vision.

Pigi smiled weakly through her fading eyes.

“ …You’re a good man, you always were, and you always will be.”

“Pigi! Come to your senses, the bleeding has stopped!”

Vikir shook Pigi’s body.

But even though the bleeding had stopped, too much blood had been lost.

The Hell Tree Seed had spread like wildfire, lodging deep within Pigi’s body and tearing out all of his internal organs.

Pigi swallowed a gulp of blood and answered.

“Closing the Hell Tree is the only thing I’m good at, and even though I can’t do anything else, … I really wanted to help.”

“Don’t be silly…!”

Vikir opened his mouth, but Pigi shook his head.

“Go.”

“….”

“Go kill the demon. Save the world.”

Pigi looked at Vikir with all the strength in his eyes.

“If I can’t be a hero, but I can be a hero’s friend, I’ll be satisfied. Go!”

Vikir gritted his teeth at Pigi’s shout.

In front of him, the Harvester still stood tall and steadfast with his scythe.

Behind him, this time, Flauros was activating an ultra-long-distance magic circle.

“Move!”

Dropping Pigi to the ground, Vikir swung his sword at the Harvester.

Thwack-!

The Harvester returned Vikir’s blow with a casual gesture, as if he was willing to play along to buy time.

…Kwagigigig!

Vikir’s blade fell, and the Harvester’s scythe picked it up.

A brief confrontation ensued between the two.

“…I know who you are.”

Pigi’s voice instantly sent a shiver down the Harvester’s spine.

Pigi’s dying eyes were giving him a contemplative stare.

“…He’s the demon, and you’re being lied to.”

“….”

“And you have the power to see through it.”

Pigi coughed and spat out a few mouthfuls of black blood.

Then he spoke with difficulty.

“I don’t think you’re a bad person, we were friends….”

But Pigi didn’t finish his sentence.

His hand fell to the floor as he struggled to smile as he said the word friend.

“Pigi!”

Tudor and Sancho ran crying, but were blocked by the wall of the last poisonous guards.

The Harvester lifted his scythe and parried Vikir’s sword.

Peoeog!

Blood spurted from his chest and limbs, but the weapon had served its purpose.

Flauros had perfected his Space Traveling Magic Circle.

[Come here, my eldest son-]

Flauros smirked and summoned the Harvester.

For some reason, even in the face of defeat and the loss of all his poisonous soldiers, he was smiling broadly.

[Can I ask you a favor?]

[A favor? You to me? What?]

[…It’s about killing a man. If he were alive, he would look like this by now.]

Recalling his past, Flauros exclaimed in a tone of satisfaction, as if he had made a bargain.

[The purpose of coming here has already been achieved! Everyone retreat! Survive on your own!]

Flauros’s shout startled everyone gathered at the water source.

“…!”

Vikir recognized the satisfaction and accomplishment in Flauros’s voice.

And why the master liar had led his entire army to this water source, his true reason and purpose.

‘Oh no!’

Vikir turned his head to see Pigi lying on the ground, bleeding out.

Flauros’s smirking gaze was fixed on Pigi, whose eyes were closed and growing cold.

The demon’s purpose in coming to Tochka was not to kill the demon hunter.

His purpose was to kill Pigi in the first place!

[Demon Hunter, I’ll save the conversation with you for another time, I promise. It won’t be long, and you’ll soon realize that today was only a taste. For my vials of poison are far more than this.]

Flauros shouted, his magic circle glowing brightly.

…But.

“Pigi doesn’t die.”

Vikir’s words were short, as always.

“Only you will die.”

At the same time, eight fierce teeth tore through the circle, tearing at the magic circle.

The attack was fiercer and more vicious than ever.

Vikir’s killing intent and determination made even the mighty Flauros break out in a cold sweat.

[Son, stop that!]

Flauros’ command was immediately heeded by the Harvester.

But.

“…Weren’t we ‘friends’? Trusting each other.”

The Harvester’s entire body stiffened at the sound of Vikir’s voice that followed.

For a moment, a glimpse of his face peeked out from beneath the hood he had cut off.

Vikir stared at him with a gaze that stretched straight ahead.

And it was that momentary hesitation that made all the difference.

…Flash!

The fiercely meshed teeth took a big bite of the light pillar emanating from the magic circle.

[Kkeu-aaaaaag!?]

Flauros screamed in unexpected shock and pain.

At the same time, the magic circle shook violently.

Paas-

Red poisonous smoke and light enveloped Flauros and the Harvester, swallowing them whole.

….

And then a surprising silence descended.

Where the battle had raged so fiercely just moments before, it was now as silent as a tomb.

The demons he had just missed. And the companions who had lost their lives.

The belatedly assembled group was speechless in the face of the devastation.

In the distance, the sounds of the Allied forces slaughtering the remnants of the poisonous soldiers could be heard.

Camus, Aiyen, Dolores, Sinclaire, Kirko, and everyone else stood behind Vikir, saying nothing.

….

And then.

Vikir’s lips moved, heavy as hardened lead.

“The real fight is about to begin.”

Everyone’s faces stiffened as they realized that the real fight hadn’t even begun yet.

A time when greater and more enormous sacrifices will be required.

The final act of this whole stage would soon come.

Chapter 473

Tochka Annihilation Battle (5)

◆

“This time, stick your neck out.”

The voice echoed in his ears, and Flauros turned to reveal his true colors.

A skeletal leopard’s face, a mane of dark flames, and eyes that burned like sulfurous fire.

<‘2nd Corpse’ Flauros>

Danger Rating : S+

Size: ?

Found in: Serpent’s Womb, Deep within the Gate of Destruction

-Also known as ‘Second Corpse’.

One of the Ten Plagues, the natural enemy of mankind, incomprehensible and unkillable.

“I will turn the water into blood.”

– The Ten Commandments 10:Top –

The Second Corpse Flauros. The Lying Leopard.

A being who held the second highest position among the protagonists who led the Age of Destruction.

The prey that Vikir had set as his ultimate goal for this battle was there.

…Flash!

Eight teeth bit into thin air.

[Huh!?]

Flauros jumped back in horror.

With the Original Ouroboros destroyed by Granola, he had no weapon to fight against Beelzebub.

Huuug!

Flauros took a deep breath and released a poisonous fog on an enormous scale.

Red death, an ominous mist that turned the water red, spewed out from Flauros’s mouth.

However.

[Hack hack-]

The Baby Madam that popped out from behind Vikir sucked in all of the red death evil spirit that Flauros spat out with a single inhalation.

[Did you see that damn spider!]

Flauros gritted his teeth and sprayed even more Red Death, but to no avail.

This was because five women appeared on Baby Madam’s back.

“Vikir-nim!”

Camus, Aiyen, Dolores, Sinclaire, and Kirko. Dolores, the foremost of them all, cast a spell over Vikir.

White holy power erupted, burning away the red death.

The priests of the Faithful launched a massive counterattack.

Baby Madam’s descendants also gathered together and began to eat the Red Death.

The Red Death evil spirits that had been rampaging across the battlefield were gradually being consumed by the enemy, the spiders of the Black Mountains, and the priests of Faithful Quovadis.

Without the Original Ouroboros, no more Red Deaths were being produced, and the end was slowly coming.

The water mist cleared, revealing Flauros’s bewildered form beyond.

Vikir is right behind him.

A chance for a stroke of luck was not to be missed.

…Jjeojeog!

The 4th Form, deployed as quickly as possible, sliced deeply into Flauros’s chest.

One could see the beating heart peeking through the smoothly cut ribs.

After that, numerous attacks were launched.

Camus’ fireballs and giant iron skewers, Aiyen’s heavy arrow, Sinclaire’s golden golem, and Kirko’s magic sword, Asmodeus, bombarded Flauros in quick succession.

Flauros’s body tattered in the flames.

On top of that, Vikir’s 8th Form Black Sun had already sealed off every direction Flauros could escape.

Flauros began to grind his teeth as the situation came to this.

[…If it weren’t for that damned Granola, how could he doubt my word?]

Flauros wondered inwardly how Granola could have recognized the lie that was his power.

Vikir, of course, did not feel the need to answer the question. He didn’t even know the answer.

Jjeog- deng-geong!

Both Flauros’s left and right arms were torn off.

Vikir dug his fingers into Flauros’s heart and said.

“I told you not to underestimate this world.”

Every cause and effect he had ever encountered. The totality of organic things.

The gigantic wheel of cause and effect they created would not be easy for even the most powerful demon to deal with.

And here is a pilgrim who has walked the hardest and loneliest thorny path of all, one that has been rolling since the wheel of asceticism was very small.

Vikir. The Regressor. A hound who went through another life in the underworld.

It bites at the nape of its prey’s neck, even beyond the ends of Hell, even beyond the bending of time.

Puugk-

A fountain of blood erupts from Flauros’s neck.

Vikir shoved the Beelzebub into Flauros’ neck and twisted it with all his might.

Wadeudeug!

The sound of tearing through the hard pelt and snapping the tough muscle fibers within.

Furthermore, the heavy, dense bones broke apart, and all the bundles within were ripped out.

Chwaaaag-

By the time Vikir pulled out Beelzebub, Flauros’s neck and body had already been separated.

Flauros, who had completely melted into Hobbes’ flesh after so much time, had to be beheaded before he could even get his spirit body out of his body.

…Thud! Deguldeguldegul-

Flauros’s head rolled on the floor.

A bizarre appearance, with Hobbes’ face and Flauros’ face mixed together.

For a being who had caused both an Imperial civil war and a two dimensional race war, his words were quite hollow.

“….”

Vikir stared at the sliced demon on the battlefield.

Although there were still a large number of poisonous soldiers remaining on the battlefield, they had lost their leader and were dying out on their own.

The ragtag group, stomping each other to death, were like straw men to Marquis de Sade and Major General Orca.

As soon as the Tochka Alliance gained momentum and launched a counterattack, the poisonous soldiers crumbled.

A struggle of all against all. It was the demons’ value of life.

The remnants of the Leviathan’s forces, too, had been forced to do as they were told.

In the language of solitary beings with no concept of kin or companions.

One man with a brain tried to rally the poisonous soldiers, who still constituted the overwhelming majority.

[Bite the troops! After retreating, regroup… kugh!?]

Thomas, the second son of the Leviathan family, rolled on the ground with an arrow in his neck as he led the remaining troops in retreat.

Bianca’s arrow, followed by Tudor spears and Sancho’s axe.

“Pigi’s enemy!”

“I will never forgive you!”

“I will not let one of you go!”

The fall of the Leviathan.

Starting with the death of Hobbes de Leviathan, who was like a symbol, the display of extreme poisonous dark master rapidly collapsed.

The giant poisonous soldiers begin to lose their minds and go on a rampage, and the minions are rapidly weakening.

Vikir looked down upon the scene and realized that the long war was coming to an end.

[…Huhuhu.]

If it weren’t for a muffled mockery from the ground.

Where Vikir turned his head was the head of Flauros.

Like Andromalius before him, Flauros was still alive, with only his head remaining.

But Vikir hadn’t let his guard down.

“Demons kill.”

Always on the edge of action. A hunter always ready.

Flauros spoke in a humorous tone to Vikir, who was immediately raising his killing intent.

[Relax, you can’t kill me anyway].

What nonsense. There’s no point in playing to the opponent’s tongue when the game is already won.

Knowing that one must be careful with demonic tongues, especially Flauros’s, Vikir saw no reason to stop his sword.

But. Flauros’s words that followed were enough to make even a man with steel veins and a furnace heart stop in his tracks.

[The moment you kill me, the ‘Age of Destruction’ will arrive.]

Not one of those gathered here truly knew what the Age of Destruction was.

Except for Vikir.

Flauros continued to click his tongue, knowing that only Vikir would be the one to talk.

[Before battle. I twist my lifeline, the cord of my life, long and tight, and tie it to the rings of the Gate of Destruction. If it were to break, the gates would naturally open].

The Demon World. The Oil World. The Gate to Polar Hell.

Vikir remembered well the day it opened.

The coming destruction, the approaching apocalypse, the sum total of all these terrible things, the world of human and demons.

[Do you think you are the only one who laid a trap for the future? In fact, if that’s the case, this one is one step above.]

“….”

A cold sweat runs down his face. His hands were trembling, even if only slightly.

Flauros is a demon who specializes in deceiving others with lies. Should he believe anything Flauros says now?

…But what if, just what if, this is not a lie?

What if killing him really does open the Gate of Destruction?

Even at this very moment, as Vikir pondered, Flauros was slowly vaporizing his body.

It seemed like he was planning to turn into the red mist of death itself and run away.

[Didn’t I tell you from the beginning that your efforts would be in vain?]

Flauros said with a wide grin.

The smile that was in full bloom was thick with malice that could not be hidden.

Tsutsutsutsuts…

Flauros’s body grew paler and paler.

In just a few seconds, he’ll be completely gone from this place.

Kill him here and now, or let him escape, that was the question.

At a crossroads where neither option was acceptable.

Sereung-

Vikir drew his sword.

To be deceived or not to be deceived.

Now was the time to make a decision.

Chapter 477

Downtown Naval Warfare (1)

◆

Sswaaaaa-

The rain poured down like a torrent.

The world that had been turned into a sea was rippling more and more ferociously.

The people gathered in Tochka gradually became restless.

“Aren’t we going to starve to death here, stuck in this place?”

“What – there’s still plenty of food, isn’t there?”

“But what if this flood continues?”

“It’s only supposed to last 150 days. We have enough food and more water, so it’s okay.”

“But it’s already an ocean outside, and how do we know the flood will stop in 150 days?”

“Well, Donquixote’s eldest son is on his way to pick up the Armada, so that’s why we’re all waiting.”

The rumors among the refugees weren’t false.

In fact, Tochka, in the highlands, is one of the most secure fortresses in the world, and a completely isolated, deserted island.

Is that why? Vikir was still gazing longingly out to sea today.

…Squash!

The waves crashed against the solid walls of the fortress on the high plateau.

The white bubbles that broke the water were like a field of flowers.

“….”

Vikir sat on the ramparts in the pouring rain.

The cold rain pounded against his body, as if cooling hot iron.

Then.

“Raining again today, what a pity.”

A voice came from behind Vikir.

It was Camus.

She walked to Vikir’s side, soaking wet, too.

“It’s pouring like crazy.”

Camus said as she watched the water cascade down the ramparts.

“This would have been a disaster if it weren’t for the sea of ??fire the demons created, but the two plagues have worked together to lessen the damage. I assume this is what you calculated in Nouvelle Vague, before the volcano erupted.”

“Mostly.”

Vikir nodded quietly.

The math wasn’t perfect, but it was close.

But if the margin of error had been a little wider, something really bad would have happened.

“….”

“….”

Vikir and Camus looked in the same direction.

Neither of them said anything for a while.

Finally, it was Camus who spoke first.

“…I’m sorry about your father.”

At that, Vikir, who had been standing motionless, reacted.

At most, his shoulders shook slightly.

The memory of that day is still fresh in his mind.

‘…Why did you do that?’

‘I don’t know.’

The memory fades to white. White ashes. Now scattered in the rain.

Hugo, who had been burned to death, was a hero to everyone in Tochka that day.

But Vikir can’t help but see him as a complicated figure.

“…He.”

Vikir spoke after a long silence.

“I don’t know how he crossed the threshold of the 9th Form.”

It was a far cry from his previous life.

Camus pauses at Vikir’s words.

“Actually….”

“?”

“He came to visit me a long time ago.”

Camus’s testimony came as a surprise to Vikir.

“It was not long after the trial in Nakajaniye, and he wanted to discuss with me a way to get you out of prison. Oh, and by the way, Sadi, I think he and that woman were holding hands back then, too.”

The fact that Sadi and Hugo were holding hands was a bit of a surprise to Vikir.

It seems that Hugo had more in mind for Vikir than he realized.

The process of Cindywendy finding Sadi, who had disappeared, the process by which Aiyen was able to go to Nouvelle Vague to avoid summary execution, and Sadi’s ability to create a false identity and pass through the Gate of Nouvelle Vague.

It was all thanks to a helping hand that was just around the corner.

Vikir’s mind flashed back to the image of Hugo in the courtroom.

-The Baskervilles’ case is as follows. The crimes of rebellion, murder with intent to kill, and poisoning of the patriarch are grave and heinous, but the accused is of Baskerville blood and deserves to be treated as a nobleman. Therefore, we ask for a ruling of mitigating circumstances.

Hugo sits backwards in his wheelchair, having made no objection to the sentence.

“….”

Vikir was speechless.

Camus continued the story.

“When we were talking about helping you escape, the topic of the Wraith Tree came up, and I couldn’t help but mention the Grave of the Swords.”

Camus raised her hand.

Tsutsutsutsutsutsutsuts…

The Wraith Tree waved its long, stubby branches in the air.

“I’m surprised the Wraith Tree reacted to Hugo, he must have read ‘some memory’ from it.”

Vikir nodded silently at Camus’ words.

He had a point.

[There is something to be gained by those who step into the realm of the supreme, and continue to fight with the same heart as when they first held the sword.]

[This is a realm that defies ordinary human understanding, empathy, conviction, faith, common sense, probability, and causality. No being who has not experienced death can ever set foot here.]

[You will probably never attain this realm in your lifetime].

[For the realm of the 9th Form lies at the threshold of death, beyond it].

[If you’re a true Baskerville, you’ll come here at the end of your life].

[You will see it again someday].

What Hugo saw was probably the figure of Cane Corso.

What did he feel in his older brother’s words?

Vikir thought again.

The 6th Form. A state of mind that can only be reached by transcending all emotion.

The 7th Form. A state of mind that can only be attained by reclaiming emotions that have been abandoned.

The 8th Form. A state of mind that can only be attained by fighting through countless devastating battles, just like the first time you held a sword.

The 9th Form. An incomprehensible zone at the core of the highest realms that only those who have experienced death can ascend to.

“….”

What must have been Hugo’s mind as he crossed the threshold.

At the edge of the threshold between life and death, Vikir thought and thought and thought.

At that time.

Thud.

Camus tapped Vikir on the shoulder.

“Don’t try to take it all on yourself. You’ve come all this way, think of the people who care about you.”

“…That’s right.”

And then there was a voice that agreed with Camus.

Dolores. She appeared in front of the wall and offered Vikir her umbrella.

“These people here are all Vikir’s followers, ready to follow him wherever he goes, aren’t they?”

“…That’s true, but don’t I have an umbrella?”

“It’s for two people.”

Ignoring Camus’s grumbling, Dolores continued to speak to Vikir.

“Don’t worry about Tudor. He’s a strong fellow, I’m sure he’ll come back with the Armada.”

At her words, Vikir turned his head back toward the sea.

The storm is raging, the waves are rising, and it seems as if no fleet could sail against it.

Now that they had won the game, it was urgent, but it was a very frustrating and hopeless situation.

“I’m always watching from the watchtower, so you should go inside. I don’t want you to get sick.”

Aiyen, who had suddenly appeared, said to Vikir.

Her superhuman eyesight, capable of seeing for miles, far surpassed Vikir’s, and if Tudor came with his Armada, she would be the first to see him.

“What is it, barbarian? Why do you keep flirting with other people’s men?”

“Barbarian? Do you want to be stripped naked again?”

“Oh, it reminds me of the old days? You think that’s still possible?”

Camus of Morgue and Aiyen of Ballak hadn’t gotten along well then or now.

Then.

“Stop fighting. It’s hard enough on the mind, brother.”

Sinclaire appeared, having finished repairing the walls.

Camus and Aiyen narrowed their eyes at her, but Sinclaire shrugged them off.

She set down a cup of hot tea in front of Vikir and spoke.

“The next battle will be the final one. Why don’t you have a cup of tea to calm your nerves?”

“ …We’re going to the Imperial Castle. I’ve only heard of it in literature.”

Beside Sinclaire was Kirko, who was in charge of security.

Kirko turned to Vikir.

“By the way, does this mean that everyone who lives in the lowlands is dead?”

“We’ve gathered as many people as we can to Tochka to prevent that from happening, and we’ve already relocated those who couldn’t make it here in time and space to other highlands. I think we’ve done all we can.”

Sinclaire answered instead.

They had apparently been having this conversation all the way here.

Just then.

“Huh!?”

Aiyen, who’d been clinging to Vikir’s side, exchanging glances with Camus, jumped to her feet.

Her good eyesight had seen something beyond the darkness and the churning waters of the storm.

Then she cried out.

“They’re here! It’s the Armada!”

She was right.

Soon, through the churning waters and storm, the great ships began to approach.

The large, massive ships ignored the waves and headed straight for the highlands of Tochka.

The number of such ships was countless. Their majesty is truly staggering.

Dolores shouted with joy.

“It’s Tudor! Tudor are back!”

True to her word, the banner of Donquixote fluttered from the foremast at the top of the captain’s ship in front.

There were even a surprisingly large number of people on board.

“It’s true! Tochka didn’t flood!”

“Is there really food there?”

“Alas, there really is salvation! There was a land that was not flooded!”

“I should have believed the words of the Night Walkers then! If only I had….”

Aboard the enormous ships were an equally enormous number of refugees.

And at the stern of the lead ship, two familiar faces appeared.

It was Tudor and Bianca.

“Vikir, I apologize for being later than promised, it’s disgraceful!”

“We’re late because this idiot came by and said we had to save all the people stranded in the highlands!”

The two were still bickering even at this emotional moment.

Camus, Aiyen, Dolores, Sinclaire, and Kirko looked at the many other refugees coming to Tochka with concern.

“We’ll have less food if we let them in, won’t we?”

“Hmm, and there might be new security problems.”

“It’s okay, they said we have enough food, and the security is manageable with the addition of the Nouvelle Vague team.”

“Five months, maybe. We’ve spent all our family’s assets.”

“I’m all for seeking justice, but I don’t want anything to get in the way of the final battle.”

Then.

“It doesn’t matter. I have to leave here soon anyway.”

Vikir finally stood up.

“It’s time for the final round.”

Everyone’s faces hardened.

They, too, understood what Vikir was saying.

Soon, the final battle would be fought on the Imperial Capital.

The final hour was approaching.

◆

The number and variety of ships Tudor brought with him was staggering.

The longships, with their small hulls and shallow draft, allowed for small, fast maneuvers; the Carvi, with 13 rows of oars and 26 oarsmen; the Sneka, with 20 rows of oars and 40 oarsmen; the Skade, with a capacity of one hundred combatants; the Draka, with over a thousand combatants; and so on.

What’s more, the crews of these vessels are veterans of Donquixote’s vast expeditions, who know how to navigate the vast expanse of the open sea.

Not only did they possess tremendous navigational skills as they navigated the North Sea, where drift ice was floating, but they also had the courage and fortitude to rush to the center of the empire, which became the sea.

Chwaaaag- Squash!

Countless ships cut through the rough seas.

The Baskerville, the Marg, the Quovadis, the Bourgeois, and even the survivors of the Donquixote and Usher families.

What’s more, the Colosseo Academy, the Themiscyra Women’s College, the Varangian Boot Camp, and the Magic Tower are all in attendance.

Prominent figures such as Osiris, the Seven Counts, Raspane, Adolf, Pope Nabokov I, Cardinal Luther, Archbishop Mozgus, Damian, and Principal Banshee were all standing at the forefront.

And in addition to that, everyone who has been in a relationship so far gathers in one place and fires up their will to fight.

The Allied Forces of Tochka went to the Imperial Capital aboard Donquixote’s ship.

Going inward, further inward, tracing the map of the Imperial Capital, which has now been transformed into a sea chart.

Meanwhile.

“….”

Aboard the lead ship, Vikir stood at the stern, gazing out at the endless horizon.

Cheolgeuleog-

Every time the ship rocks from side to side, you can hear the sound of the chains wrapped around Vikir’s hands scraping on the deck.

Beside him, MiniPin and Chihuahua look worried.

“Oh no, Deputy, there’s over there…!”

Vikir turned his gaze in the direction Chihuahua was pointing.

A giant shadow streaked across the water beside the ship.

An enormous sea monster of some unknown nature could be seen passing beneath the water.

It’s a species that, by definition, shouldn’t live here.

‘I can see how the Imperial Capital must have changed.’

Where the emperor lives. No, now the crown prince lives here.

I can only imagine what the submerged place must look like now.

In the center of the empire, on the Impeial Capital, the last stand would be made. The 1st Corpse the protagonist who led the Age of Destruction.

And the end of the many lives Vikir has crossed.

The revenge of his fallen comrades was slowly coming to an end.

Whiiiiing-

A strong sea breeze blew and inflated the sails.

The ship began to fly over the waves.

Cheolgeuleog-

The sound of chains scraping the deck again.

Vikir tightened his grip on the chain in his hand.

MiniPin, beside him, turned to the end of the chain and stammered a question.

“Uh, by the way, Deputy. I’ve been wondering before… what is that?”

He didn’t ask because he didn’t really know what the thing at the end of the chain was.

It was a coffin.

What Vikir was carrying was a large, heavy coffin.

No telling who was inside.

Chapter 480

Downtown Naval Warfare (4)

◆

Who says that the first life came from the sea?

In this worldview dominated by creationism by God, few would agree with the above proposition.

However, many people agree with the statement that the last life perishes in the sea.

…Kwakwang!

The final battle against the demon began with a naval battle.

The black swirling sea, the storm blowing like crazy, the pillars of fire rising up as they break the sea surface, and the monsters of the deep sea baring their teeth.

Donquixote’s Invincible Armada and the Tochka Alliance are engaged in an all-out war against the demon’s minions.

The location is the highest center of the empire, the ‘Empire Capital’.

The city, once a gathering place for all cultures and fashions, where the richest and most sophisticated walked with graceful strides, was now in the midst of a fierce naval battle with tidal waves, winds, and torrential rains.

And in the midst of all this great chaos, there was one great chaos, the biggest, heaviest, and most vast of all.

A monster that appears most often in sailors’ epics.

A terror that no one has ever seen, but everyone has heard of.

An unknown being that can pull an island into the deep sea with each of its eight legs.

<Kraken>

Danger Rating: S+

Size: ?

Found in the deepest part of the Lower Sea

-Also known as the “Great King of the Deep Sea” or “Antagonist of Nouvelle Vague.”

One of the two monsters born with light and darkness at the creation of the world.

It is by far the best among the various strange creatures that frequently appear in sailors’ epics.

It lies alone at the bottom of the ocean floor, too cold and dark for anything to live, but once it begins to move, it changes the landscape of the six oceans.

No one knows why this terrifying creature, which belongs in the depths of hell, is living in the oceans of the human realm.

Huge and round, its head resembles a rocky island from a distance, with countless attached oysters, barnacles, and seaweed.

Eight tentacles, each one a tributary of a mountain range.

Two enormous, circular eyeballs burn a fiery yellow as they feed on the darkness of the great deep.

Kraken.

One of the two monstrous creatures that resulted from the separation of darkness and light in the creation of the world.

A great king who rules the entire deep sea.

Another name for the kraken is ‘the Antagonist of Nouvelle Vague’.

Eudeug-

Orca gritted his teeth.

Kwakwakwakwang!

He swung his club with all his might, meeting the Kraken’s tentacles as they fell toward the ship.

Not even the mightiest Orca could fully defend against the Kraken’s tentacles.

Even the barrage of artillery from the Knights of Usher pales in comparison to the Kraken’s overwhelming size and defense.

How long had it been deposited over time?

The Kraken charged, tens, hundreds, thousands, tens of thousands of layers of armor of oyster shells, barnacles, and coral shells encasing its entire body.

Peopeopeopeong!

A hole opened up in the Usher family’s fire net, and countless monsters began to pour in.

As they tore through the netting of the bombardment, they tore holes in the ship’s sole or clung to the railings to pull themselves up onto the deck.

Several ships in the Invincible Armada were already showing signs of sinking.

But the Allies were no slouches either.

D’Ordume, Souaré, BDISSEM, and Flubber stepped forward.

“Leave it to us. That’s a demon of the deep who used to raid our Nouvelle Vague regularly, and he owes us a debt of gratitude.”

“We’ve fought him a few times before. See that scar over his eyeball? I made it for him about ten years ago.”

“My God, I never thought I’d see you here again.”

[…! …! …!]

D’Ordume created a whirlwind of strikes and began scraping the oyster shells and barnacles off the Kraken’s body.

Waggigigigigig-

The thick, carapace-like armor of the Kraken’s body, seemingly made of time itself, is sliced away by the axe blade.

The living ones shattered with a burst of fluid, and the dead corals beneath them crumbled lightly.

Souaré, too, drew on her dwarven strength.

She lifted the skyscrapers from the bottom of the Imperial Capital, now a sea, and stabbed the Kraken at the base of its body with a spear of earth and stone.

Peopeopeopeopeog!

The Kraken let out a dull roar beneath the water.

BDISSEM took advantage, wrapping countless chains of seaweed around the Kraken’s body.

Flubber, too, spread out, covering and dissolving parts of the Kraken’s body.

O-ooooo-

The sound of a boat horn coming from under the sea.

This must be the roar of the Kraken in pain.

The water boiled over, and an earthquake began to rage.

…Peoeog!

Vikir sliced through one of the tentacles falling toward the ship with a single blow.

Black blood splashed, leaving a cold, sickly taste in his mouth.

Just then.

“My friend, now!”

Tudor shouted from behind him.

Vikir turned his head to see a ship, driven by Tudor himself.

A ship with a large, pointed spear at its head was charging furiously towards the Kraken.

Kwakwang!

Tudor’s small fleet had managed to sever one of the Kraken’s tentacles.

It was a feat not even the mighty Orca or Sade could accomplish.

Tudor turned to Vikir and shouted.

“We’ll take care of this gatekeeper on our own lines, you go forward!”

“….”

Vikir watched Tudor’s face as he did so.

He’d been a mere little chick when they’d met at the Academy, but he’d risen to hero status in recent years.

Seeing him now commanding so many ships against the Kraken made him realize that he no longer needed to worry.

With a little more time, he could be as great a hero as Tudor was before his regression, or even greater.

For in this life, he survived, not died.

And Sancho and Bianca’s presence alongside Tudor only strengthened Vikir’s conviction.

“Vikir, I need you to follow me!”

“You said there’s no time! We’ll do something about it!”

Finally, Tudor closed the conversation with a tremendous shout.

“My friend! Go and become a myth!”

At the same time, the Invincible Armada and the Kraken engage in another ferocious battle.

The sky and the waters are turned upside down in a frenzy of thunder and fire, tidal waves, and earthquakes.

Morgue’s magic, Quovadis’ holy shields, and Bourgeois’ supplies continue to burst forth.

The hounds of Baskerville were also tearing at the Kraken’s massive body with all their might.

Soon, Vikir is in a small carved boat.

He plans to sneak through the gap in the Kraken’s line of sight and march on the palace.

Then.

Chwa-ag!

The Kraken’s body suddenly flipped over.

One of its giant eyeballs turned toward Vikir.

In addition to its two visible eyeballs, the Kraken had hidden a third giant eyeball in its tail!

Kugugugugugugu-

Then, eight legs stepped back from the front and faced Vikir.

The severed and charred legs swung wildly at Vikir, aiming for him as they were.

“…!”

Vikir gritted his teeth and drew his sword.

Kwakwakwakwakwakwakwang!

The surface of the water behind Vikir shattered with a loud crash.

Octagon(八脚). Eight legs.

Eight gigantic legs jutted out from the sea floor, blocking the Kraken’s tentacles.

[Kaaaah!]

Baby Madam. How had she gotten this far?

Leaving her children behind, she followed Vikir alone, and, stepping over the Clock Tower of the Imperial Capital, where they had once glided together, she drew out her eight legs.

Peopeopeopeopeopeog!

As soon as she emerges from the water, she stamps down on the Kraken’s legs.

The Kraken was very surprised to see another creature as large as him, let alone the venom spreading through his body.

Suddenly, as he struggled with the Madam, another barrage of Allied artillery began to rain down on his back.

Oo-oooooo!

The Kraken was forced to turn around again.

Naturally, Vikir was out of the way.

“…Thank you.”

The first words out of Vikir’s mouth were his first acknowledgment of indebtedness.

His friends, who would have been jumping around in joy if they had heard those words, didn’t actually hear them.

Next thing you know, Vikir’s boat is racing furiously downwind, fueled by the southeast wind.

The wind was strong enough to snap the masts, and the small craft sped along at the speed of an arrow.

And then.

Kung!

Vikir’s boat, riding the high waves, crashed into the solid steps and shattered.

Vikir leaped onto the deck and landed on the steps before the boat broke apart.

A golden staircase so high it seemed to reach the sky.

Though it had been flooded by the sea halfway up, it still stood tall and majestic.

Above it was an imperial castle that was usually hidden by clouds and was not visible.

Teog-

Vikir stepped onto the stairs leading to the imperial palace.

…Drrrr!

The sound of a coffin being dragged on chains.

Vikir climbed the stairs, dragging a coffin.

…And Kirko, seeing Vikir’s backside shrinking in the distance, scratched his head in desperation.

“What is that coffin? Who’s inside?”

“Come to think of it, I think he’s been carrying that coffin since he came out of Tochka.”

It was Sinclaire who answered the question.

Dolores spoke up in a tone that suggested she was puzzled as well.

“I was wondering the same thing last night.”

“Mmm. Me, too. So he said it’s the souls of all his dead comrades?”

Aiyen nodded in agreement.

Then, for the last time, Camus’ eyes narrowed.

“Hmmm. I have a bad feeling about this.”

If a great mage of Camus’ caliber had a bad feeling, it was a bad one.

Aiyen, Dolores, Sinclaire, and Kirko’s gazes were demanding to know why.

Finally, Camus opened her mouth to answer their questions.

“…I guess it’s my feelings as a woman?”

Chapter 484

The Marquis of Discord (4)

◆

[The realm of the 9th Form lies beyond the threshold of death…]

A voice crackled into the distance.

The realm of the Supreme glimpsed in the briefest of moments, left a mark on his retina.

As a result of drawing the scenery there in the air like a hand-drawn ink painting, nine teeth were created, which was said to be absolutely impossible in life.

The trajectory of a cluster of living stars.

…Flash!

The Baskerville 9th Form was revealed.

[Keuhag!?]

Blood spurts from Andras’s mouth.

The nine teeth that tore through the boundary between life and death instantly tore Andras’ body into tatters.

Vikir stood still, a dazed expression on his face.

At first glance, it seemed like he was just standing there, mesmerized.

But Andras’s eyes showed something else entirely.

Ku-ooooo!

A crimson aura rises with terrifying momentum.

A dog of death with a black body, bright red eyes, and an open mouth.

[…Yes, I’ve seen death a few times, so maybe it’s possible to cross the line between life and death alive, but I never thought I’d get there].

Andras muttered in surprise.

But there was still an odd ease in his hand as he drew the sword at his waist.

Gurgling!

Flames roared up the hilt of the sword, which looked like it had been molded from volcanic ash mixed with water.

Kazanbai, one of the Seven Demon Swords, crashed down on Vikir’s head.

Beelzebub parries the vertical fire strike, deflects it, and immediately strikes back.

…Kkaang! Ttang! Kkang! Kwagigigigigig-

Countless sparks of fire and shards of aura scatter in all directions.

‘Good thing there’s only one sword.’

Vikir thought as he parried Andras’s sword.

Andras, who had originally carried two swords, Kazanbai and Asmodeus, before his regression, now wielded a single sword.

It was much easier to deal with a master of dual-wielding when he only wielded one sword.

[Tch. Is it still difficult with a divided body? We have to become one properly…]

Andras rolled his eyes and adjusted his stance.

Vikir exuded a crimson aura and gathered all nine teeth into one place.

…Kurrrrrrr!

Black Sun. The star grew even heavier and more massive.

A black, enormous sphere of destruction that sucked everything in its path into its center and crushed it from within.

Andras chuckled in disbelief.

[Awakening at the last moment in the final battle and fighting the final boss one-on-one, isn’t that a cliché?]

“Stories sell for a reason.”

[…That’s true.]

At the same time, a dull noise erupted.

Andras’s face was sliced horizontally, leaving only his mouth.

Kurrrrr!

Vikir’s sword bent at an odd angle in midair and returned.

Andras regenerated his face in an instant, then spread his wings and fell backward.

Kwakwakwakwakwakwang!

In the blink of an eye, dozens of blows were exchanged.

…Flash!

Andras unleashed a thousand flames, melting the surrounding golden pillars.

Vikir swung his strike through the dripping ceiling and pillars.

Andras also struck down his flaming sword and confronted Vikir.

In what seemed to be the final battle, Vikir suddenly felt someone standing behind him.

The same warmth he’d felt on the battlefields of Tochka.

A comfort he didn’t want to admit.

Then, a small voice echoed in Vikir’s ear.

‘You’ve grown up.’

The voice sounded so clear like it was right next to him.

At the memory, Vikir felt an unexplained emotion welling up in his chest.

This intense, vomit-like emotion was directed at his father, Hugo.

It was something he’d spent his entire life, through two lifetimes, denying, suppressing, and eradicating.

And it burst out like an explosion, carrying the aura of the tip of the sword.

…Kwakwakwakwakwakwang!

A straight line is formed by the movement of a huge, swirling black sun.

Black Lightning.

It soon splits into nine trajectories, each stretching forward.

Nine teeth, each piercing, grasping, tearing, cutting, slicing, dismembering, crushing, mincing, and mashing.

The perfection of Baskerville’s swordsmanship tore the world apart.

In the Grave of Swords, Cane Corso’s demonstration of ‘The Ultimate Level of Killing Intent’ unfolds.

It is a level of swordsmanship unheard of even in the Age of Destruction.

Even for Andras, the pinnacle of predators, this was his first time experiencing it.

[What kind of nonsense…!?]

A slash that goes beyond eight directions and tears through all nine directions.

Andras struggled in the midst of the torrent that crushed his entire body.

But the outcome had already been decided.

The winds whipped around and the fragments of his aura were oxidized with intense flames.

…Ppajig!

The sword broke.

Kazanbai, one of the Seven Demon Swords, was burning bright red and crumbling to pieces.

Andras’s body was the same way.

Lava boiled from cracks all over his body.

His wings were tattered, and his two eye sockets were blackened and withered.

Vikir realized it was all over.

Though it had taken all of his strength, he had gotten what he wanted.

Once and for all, the life of Andras, the Marquis of Discord.

…Thud!

At last, the last enemy, Andras, fell to his knees.

Vikir held out his magic sword, Beelzebub, for the final word.

“Demon kill.”

The immutable logic of death and rebirth.

The ideology of demon hunters can be said to be dogma itself.

…However, there was one more absolute thing that did not change.

[I can’t help it].

That is the malice of demons toward humans.

It’s like that smile on Andras’s face at the end, even though he’s exhausted all his power.

[What did they say about stories that sell for a reason?]

Andras’s blackened, dying eyes once again emanated a darkness that was almost unbearable.

[…I couldn’t agree more].

Even Vikir could not help but pause at the strange composure of Andras, who was showing signs of extinction.

[The protagonist awakens at the last moment and faces the final boss in a one-on-one fight. In the end, the protagonist overcomes through the power of love and friendship. The villain’s final struggle must also be present, right? True despair].

“The concept of emptiness does not work.”

[Huhuhu- I don’t play such shallow tricks].

The ominous darkness emanating from Andras’s eyes grew darker and darker.

Suddenly, Vikir saw Andras’ current form overlaid with a memory from the past.

It was the last of Andrealphus the 3rd Corpse, and Flauros the 2nd Corpse.

Both of the demons he had slain before had been willing to pay with their lives to open the Gate of Destruction.

At a heavy price, of course.

Not so, Andras said.

[I, too, have no choice but to open the Gate of Destruction with my own magic and life.]

“Enough of this nonsense. I know that the Gate of Destruction can only be opened once.”

There is already information obtained from Seere and Decarabia.

The Gate of Destruction can only be opened once in this life, even by the most powerful demons.

Since Flauros has already failed to open and maintain the Gate of Destruction this time, there is no way the Gate of Destruction can be opened in this world anymore.

“I’m sorry, but the Gate of Destruction has already been opened by Flauros, and he has failed to keep it open, because of this torrential rain and the great flood that is now falling.”

[Oh, so that was you? I thought it was just bad luck that the great “last remaining dragon” was awakening at that time…]

“Once the gate is closed, it’s closed, and now it can never be opened again. No matter what sacrifices you make.”

Andras smirked at Vikir’s declaration.

[…Well, is that true?]

Andras laughed bitterly. And he continued speaking in a relaxed tone.

[I’m afraid I’m the one who’s sorry. There’s one more Gate of Destruction, and it’s already wide open.]

“…!”

Vikir’s eyes widened.

Then Decarabia, who was hanging on Vikir’s chest, shouted.

[It’s ugly, Andras. To prolong your life with such lies. There is only one Gate of Destruction. How can you say that you can create two when it takes the combined mana of ten demon-king demons to create one in the first place!]

[Hahahaha- What is it, Decarabia? You’re acting funny, but I’m not lying, another Gate of Destruction is already open.]

Andras burst out laughing.

[No, not just one! I can open more than a hundred!]

At the same time.

Andras gathered his last remaining mana and summoned black magic circles around him one after another.

Kiiiiiiiing-!

Dozens of dark portals drew in the air.

All of them were magic circles that didn’t require much mana.

However.

“…!”

In an instant, Vikir’s expression stiffened.

[You. I called you].

Vikir’s mind flashed back to the conversation he’d had with Andras when they’d first met.

[It was I who brought you back.]

What Andras summoned was not a portal to polar hell.

‘Oh no!’

A world line where the door to Polar Hell is already open.

It was a portal to the world where Vikir originally lived before regressing.

Chapter 485

The Marquis of Discord (5)

◆

The river of blood has finally dried up.

The decades-long war between the human and demon realms has been recorded in the history books as the Age of Destruction.

And the day the human world’s victory was carved into stone.

A head was hung on the main gate of Baskerville House, a house known for its Iron-Blooded Swordsmen.

<Name: Vikir Van Baskerville>

<Crime: Internal Communication>

Vikir. ‘Vikir van Baskerville’.

The illegitimate son of Hugo Le Baskerville, the patriarch of House Baskerville.

A shadowy figure with countless blood on his hands for years behind the scenes.

The hound of the House of Baskerville.

◆

….

A severed head is speechless.

The world in which the dog’s neck hung was still suffering from the aftermath of the war.

The Imperial Capital was destroyed in half.

Le Rouge Et Le Noir Mountain were devastated by fire and water.

The Colosseo Academy is in ruins.

Dozens, perhaps hundreds, of Hell Tree that soared into the sky.

Leviathan, Donquixote, and Usher, are still shrouded in Red Death.

Baskerville, where only smoke rises.

The fallen Quovadis.

The fallen Bourgeois.

Morgue, struggling alone.

In Tochka, dead bodies dried up due to the depletion of drinking water.

Broken angel statue.

A crumbling clock tower.

The Nouvelle Vague vanished without a trace….

How can he forget such familiar scenes!

How can he forget this wasteland, reddened with the blood of so many fallen comrades…!

“…! …! …!”

Vikir shuddered as if struck by lightning.

Indeed.

Andras had not opened the Gate of Destruction.

However, it was no different from opening the Gate of Destruction.

A world beyond where the Gate of Destruction is already open.

The world that Vikir lived and died in before he regressed.

The portals to it have been thrown wide open!

[Huhuhuhu- A world line where the Gate to Destruction is already open. It’s the gate leading to that place.]

This wasn’t just Andras’s ability alone.

Emperor’s blood.

Golding Gerald, the first Emperor of Rock, the great empire that united the continents, was said to have the ability to see the future.

The first crown prince of the Golding family, who inherited the bloodline of the first emperor, also possessed the power inherent in his blood.

The combination of his host’s ability to foresee the future and his own ability to open a gate gave Andras the ability to jump through time and open a gate to the past or future.

In other words, he has the power to interfere in parallel worlds.

While this ability was quite limited in many ways, it was still a tremendous power.

Unlike the other Ten Corpses, Andras chose a host with the most power he could muster.

The result was that Vikir was standing here now.

Andras smirked.

[Are you finally willing to make a deal? Tell me who my brother is and where he is now, and I’ll spare you the worst of it].

“….”

[You’re not planning on destroying this world either, are you? Are you planning to bring only misfortune wherever you go? Isn’t it necessary to protect at least one of the world?]

“….”

Vikir frowned.

The original world where he had died.

The Gate of Destruction has already been opened, and the destruction of polar hell has descended.

Tsutsutsutsutsutsuts…

There was a bridge between that world and the current one.

It was only a bridge, but it was still indirectly connected to Hell.

The rains of fire will flood.

Countless demons would cross over.

It was clear that countless human beings would perish once again.

However.

“…In the last life, humans were victorious. In any case, the Age of Destruction is over.”

Yes.

Although 99% of humanity perished, and Vikir himself was executed at the end of the story in a plot left by the demon, … humanity was not wiped out as a result.

The Great Flood came later, ending the rainy season of fear.

All of the Ten Corpses were either dead or disappeared with their magic power wasted.

The thousand fires that lit the world were extinguished, and the remnants of the monsters were hunted down.

Everything must be righted.

All the vile things that crossed the Gate of Destruction eventually vanished.

As a result, the humans, once as numerous as grains of sand on a white beach, were reduced to a handful, but a victory was a victory nonetheless.

“So, even if you created a portal to the other world, there are no flames and monsters to cross over.”

Vikir said through clenched teeth.

Before the regression, humanity avoided the apocalypse thanks to the sacrifices of countless heroes.

It was a vision he saw clearly before his throat was cut.

But Andras merely laughed in disbelief.

[Do you really think so?]

“…What?”

[Do you really think the destruction is over and you humans have won?]

Andras goes beyond ridicule and bursts into laughter.

And underneath that unpleasant smile, there was a hint of composure and malice that could not be hidden.

Soon, several more portals opened around him.

Tsutsutsutsutsutsutsutsutsuts…

A portal with an eerie aura.

A mirror-like transparent membrane appeared in the darkness.

The world beyond the portal became a little more visible.

A wider land and a higher sky came into view.

A moment.

“…!?”

Vikir’s eyes widened in shock and disbelief.

His pupils fluttered as he saw a world he didn’t recognize.

After Vikir was executed, the world was becoming more and more cruel.

He sees a great fire rising from the plateau where the surviving humans had gathered.

The roar of giant monsters that were thought to be extinct can be heard.

Centipedes wrapping themselves around mountains, cephalopods as large as islands rising from the sea, giants tearing through the earth, birds so large they cover the sky, and various ferocious monsters racing across the land.

And there were demons, some of them seemingly powerful, leading hordes of monsters on a rampage.

The deserts of the east were turned into muddy pools of human blood.

Storms were blowing, strong enough to turn the jungles of the west into a wasteland.

The seas to the south have been turned to rotten water by a virulent plague.

A tsunami of flame so hot that it turned the snowy fields of the north into lava fields.

The demons and monsters that rampaged in hordes were more numerous and far more vicious than any of Vikir’s most desperate times.

O-ooooooooo…

All that could be heard were cries of rage, sorrow, and agony.

The few remaining humans were fighting back desperately, but it was clear that they would not last long.

“Oh, how can this happen? Surely I died after seeing the victory of the Human Alliance…!?”

It was rare for Vikir to panic.

Especially since he’d regressed.

But what was happening now would surely surprise even a seasoned veteran who had crossed so many lines of fire.

“This is ridiculous. Is that really the world I used to live in?”

Vikir’s pupils trembled.

The world in front of him was indeed his original world.

This was the intuition of a superhuman.

A terrifying sight that far surpassed all the horrors Vikir had seen and heard before his return.

A sight so horrifying that even a Regressor who had lived through the Age of Destruction would be appalled.

-We’re down! More demons are coming!

-Annihilation! This is annihilation!

-This is… impossible!

-How much longer do we have to fight!

-Kill me! Just kill me!

-I’d rather have been there when the Gate of Destruction first appeared.

-The heroes are all dead!

-…It’s over, it’s the real end of the world.

.

.

Countless people were dying.

The situation has gotten so bad that even the great heroes of the Age of Destruction, the great heroes who fought alongside Vikir, are dying like garbage.

The monsters that burst forth from the Gate of Destruction, and the Ten Corpses who led them, had been little more than a ‘tutorial’.

Vikir doubted twice or thrice that Andras was showing some kind of illusion.

[…Human. That’s not an illusion or brainwashing, it’s real].

It’s not a lie, since the same thing is being seen through the eyes of the demon Decarabia.

What they were seeing through the portal was clearly the world after Vikir’s execution.

Andras clutched his gaping stomach in disbelief.

[What did I tell you earlier, that the world was much more stable after your death? If I were to be honest, that was a lie.]

“You can’t do that! I surely died watching all ten of them lose!”

[You saw it well, It’s true that we failed. In any case, it is ‘us’.]

“…!?”

Andras chuckled.

[As long as the ‘Gate of Destruction’ remains, the demons will be able to rebuild their power, do you know why?]

Andras’s words were followed by an unbelievable statement.

[Because we Ten Corpses are only the ‘weakest’ among the Demon Lords.]

Obvious story.

A common cliché.

…But there is a reason why those things work.

That’s because the obvious and common things reflect reality best.

And then, beyond the many portals, giant shadows are revealed.

Tsutsutsutsutsutsutsutsutsutsutsu…

The shadows were so huge, so vast, that as if the world beyond wasn’t dark enough, they stretched beyond the portals into the world here.

Andras said.

[I am Andras. ‘Marquis of Discord’. And a demon of the Bottom Seats ranked only 63rd in the 72 ranks…. Do you understand what this means?]

With a smile that tore the corners of his mouth past the base of his ears and up to the crown of his head.

[It means that beyond that Gate of Destruction, there are 62 demons stronger than me].

Chapter 486

The Marquis of Discord (6)

◆

[Beyond that Gate of Destruction, there are sixty-two demons stronger than me.]

The impact hitting the back of the head instantly turns his vision into a dizzying darkness.

Vikir could tell Andras’s words were mocking, but not untrue.

“…! …! …! …!”

Vikir could feel the malicious gazes from all sides of the portal now, cutting into his skin in real-time.

His skin burned as if it had been under a magnifying glass for a long time, the unpleasant sensation of countless worms burrowing deep into his insides, and the feeling of being watched by countless eyes.

He could feel the other 62 great evils watching him.

The gazes from beyond the wall of searing black flames were like thick spears, piercing into his body and soul.

If it were a normal person, just receiving one of these gazes would have been enough to make them vomit blood and die.

Tsutsutsutsutsutsutsu…

Vikir watched as gigantic shadows were cast beyond the dozens of portals Andras had created.

The nebula-eating serpent, the leader of the insects, the king of the vampires, the scorpion that spewed dark venom, the woman who was beautiful on the outside but no one could tell what was inside, the desert-eating monkfish, the lord of all things rotten, the centipede that scales mountains, the one who walks beneath the sea, the giant that tears up the earth, the fire-drinking lion, the bird with wings that covers the sky, the executioner of the graveyard, the corpse that lies rotting in the swamp, the tentacles that burrow deep, and so on….

Things with all sorts of sinister names were showing interest in this world.

They salivate and turn to look this way.

A world where the Gate of Destruction has not yet been opened, where there is still so much to destroy and ruin!

Vikir gritted his teeth.

…!

Some of the great shadows cast beyond the portal have already noticed the presence of this world.

And some of the more vile among them were preparing to cross over.

Gazes that convey a huge malice and an intense desire for destruction that have never been felt before, even in the Age of Destruction.

Andras chuckled.

[The 62 Demons of the Otherworld are absolutes that not even I can stand against, and among them are noble ones that I dare not even fathom, whose shadows on the ground cannot even be kissed.]

“….”

Vikir looked out over the great portal at the forefront.

A single shadow loomed over the army of demons.

It emanated a nostril-bursting stench.

The name ‘Baal’ can be seen written on the flag in the language of a long-extinct demonic sovereign.

The shadow of evil it cast was thicker, darker, and more ominous than any other.

‘…You seem stronger and more evil than all Ten Corpses I’ve ever faced combined.’

Even Decarabia, hanging from his chest, trembled.

[This is the ‘Mother of Destruction’, the mother of the 72 demons. When she crosses over, it will be the end of all things, the end of this world. She is the one and the all, the all and the one. ….]

Vikir suddenly realized the meaning of Decarabia’s words.

[Are you confident, then, that you can bear the wrath of your own people, that you can take the wrath of one who is ‘one and all’, who is ‘all and one’, with your whole body?]

[…The answer will be kept secret forever by covenant.]

A line of dialog between Belial and Decarabia during the battle at Bourgeois.

It was a warning to the remaining 62 demons beyond the portal, perhaps preparing for reinforcements after the Age of Destruction.

Andras spoke.

[The construction of the Gate of Destruction. It is the building of a bridge over which the 72 demons of Polar Hell will cross with the armies they have recruited from their respective realms, and our row of bottom seats is the Pilot, who has crossed over to do just that].

“….”

[You thought the war was over after you died, but you were sorely mistaken. We on the other side of the world line have just finished our work and fallen back. Now the remaining humans in that world are facing their true destruction against the remaining 62 demons. You should be glad you died before then and were brought to me.]

Andras looked at Vikir.

Then he opened his mouth, emanating darkness and a foul smell from his eyes.

[It is not too late. If you tell me who and where my brother is, I can close this door now. I don’t want to send upward what I can finish in my line. World interference is complicated enough.]

“…”

[I know it’s not your world, but don’t you think this one is nicer to you now, and do you want it to be destroyed like that one, which is wrong anyway?]

Andras conjured numerous illusions into the dark mists of his own creation.

Sssssssssssssssssssss-

It depicted all the people Vikir had met and all the connections he had made since his regression.

‘Don’t try to take it all on yourself. You’ve come all this way, think of the people who care about you.’

‘All these people here are following you, Vikir, and they’re ready to follow you wherever you go, right?’

‘You shouldn’t go inside because I’m always watching you. I don’t want you to get sick.’

‘Stop fighting. My brother, I’m already feeling very disturbed.’

‘…Are you going to the Imperial Castle? I’ve only encountered it in literature.’

The voices in his head are as vivid as if they were right next to him.

Camus has always been by his side.

Dolores, who has been supporting him without making a sound.

Aiyen, who not only saved his life but also crossed life and death with him many times.

Sinclaire, who chose to stay by Vikir’s side despite her own conflicts and worries.

Kirko, who turned his back on her homeland and followed Vikir into the terrible war ahead.

That’s not all.

Colleagues that he met in the jungle of ??Le Rouge Et Le Noir Mountain.

Friends from the Colosseo Academy.

Ties made in Nouvelle Vague.

The triplets Highbro, Middlebro, and Lowbro, who met in Baskerville as enemies and became trusted allies.

Osiris, the eldest son, who was always distant and cold, but now seems like an older brother who is not good at expressing his emotions.

The Seven Counts, now bonded in their own way.

…And Vikir’s feelings for Hugo that he still can’t explain.

And the countless other faces that stare back at him.

The darkness of his vision swells. The visions surrounded Vikir, animated as if they were within reach.

[Now, you have no other choice, if you wish to close the portal, accept my offer.]

Andras continues to wiggle his tongue, knowing full well that Vikir is in no position to defeat them.

But. Vikir is not swayed at all.

“I could kill you and close that door.”

[Are you still dreaming? The portal I have created cannot be closed by anyone but me! It is not like the Gate of Destruction! Have you seen the holes in your clothes close themselves? When I die, this portal will remain open forever!]

Andras continued to urge Vikir on as if he were full of energy.

But Vikir’s demeanor remained steadfast.

“I don’t make deals with demons. I only kill them.”

[You’re insane. Do you really have no intention of closing this portal?]

Andras’s threats were becoming more and more tangible.

The ends of the 62 shadows slowly falling beyond the portal converge toward Vikir.

But despite this, Vikir maintains his unwavering demeanor.

“No. I can close it.”

Andras was about to scream at the top of his lungs.

…Just then.

Andras, who was just about to say, ‘What can you do!’, could only squeak out the sound of the escaping wind.

Puug-

A sword pierces through his chest.

The sword pierced through his back and exited his chest, the back edge of the sword piercing right through Andras’ heart, which was pulsing with mana from the portal.

[…?]

Andras’s face instantly changed to that of the First Prince, Jack Merrydue.

Kkigigig-

His head spins slowly, ticking like a rusty clockwork.

The landscape behind him comes into view.

There was a heavy coffin attached to an iron chain.

Vikir had been carrying it on his shoulder ever since he entered the palace, ever since he sailed from Tochka.

The coffin lid, heavy with the sense of duty, guilt, anger, and hatred for the demons that the old demon hunter had carried in his heart all his life, was now wide open.

And the being that lay within was now driving a sword into Andras’s back.

The crown prince’s eyes widened as he recognized the face.

The owner of the hand that held the sword hilt.

He was Pigi.

Just Pigi, with no last name.

An inferior student at the academy, a frail friend who had always followed Vikir.

But somehow, the brilliance that radiated from his eyes right now was enough to overwhelm Andras, who stared back.

Andras stammered into the crown prince’s mouth.

[Golding… Golding Ralph. Golding Pigi Ralph And… No, Andras!]

The Second Crown Prince, is one of the two branches of the Imperial bloodline.

At the same time, the first of the Ten Corpses, another heteromorphic Andras and a heteromorphic Andras stood there.

First Crown Prince and Second Crown Prince And the beings of this type gathered in one place.

<‘First Corpse’ Andras>

Danger Rating : S+

Size: ?

Found in: Serpent’s Womb, Deep Within the Gate of Destruction.

-Nicknamed ‘The First Corpse’.

One of the Ten Plagues, the natural enemies of mankind, incomprehensible and unkillable.

“Both worlds will become dark.”

– 『Ten Commandments』 10:1 –

It was the emergence of a true First Corpse.

Chapter 487

The Marquis of Discord (7)

◆

‘It will swarm like a swarm of flies.’

The 10th Corpse ‘The Inferior Second Son’ Andromalius.

‘Boils will be rampant because of disease.’

The 9th Corpse ‘The Thousand Faces’ Dantalian.

‘Livestock and herds will perish.’

The 8th Corpse ‘King of the Dead’ Seere.

‘They will sweep away like a swarm of locusts.’

The 7th Corpse ‘Wailing Wall’ Decarabia.

‘Lice will boil in your body and in your barns.’

The 6th Corpse ‘The Worthless One’ Belial.

‘Take the life of the firstborn that year.’

The 5th Corpse ‘The Unicorn of the Abyss’ Amdusias.

‘A horde of reckless frogs shall rise.’

The 4th Corpse ‘The Reckless Knight’ Cimeries

‘There will be hail.’

The 3rd Corpse ‘The Ice Duke’ Andrealphus.

‘I will turn water into blood.’

The 2nd Corpse ‘The Lying Panther’ by Flauros.

‘Both worlds will become dark.’

…And the 1st Corpse ‘The Marquis of Discord’ Andras.

The 10 disasters that were cast over the royal family and the ominous beings that caused them.

Now, with them all destroyed, there is only one remaining, the Marquis of Discord, Andras.

And that Andras is inherently a being of two bodies.

The two separate bodies have now come together to face each other.

They were Jack, the reigning heir to the throne, and Pigi, the rumored second in line to the throne.

Vikir stared at Pigi’s face as he stood there, his expression stern.

Why had Pigi turned away from the Academy, and from all relationships with others, in the past?

Was it simply a matter of bullying, harassment, and alienation?

…No.

Vikir had suspected this from the beginning.

‘Pigi is a much stronger friend than I thought. He’s not the type of person who gets lost simply because of bullying or loneliness.’

Perhaps Pigi’s reason for leaving before the regression was because he questioned his lineage.

Vikir made his own guess based on what had happened in the past.

‘Pigi. Isn’t your blood supposed to be black in color?’

‘Huh? Aah, it’s always been this way, huh? It’s been like this since I was a kid, actually! The doctors said it’s because I have a lot of iron in my blood… but it seems like it’s gotten a little darker since I’ve been in the Hell Tree?’

It was a guess that was related to the phenomenon in which Pigi’s blood distorted the causality law when he was trapped in the Hell Tree.

Pigi died once in a previous fight with a demon.

Three days after his death, the heavy lid of his coffin was lifted and he opened his eyes.

The moment Pigi opened his eyes, this was the first thing he thought of.

‘The reason you woke up first is because there was something you had to do first.’

Vikir’s words were still ringing in his ears as he exited the Hell Tree.

The weight and warmth on his shoulders.

‘Never look back. From now on, you go alone.’

In the cunning and malicious trap within the Hell Tree, where everything was trying to deceive and harm him, the only thing that pushed his back was the rough, scarred palm.

Then, raising his head, Pigi locked eyes with a gaze from beyond the portal.

‘…Please go where you are comfortable.’

It was a decapitated head, displayed on a tall pole.

“…What I will do.”

Pigi lowered his gaze and looked at his hands.

Black blood trickled down them.

The handle of the sword piercing Andras’s heart was clearly visible.

[Yes, you… Didn’t Flauros kill him, huh, he was the most suspicious of the candidates, so I told him to be extra careful…]

The 2nd Corpse Flauros used the water source to dig a trap in order to get another form of Andras.

Or to destroy it before it awakens and becomes a threat.

[What the hell did you come here for, to close the ‘gate’?]

Andras said through gritted teeth.

Suddenly, Vikir had a point.

It was the information about Andras that Decarabia had told him in the past.

[Ahem! The structure of the body is heterogeneous. Normal living beings tend to divide individuals based on their own bodies, but that doesn’t work for him.]

‘…What does that mean?’

[In other words, you will divide and define human beings based on you. There is one human being named you, and if there is another human being who meets the same criteria, there is two. And three. Four. Five…. But not once. Two can be one, and one can be two. Since the criterion for separating the ‘a’ and the ‘non’ is outside the human concept, it is impossible to cut them according to conventional wisdom.]

‘I have no idea what you’re talking about. You mean, like you, you have an unusual body structure?’

[Whatever. I don’t know much either. He’s a very secretive creature. But… I only heard that the roles of ‘those who close the door’ and ‘those who open the door’ are separate. This is all I know.]

Decarabia is also an object-type, inanimate-type demon, so it has a very special body shape.

But even Decarabia considered Andras’s form to be strange.

One soul split in two. One body.

It naturally led to rumors of the Oracle spreading throughout the world.

An oracle that caused the civil war in the empire, an oracle that turned the Seven Great Houses against each other.

It was said that the first and second crown princes, both descended from the blood of the first founding emperor, possessed the power of prophets, and that ‘one of them would destroy the world, and the other would save it’.

The reason for this civil war was to prevent the wrong crown prince from ascending to the throne.

And the truth behind it was spoken by Andras, who took over the body of the first crown prince.

[Fufufu- Yes. I am the one with the power to open the gate, and the other Andras, you have the power to close it. Which of us perishes first will determine the end of this dark cloud.]

Andras grabbed the sword that had pierced his chest and crushed it in his hand.

…Kurrrr!

Flames flew towards Pigi.

But it was blocked by Vikir.

Kwakwakwakwang!

Vikir gritted his teeth as Andras’s magic burned and melted everything around him.

“Even a crumbling body can unleash this much power.”

If Andras hadn’t been split in two, if he had killed Pigi and absorbed his soul, if he had even had the magic sword Asmodeus at his disposal, the result would have been unthinkable.

[Open or close the gate, it’s time to choose one, don’t interfere!]

Even at this moment, Andras was baring his sharp teeth and showering fireballs at Pigi.

Kwakwakwakwakwang! Kurrrrrr!

The entire Imperial Palace began to shake ferociously.

Andras’s demeanor was desperate and desperate again.

It was true that he wanted to find his brother and become one.

But the way to become one was through the logic of a game of survival where each must kill the other.

In front of him, Vikir couldn’t help but think of the past.

When Granola’s participation in the war had killed Pigi, Vikir had personally picked up Pigi’s body.

Just as he had before the regression.

‘…I had also personally carried Pigi’s body back then. I was with him on his deathbed.’

Vikir’s memory of the exact circumstances is hazy.

But when he recalls the moment, he thinks.

‘…He’s a good person.’

It’s a phrase he’s heard over and over again in moments of crisis, and it sticks in his mind.

Since then, Vikir has had some amazing experiences.

Pigi’s body hadn’t decomposed, even though it had been days since he’d returned from the battlefield.

Pigi’s body smelled stronger as time passed.

At the same time, there is also a bad smell.

But it was of a completely different nature from the stench of decomposition.

Awakening.

With his death, Pigi was reborn into something completely different, something not human.

It was due to another Andras self that had been dwelling near his soul all this time.

“…I thought it was somehow similar to Seere.”

It was the way of demons hovered around their hosts, waiting to strike when their minds or bodies were at their weakest.

As soon as Vikir smelled the familiar yet unfamiliar odor on Pigi, he held up the Mirror of Truth he had borrowed from Dolores to Pigi’s face.

And in the mirror, he saw a surprising reflection.

The First Emperor. The same face he’d seen so many times in portraits.

Pigi’s lineage was now revealed to the world.

The soul of another variant of Andras had been lingering around Pigi’s body, waiting for the moment of awakening.

“I see now why your blood was able to close the Hell Tree.”

Pigi smiled faintly at Vikir’s words as he stood in front of him.

Pigi’s soul, which hadn’t been completely extinguished, was able to remain in his body with the help of Camus.

Andras’s ego, which unlike Seere’s, had a completely different structure, fused with Pigi’s soul, and as a result, Pigi was able to stand here now.

…Also.

An intangible string connected Pigi and Vikir’s hearts.

It was the same string that Andras had noted when he occupied the body of the First Crown Prince, a strand of unbreakable bonds from the world before the Regression.

[I remembered, Vikir, how you and I met in the other world, and….]

Pigi opened his mouth in a tone that was somewhat sad, but full of longing and joy.

[Why I brought you back.]

Chapter 488

Running Hound (1)

◆

[…I remembered why I brought you back.]

Pigi’s voice was trembling slightly.

At the same time, a memory of the past flashed through Vikir’s mind.

It was the same events that had unfolded before and after the regression.

‘When did we bully you?’

‘It’s just a friendly gesture, I’m going to see you for a long time.’

‘Hey, why are you crying and XX, are you trying to make us look bad?’

‘Hey. Don’t cry. Have a drink.’

‘Ew! That’s so dirty! It’s all over my tights!’

‘Wahahahaha! You puked, you crazy guy, you’ve been so colorful since OT!’

‘From now on, your nickname will be Puke! Puking Pigi!’

‘I’ll call you Puke until I graduate!’

In his previous life, Pigi couldn’t handle the bullying and dropped out, becoming a low-level government employee and struggling to make a living.

His parents had gone into debt to send him to the Academy.

Then, when the Age of Destruction began and the Great War against the demons began, Pigi volunteered to go to the front lines, where he made many contributions to the Allied Forces of Humanity by implementing numerous supply strategies, intelligence analysis, and collection measures.

He was a respectable comrade in arms.

Although he left disappointed in the world and in himself, but he was strong enough to overcome his own trauma and join the Allied forces after seeing the Hell Tree rise in the Academy, the Imperial Capital burn, and his classmates and civilians die.

But just a few months into the war, Pigi is assassinated.

Vikir still remembers the devastated look on his parents’ faces when they saw their son’s cold, dead body.

So Vikir turned back and twisted the causal chain.

‘You try to make a nuisance of yourself in the Academy one more time, and I will not only kill you but your father and mother as well.’

The Night Hound terrorized the bullies who had been harassing his friend and deterred them from repeating their misdeeds.

That small act of kindness rolled like a snowball and eventually made a huge difference.

The result is the ultimate darkness, driving a sword into the heart of the mightiest demon!

[I guess I, too, on the other side of the world line, thought you were my only friend.]

Pigi’s words reminded Vikir of Pigi’s last moments before he regressed.

Vikir had collected Pigi’s body then, too.

At the time of the assassination, Pigi hadn’t died.

When he was first found bleeding to death, many people turned away.

In their defense, it was war and the situation was urgent.

It was more urgent to heal one wound on a great hero than to spend the time and effort to save a dying Pigi.

More people would be saved that way.

The world is efficient.

The world runs on cogs of cause and effect, and each of those cogs, large and small, has a place, a role, and a value.

The small, insignificant cogs are left out in the cold while everyone else looks the other way.

In distrust of the world, in loneliness, in bitter cynicism and resentment.

Just then.

A hand closed Pigi’s eyes.

Wrinkled and scarred, covered in sticky blood, and completely covered in burns and sword marks.

…But a big and warm hand.

There was a boy there, a boy he’d met at the Academy, many, many years ago.

Pigi stared at Vikir with narrowed eyes.

It was a face he recognized. The servant of the boy who had shared the same room in the Academy dormitory.

The hand that had wordlessly handed him medicine when he was beaten and crying.

When no one else was around when he was traveling, he would quietly sit with him.

When eating alone, he would sit across from him and stare off into space.

When Pigi failed a test, when Pigi missed his mom so much, and when Piggyg thought about ending his life, he would appear from time to time to comfort Pigi.

And now, many years later, in his final moments, whether by coincidence or necessity, the boy’s hand is still covering Pigi’s eyes.

The boy was the only one who was nice to him throughout his entire school career.

Though it was only a small, fleeting act of kindness, it remained in Pigi’s heart as big and warm as the sun.

Suddenly, Pigi remembered the voice he had heard during his midterm exams at the Academy.

Now that he thought about it, it was definitely the voice of a servant boy.

‘It’s okay now.’

The servant boy had said as he closed Pigi’s eyes.

It had a far greater effect than any other magic in the world, making the pain in his body and mind vanish in an instant.

The pain of his birth, the guilt of his parents, the obligations of being a child, the burden of his studies, the loneliness of not making friends, the world that had finally turned its back on him, the pain of his body, and one word that relieves it all.

‘…Please go to a place where you are comfortable.’

It was the ‘consolation of a friend.’.

And as Pigi heard Vikir’s voice from beyond the time-shift in a vision, he heard a vision that Vikir had often heard, too.

‘…He is a good man.’

He remembers it clearly now.

It was Pigi’s last words to him, not from beyond the time axis, but from his own memories.

It was the same voice he’d heard every time he’d poured Pigi’s blood into demons like Amdusias, Cimeries, Andrealphus, and Flauros since his regression.

[Many people say that humans are black-haired animals.]

“….”

[The humans I have experienced are animals that remember the kindness they received.]

The human Pigi looked at Vikir and smiled broadly.

“You’re a good man, Vikir.”

It was a smile that could light up the world.

Even Pigi, with his distrust of humanity, his cynicism, and bitterness, who had left the gates of destruction wide open without closing them, could not be as cold to Vikir as he was to this one man.

It was impossible to turn away from him.

Like the intangible link between Seere and Camus in the past, Pigi’s residual thoughts became a strong, unyielding bond that connected him to Vikir on the other side of the world line.

The tenuous hope that the parallel world might have a different ending.

As a result, Vikir regressed. No, the parallel time axis was skipped.

By Pigi’s arrangement, which led Andras to choose and summon Vikir.

It was the result of a collaboration between Pigi from this world line, Pigi from that world line, and Andras of this type.

A small, seemingly insignificant act of kindness to a stranger is the miracle that saves the world.

…And of course, there were those who could not understand this improbable and unreasonable coincidence.

[Shout nonsense! How dare you fool anyone with such a ridiculous development!]

Andras. Jack Merridew.

He was awakened by hanging himself with an umbilical cord while he was still in his mother’s womb, and he made a strenuous effort from an early age to get rid of Pigi from his natural birth.

Sending snakes to the cradle, deliberately forcing them into dangerous places, kicking them out of the family, etc…..

[I didn’t know that that lowly bitch would run away from the palace, but I should have just killed her right away. Ugghh!]

However, Pigi shook his head.

[Even if it weren’t for you, I would have died of my own accord, with all kinds of distrust of humanity and hatred of the world.]

[…!]

[If someone had said to me, ‘You’re a good guy,’ it wouldn’t have happened].

Pigi seemed to be imagining himself on another worldline.

However.

[On this side of the world, I’ve come to know and understand a lot about humans. My family, my friends, and the people around me are all valuable and important].

Tudor, Sancho, Bianca, Sinclaire, and Dolores, his classmates from Colosseo Academy.

And the countless companions who joined forces with him in the Hell Tree, the comrades-in-arms of Tochka who shared his burning thirst.

With their faces in his heart, Pigi stepped inside the coffin.

And, of course, Pigi chose.

[I will close the gate.]

Andras’s two selves are divided into ‘the one who opens the gate’ and ‘the one who closes the gate’.

The gate that Andras(J) opened cannot be closed by Andras(J). It must be closed by Andras(P).

Conversely, Andras(P) cannot open a gate that Andras(P) has closed. It must be opened by Andras(J).

The gate opened by Jack can only be closed by Pigi.

The gate that Pigi closed can only be opened by Jack.

In the end, it was clear that without either of them, something irreversible would happen.

Tsutsutsutsutsutsutsuts…

The gate Andras had opened was being closed by Pigi.

[Nooooooooooooooo!]

Andras screamed, but it was too late.

Deng-geong- deng-geong- deng-geong- jjeog! Peoeog!

The gate slammed shut, severing the bodies of several giant demons that had been slowly pulling themselves out of the portal above.

The nebula-eating serpent, the leader of the insects, the king of the vampires, the scorpion that spewed dark venom, the woman who was beautiful on the outside but no one could tell what was inside, the desert-eating monkfish, the lord of all things rotten, the centipede that scales mountains, the one who walks beneath the sea, the giant that tears up the earth, the fire-drinking lion, the bird with wings that covers the sky, the executioner of the graveyard, the corpse that lies rotting in the swamp, the tentacles that burrow deep, and so on….

…Kung! …kwakwang! …kuleuleung!

Dismembered body parts of demons fall to the ground, causing an earthquake.

[Ugh… Uuuuuuggh…!]

Andras shuddered with rage.

Even now, the 62 portals are slowly closing.

[You can’t do that! If you want to close them, I’ll keep them open!]

Andras clenched his remaining magic power.

Tsutsutsutsutsutsutsuts…

If Pigi closes and Andras opens, the result is the same anyway.

From now on, it’s just a matter of who has more magic and who can interfere with the door the fastest.

However.

“Are you sure you’re not forgetting me?”

Andras felt his heart split in two, then four.

Vikir was standing in front, driving his sword into Andras’ heart.

…Ppuug!

Vikir continued to drive the sword into Andras’s body.

Kazanbai has been destroyed and Asmodeus is in the hands of Kirko in the distance.

Only one of the twin swords that symbolized Andras remains, and even that is now destroyed.

Furthermore, having failed to steal Pigi’s soul and body, Andras is left with only half of himself.

In such a situation, there was no way that Vikir, who had developed as many as nine teeth, would be pushed aside.

Peopeopeopeopeopeopeopeopeog!

Andras’s body was crumbling in real-time.

The hound knew victory was within reach.

He pushed harder and harder to break his prey’s neck.

…At that moment.

“!?”

Vikir’s eyes widened to tears.

Black blood splashed from Andras’s body.

It flows into Vikir’s body through his wounds.

Tsutsutsutsutsutsutsutsuts…

Just as Pigi’s blood had shocked the demon, Andras’ blood was causing Vikir to experience a strange phenomenon unlike anything he had ever experienced before.

[Didn’t I tell you? I inherited the lineage of the founding legend, the First Emperor.]

It is not the blood of a demon, but the blood of a human being.

A relic of an ancient hero who was said to have possessed the most unique ability in the history of mankind, a unique ability that allowed him to rise to the pinnacle of all mankind.

It was his power as a member of the Imperial Family, the Golding Family of the Prophet Clan.

[Now, this is a ‘Spoiler’. I’m about to show you your future.]

Andras laughed as he gripped Vikir’s arms tightly.

[…After a lifetime of entangling yourself with demons, Aren’t you curious how your life will end?]

Chapter 489

Running Hounds (2)

◆

The blood of the Imperial Family, who possess astrology, astronomy, and other abilities to foretell the future.

The first crown prince, Jack, is the one who inherited the abilities of the founding Emperor, whose ability to see the future led to the beginning of the empire.

Andras is currently using Jack’s body as a host to maximize the abilities in his bloodline.

[Keulleog!]

Pieces of crushed internal organs and black dead blood are gushing out from under the lower jaw, which has fallen all the way to the chest.

The cracks all over his body burned brightly.

Tsk tsk tsk tsk tsk tsk tsk tsk tsk tsk tsk tsk tsk tsk tsk tsk tsk tsk tsk tsk tsk tsk tsk…

His body was slowly, gradually, in real-time, crumbling like ash from a burned-out volcano.

However.

[…I see!]

All the while, Andras continued to emit angry streams of mana from his eyes like dark clouds.

The flow of mana gathers in one place, creating red blood veins.

The veins converged again, forming the shape of a giant eyeball.

The eyeball floated high in the air, casting an eerie glare down at the ground.

In a situation where the life of the body had reached its peak, this one evil demon was squeezing out all the vitality that was depleted and showing off his foresight that had risen to an unprecedented limit.

[…See! See! Your future!]

And then, with a foresight so accurate that even the demon shuddered, it flowed out of the crown prince’s body.

A swamp of blood and gore, a mountain of bones, an atmosphere drained of mana, and a massive mushroom cloud rising over the distant horizon.

It was a common sight in the Age of Destruction, one that had been seen many times before in the Hell Tree.

This is what Vikir’s mental image of the world was like floating in the residual thoughts of Amdusias.

However. What was about to unfold was certainly unlike anything Vikir had ever seen before.

…An endless, barren desert.

…A massive tower towering in the middle of the desert.

…An old man in black walks lonely and alone toward the tower.

Each vision pierces Vikir’s mind, fragmented and disjointed.

They are unfamiliar memories that Vikir has never experienced firsthand.

But they were also memories he’d experienced many times before, often indirectly.

‘…I’m sure it was when I faced Amdusias in the Hell Tree when Pigi’s blood closed the Hell Tree, and when I faced Cimeries.’

A world in flames, the Age of Destruction.

A moment of apocalypse, when the ground melted and the breath of all living things burned away.

But the future that Andras’s blood was showing him now was a much later landscape.

[See! You look old as time goes by! Your shadow all alone!]

Of course, what Andras sees is what Vikir sees as well.

A desolate desert that stretched for miles and miles. An old man pacing in solitude with nothing around him.

He coughed dryly as his long, gray beard and black fringe of hair blew in the dry wind.

There is no one, nothing, in sight as the old man traverses the vast desert.

A few images flashed past him, but they were too fleeting to be sure.

[See it! See it clearly! You say you value your relationships with those around you now, but in the end, you are alone! You’re all alone in your old age, wandering around alone and rooted nowhere!]

Only Andras burst out laughing.

In the meantime, the landscape continued to move quickly.

The old man crossed the desert.

The old man, bravely wading through strong winds and quick quicksand, looked solitary and lonely.

[See! You are being chased! You are fleeing from those who are pursuing you!]

His long beards blowing in the sandstorm.

The old man pauses for a moment, noticing something towering above the endless desert horizon.

It was a tower. A single tower, jutting out like a sword.

Andras’s blood-red eyes flashed.

[A life where you have to run away from pursuit until the end of your life! Words that reflect on loneliness and solitude! But those who pursue you will find you! And in the end, you will reach where you are! You cannot run away from them! Forever! Forever! Hahaha- I see it, the furious looks of those who pursue you, your miserable future, bound and shackled to them forever!]

It naturally made Vikir recall the trauma of his previous life.

Memories of running away while falsely accused.

How he was eventually caught by the hounds of the Baskerville family and left covered in blood.

Being dragged to the guillotine, leaving a trail of blood on the ground.

Eventually, his throat was cut.

Cold sweat trickles down Vikir’s face.

Eventually, Andras predicted Vikir’s end.

[In the end, there will be five bodies!]

Five Body Divisions. The terrible punishment that began to become popular during the Warring States Period by the emperor of the Demonic Suzerainty.

Vikir himself was once nearly subjected to this before being sentenced to the guillotine, so naturally, he can’t help but get a shiver down his spine.

“….”

The Hound gritted his teeth.

His breath caught in his throat. His lungs were constricting with cold sweat, and his mind was becoming foggy.

‘Cradle’ and ‘Grave’.

…The time between these two places, at either end of the timeline of life, is life.

What kind of life was it?

And again, ‘grave’ and ‘cradle’.

Vikir recalled the middle link of memory that connected the end of the first life to the beginning of the second.

Vikir.

He struggled.

He had always struggled.

An illegitimate son, the child of a concubine.

Hence the Van middle name.

He wasn’t even born with a family name, like La or Le, which his siblings were given, so he had to work a hundred times harder than everyone else.

But it didn’t end well for him.

After crossing so many lines of fire, luck finally turned against him.

He was falsely accused of being a demon spy and executed.

The Hound thought intensely.

‘I want to live.’

‘I want to live again.’

…And a miracle happened.

Eung-ae-

The flutter of a butterfly’s wings from a previous life. A small, insignificant change.

And the end of that change changed the world dramatically.

…Of course, the hound didn’t do it alone.

Many, many faces have worked to bring him this far.

Even at this very moment, when he thinks of them fighting bloody battles with monsters outside the Imperial Palace, he can’t just sit here and break out in a cold sweat.

“Demon Kills.”

Despite the string of dire prophecies about his graying hair, Vikir was undaunted.

For the sake of his colleagues, he can’t afford to wallow in sentimentality.

A single praying mantis cannot stop the gigantic wheel of cause and effect.

But even so, he must resist the reality at hand as best he can.

That was a much better choice than being swayed by the demon’s tricks.

But Andras smiles from ear to ear.

And with a final flick of his tongue at Vikir, he said.

[Think carefully, all you see in your words is a ‘grave’! Only the terrible fate of having your body and mind cut into five pieces awaits you! If you change your mind even now, you can change this future!]

The demon does not stop playing tricks on humans until the last moment.

…Huug!

At the same time, a thick darkness rose from Andras’s entire body.

All the illusions that Vikir had ever seen, including Nymphet, were blooming there.

The comrades he had failed to save, the friends he had sent on their way, and the countless dead he had mourned stared back at him.

As before, he raised his tongue like a dagger and aimed forward.

However.

…Flash!

The red light emanating from Vikir’s eyes saw right through all of these illusions.

A void of nothingness.

A being like the dark nothingness that forms the abyss of magic.

Vikir realized with a startling realization.

In the end, Andras is empty.

Nothing (Nevermore).

He was nothing more than The Raven, visiting a frail and weary body in the dead of night.

“….”

Suddenly, Vikir was about to say the words he had always repeated dogmatically, ‘Demon Kills’.

The emotions that were boiling inside of him now would not be resolved by the words alone.

The hatred of the demons that had accumulated over the course of his two lives, the self-pity he felt for himself, the regret he felt for what he hadn’t accomplished and what he couldn’t do, the regret and guilt he felt for the relationships he had lost, and the complicated thoughts he had about his father, Hugo.

The frustration, sense of isolation, resentment, and anger about all of these things swell greatly with each inhalation.

…Pakang!

Vikir drew his sword at full length.

He slashed straight through the visions in front of him, forcing all of those old, stale emotions he’d been storing up in his lungs to come out of his bloodied throat.

[…!?]

Andras’s eyes widen to tears.

Jjeoeog-

Vikir’s sword fell like a bolt of lightning.

A final leap to slice through nothingness. The will of man.

Just before the head of the last enemy, the last demon falls off from the body and flies away.

The hound, who had been biting and killing demons all his life, opened his mouth with a sigh of relief.

“Fuck you.”

It was his personal feelings revealed for the first time.

Chapter 490

Running Hounds (3)

◆

I close my eyes and listen to the waves.

I can’t see the sky, the sea, or anything else in the darkness, but I can feel the gritty sand between my toes.

When the waves hit the sandbank and break, my slender wrists flail.

The waves wash away the little sand I hold in my hand.

I cry and hold on, but I get nothing back.

Not the waves. Not the sand. Not even my tears.

I ask through my stitched mouth.

-God. Can’t you hold them tighter?

-Isn’t it possible to save even just a handful more from those cruel waves?

-The ones I’m holding now, or maybe I am clutching.

-Is all this simply a dream within a dream?

My beloved looks down on My wailing from the sandbank.

I speak with a sewn mouth.

-Don’t sing me a sad song when I’m gone.

-Do not plant red orchids or green marigolds next to my head.

-Just put a sword at my grave to cut through the weather and time.

-And if you have a moment to spare, remember me.

-But even if you forget, I can’t do anything about it.

-Because I won’t be able to hold your throbbing heart, or listen to your bleeding throat.

-Just follow the cry of an owl screaming in grief.

-Buried in the dawn twilight, dreaming and stirring.

-At some point, out of nowhere, I might remember the face of the person I loved.

-Or perhaps I shall forget.

◆

“…!”

Vikir snapped out of his daze.

For a moment, his legs gave out and he nearly collapsed.

They say the heaviest thing in the world is an eyelid.

Vikir felt the mana drain from his body like a tide.

A chill ran down his spine. His toes and fingertips were so cold they felt like they were about to fall off.

The magic sword Beelzebub protruding from his wrist had never felt so heavy and sharp.

…Kung!

The vibration transmitted to the floor, this heavy feeling.

Vikir’s body did not create it.

Nor could it have been, for Vikir never knelt on the floor, even under these circumstances.

What had fallen to the floor was the head of a demon.

Andras.

First Corpse. Marquis of Discord. The last enemy. The last demon.

With the head of an owl, it fell to the floor in a spray of thick blood.

Vikir’s 9th Form was so powerful that the severed part of his neck showed no signs of regeneration.

No.

Jjeojeojeog-

The petrified, crumbling cut showed no sign of regeneration.

Andras was really dying.

Neither the soul nor the body can go anywhere, it is eternal death.

“…Did you do it?”

Vikir muttered to himself.

Moment.

[Human! Don’t say such ominous things! Survive again!]

Decarabia shuts Vikir’s mouth in a panic.

Vikir laughed, dryly, but with a hint of blood.

The moment you foreshadow the end, what follows is also a story that sells well and is an obvious cliché.

But this time, there was no such predictable event.

Andras poured out all of his strength and, as a result, self-destructed from within.

To add insult to injury, Baskerville’s ultimate move struck him, the 9th Form and his soul was torn to shreds.

…Of course, that didn’t mean Andras was instantly annihilated.

[Hahahaha- so this is how it ends?]

Andras’s two blackened eyes radiated darkness.

His tongue still moved, even though only his severed head remained.

Though it has stiffened considerably.

[You have won, demon hunter. The Gate of Destruction will soon close, and you and the other humans will never meet the rest of the demons.]

“….”

[But is that a good thing, is it the right thing to do, for all of humanity].

Andras smirked.

[In a way, you’ve blown your chance to atone for the original sin of humanity…]

But Andras didn’t get to finish his sentence.

Vikir lifted his foot and stomped on the severed head.

…Pulsseog!

Andras’ body and head turn into spicy, fine ash and flutter.

Then, in Vikir’s ears, Andras’s prophecy hovered over Asrai and vanished.

[A life of running and fleeing from chase until the end of time, with words of loneliness and solitude].

[But those who pursue you will find you, and in the end, they will reach where you are.]

[You cannot escape from them. For all time. Forever.]

[I see the furious faces of those who pursue you. Your miserable future, bound and shackled to them forever.]

Trauma lasts a long time.

Vikir, who in the past had to suffer a long chase after being accused of being a traitor and a spy, gritted his teeth and endured the prophecies, or rather curses, left behind by Andras.

[In the end, there shall be five pieces!]

That was the end.

Andras shattered and vanished.

Completely broken and gone, literally gone, even from the world beyond the threshold of death.

At the same time.

Kudeudeudeudeudeudeu-

The floor began to shake violently.

The Imperial Palace was collapsing.

The collapse was probably triggered by the raging naval battle outside.

Kwakwakwakwang!

The roof and pillars behind him collapsed and a huge tentacle fell down.

Torn and charred pieces of the Kraken’s leg flew everywhere.

“Looks like things are starting to clear up outside ….”

Vikir turned his head.

Beyond the crumbling rubble, a portal still stood open.

And standing at the portal was Pigi. A comrade-in-arms through two lives.

“It’s been hard, really.”

Pigi smiled sadly at Vikir.

Vikir asked.

“…What happens now?”

“Simple, once I close this last portal, it’s all over.”

The Gate of Destruction closed.

There was only one portal left leading to a world where the Gate to Destruction was open.

“I can only close gates, not open them, so once I close this one, all gates are gone, forever.”

“….”

Vikir nodded silently.

An exhausted hound, at the end of a long journey. Can he lay down now, his body crushed in a bloody ball?

…No.

There was still one thing left to do.

No, the biggest one. There is indeed a task to be done.

Kkudeug-

Vikir rose to his feet, clutching his knees with his hands.

He turned to face Pigi, his gaze unwavering.

Finally, Pigi turned to Vikir and asked.

“Before I close the last portal, I’m going to give you a choice.”

“….”

“Do you want to go back to the world you came from?”

Yes.

The world beyond the portal is a world where Vikir is dead and gone.

With a new body in this world, the Hound is ready to cross over once again.

But deep down, Pigi doesn’t want Vikir to go there.

“Once you go back, you can never come back here again. The bond is severed. It’s goodbye forever.”

The other world has almost returned to peace.

The Rainy Season of Fear had ended as quickly as it had begun, and the great flood would soon be over.

The demons have been annihilated.

Many people have survived, and all demons and monsters will perish.

“Now all you have to do is live a happy life with those who follow you. You don’t have to go back to the barren world you came from, do you?”

Pigi is right.

The other world is populated by 62 demons, each more powerful than the last.

A world overflowing with destruction and apocalypse far more terrible than the worst times Vikir has ever experienced.

It must be a hell of unearthly proportions.

Pigi said impatiently.

“Some of them have not yet given up their love for this world, and I can feel them swarming toward this one remaining portal.”

The last portal Andras had created before his death.

There’s a real malice rushing toward this passage.

If this portal isn’t closed quickly, a truly terrifying demon may come through.

Something far stronger and more evil than all ten of them combined.

Vikir was conflicted.

Just then.

-Annihilation! Total annihilation!

-I can’t hold out any longer!

-Retreat! Retreat!

-There is nowhere to retreat to!

-God, save my child in danger…

.

.

From beyond the gate, he heard pitiful screams.

It was the death cry of the comrades left behind in the Age of Destruction, the last remaining handful of humanity.

And there were a few familiar voices among them.

-All Morgue is powered! Imprisoned here!

-Keep the faith until the end, people!

-Haha… Now neither money nor gold is of any use to me.

Vikir made a decision of either yes or no.

“I can’t end it this way, not after hearing the voices of my comrades who are still alive.”

Moving on. To the original world. Back to the original world.

He will have to walk the thorny path he has walked once again.

No, it was clear that it would be a much longer and harsher pilgrimage than that time.

But still, the hound goes. Even though he was covered in blood and limping.

At Vikir’s words, Pigi closed his eyes as if he knew it was coming.

“I knew it. I knew you’d do the same.”

Vikir didn’t say anything in response, just nodded once.

And then.

Vikir ascended the stairs.

The shattered throne, the precarious staircase on the verge of collapse.

Finally, the last remaining portal to this world comes into view.

What he sees beyond is a world with a severed head.

A timeline of shame filled with blood and stains.

Vikir turned his head and locked eyes with Pigi.

Pigi nods with a wry smile.

Night Hound. Vikir Van Baskerville returns to his original world.

It was time to move on.

Just then.

“You’re not going anywhere!”

There was a voice that grabbed Vikir by the back as he was about to cross the threshold.

Chapter 491

Running Hounds (4)

◆

The dark clouds on the horizon recede.

The sun rose, the rain weakened, and a double rainbow appeared.

The monsters had lost their strength and were running away to the bottom of the sea.

…Kwakwang! Pungdeong! Uleuleung-

The Kraken, the strongest enemy of the Tochka Alliance, lost all its tentacles and crumbled beneath the water.

In the distance, the Imperial Palace can be seen collapsing.

“Aaah! The black fog has lifted!”

“Vikir did it!”

“…Also!”

Tudor, Sancho, and Bianca shouted in joy.

But.

“Hmmm. I have a bad feeling about this.”

Standing over the corpse of a large monster, Camus had been feeling uncomfortable since earlier.

The flow of mana was strange. There’s a huge surge of mana, then it breaks off, and then it flows out again in a faint trickle.

This was a completely new type of energy that did not belong to Andras.

Furthermore, Vikir’s aura was also fading, as if it were about to break.

It wasn’t a matter of life force, but rather a feeling of being very far away.

“Camus, what’s wrong, do you sense something bad?”

Adolf Morgue loomed over the corpse of the monster across from Camus.

Camus answers her uncle’s question with a simple nod.

“ …It’s like a woman’s instinct.”

By this time, Aiyen, Dolores, Sinclaire, and Kirko, all of whom are as capable as Camus, are also sensing something fishy.

Kwakwang!

Camus sprinted across the surface of the water.

Four shadows followed behind her.

Aiyen, Dolores, Sinclaire, and Kirko.

Their appearance made Camus turn around, irritated.

“What the hell! Why are you following me!”

“I’ve been keeping an eye on the palace since earlier. I had a bad feeling.”

“Vikir might be injured, and we need to get him some medical attention as soon as possible.”

“I’m worried about my brother. He deserves a cat’s hand!”

“I was following him the whole time. Is there a problem?”

Just then.

Chaaaahhhhhhhh.

The sea surface parted, revealing a vast expanse of land beneath it.

Madam. It was holding out its back to the five women, including Camus as if inviting them to get on.

“Okay!”

Camus, Aiyen, Dolores, Sinclaire, and Kirko climbed onto the Baby Madam’s back and rode toward the palace.

And soon.

They witnessed a shocking scene.

Pigi had risen from the dead, and Vikir stood before the portal, covered in blood.

The first to let out a new scream was Camus.

“Where are you going! Hey…!”

In her panic and anger, a swear word escaped the tip of her tongue before she tucked it back in.

Camus pressed her hands firmly to her chest to control her anger.

“Huh… No, I can’t, I’ve barely corrected my way of speaking, and I can’t swear again, damn it!”

But she couldn’t hold it in any longer.

She stretched out a trembling finger and pointed at Vikir.

“Where are you going!”

“….”

Vikir’s eyes widened at Camus’ sharp question, but he didn’t say anything.

A few more moments passed before he finally opened his mouth to answer.

“Where I came from. I’m going where I’m supposed to be.”

“Fuck! Where you’re supposed to be is next to me, don’t you realize that?”

The area around Camus’ eyes was turning as red as the color of her pupils.

“…Do you always think about yourself?”

“….”

“Do you ever think about me when you’re thinking about yourself?”

Camus spoke in a quiet voice.

“Who am I to break up all the gossip that comes into the house?”

“….”

“Because of you, I never had the love life that everyone else had, the school life that everyone else had, and I spent all my youth searching the jungles of Le Rouge Et Le Noir Mountain, and then you turned my path to black magic and made it awkward with my uncle….”

“….”

“Didn’t you know that I became a delegate to the Dark Hall just to meet you, and then I transferred to a school to meet you, and then you fell into the Hell Tree, and when you came out, you were tried and sent to prison, and when you escaped, you staged a sit-in in Tochka, and now you’re in the Imperial Palace….”

“….”

“You bastard, who’s the hound of House Baskerville!”

Camus was about to use her signature magic.

Vikir realized he couldn’t handle Camus’ anger in his current state, so he quietly raised his hands and stepped out of the portal.

Only then did the Camus’ momentum slow down a bit.

Vikir suddenly took a closer look at Camus’ face.

Time had certainly passed.

She was still the same little eight-year-old, but she had grown into a determined young woman.

He thought it was just a crush that would end after a while, but it wasn’t.

Just then, another girl walked by Camus’ side.

It was Aiyen.

“I’m sure you haven’t forgotten your time in the jungle, or what happened in Nouvelle Vague.”

“….”

“The first time I saw you was in a slave trader’s cage. When you rescued me, I knew in my gut. I knew I would spend the rest of my life with you, and that nothing could separate us, not even the harshest of fates.”

“….”

“I never forgot you, not even during the Red Death epidemic or when I was trapped in the Hell Tree. I even traveled into Nouvelle Vague myself to rescue you.”

Aiyen’s face flushed a rare shade of red.

“And I’m already married. You’ve seen everything I’ve seen and everything I can’t, even urinating…..”

At that moment, the word urinating came out of Aiyen’s mouth, and the person next to her blushed bright red.

Dolores was wriggling her fingers.

“…I, I am”

She hesitated for a moment, then gathered her courage.

“I’ve been working so hard to be of help to you, Vikir! I’ve studied soul resonance so I wouldn’t be a nuisance as your soul mate, I’ve followed you on demon hunts, and I’ve even formed an organization called the Night Walkers to fulfill the mission you left for me….”

Dolores looked up at Vikir with tears in her eyes.

“I’ve done a lot for you, and it’s not fair that you’re leaving without giving me a compliment….”

And beside her stood another woman who had been with the Night Walkers all along.

Sinclaire.

She looked up at Vikir, her eyes wide and clear.

“Do you remember what you said to me before?”

“….”

“You said it was entirely up to the individual to decide what to see, what to believe, and what choices to make.”

“….”

“You’re right, brother, and that’s why I’m going to make a decision that’s solely my responsibility.”

“….”

“I want you to go out with me, brother, seriously, like marriage! We promised each other when we were having midnight snacks in the dorm, and one day, when you get everything you want, you’ll take me as your bride!”

Camus, Aiyen, and Dolores’ eyes narrowed at Sinclaire’s bombshell.

A fifth voice broke through the bickering among them.

It was Kirko.

“Garam. No, Vikir.”

“….”

“I’m still stunned. Why you saved me, and what was going on in Garam’s mind. Everything is just confusing.”

“….”

“So I want to follow you for a while longer, to find the meaning of my life, what I have to live for.”

“….”

“I’m a body that has already died once. If it weren’t for you, I would have no ties or regrets in this world.”

“….”

“This may sound a bit brash, but… you’re the one who saved me from disappearing with my hometown, so I think you owe me that much,

so take me with you. To where you originally belong.”

Camus, Aiyen, Dolores, Sinclaire, and Kirko.

They were giving Vikir as determined a stare as he was.

Vikir spoke, his voice cracked and hoarse.

“Where I came from is a devastated place.”

All five women nodded.

“I know. I can guess that from your personality.”

“What kind of environment did you grow up in to have such a bad personality?”

“Seriously, Vikir, you need to reflect.”

“Brother, do you have a personality problem?”

“It’s worse than Nouvelle Vague, so… I’m a little curious.”

Vikir said again.

“I am a terrible human being. I carry a heavy burden… and I’m old.”

All five women nodded once more.

“I know you’re a terrible person, and you should be grateful that you know that because that’s why we love you.”

“You did seem older. The way you talked and acted.”

“Our Pope said you seemed old in spirit from the beginning, which is why she called you an old man at first….”

“The carrying part reminded me, brother, do you remember when we were in the Hell Tree, you kicked me for taking on the fist of a Demonic Dragon? I’m secretly behind you~ I’m going to make you regret kicking me.”

“How much age difference is appropriate between a man and a woman? I don’t know because I’ve never been in a relationship, but is it weird if there’s… Is it strange if we are 50 years apart?”

They walked up the stairs, spouting off one comment after another.

And then.

Camus, Aiyen, Dolores, Sinclaire, and Kirko stood behind Vikir.

Just as they had always done.

Of course, their faces didn’t change at the sight of the landscape beyond the portal.

“I can’t send you to such a horrible place alone, remember? You said you’d stay with me through death’s door.”

“I’ll go with you. I want to help my tribe, whoever might still be alive on the other side.”

“I saw your inner Vikir in the Hell Tree of Cimeries. You said we were colleagues. Let’s share the burden, Mr. Choco.”

“Wherever my brother goes, I will definitely follow. Don’t you dare leave me behind.”

“It’s an interesting place. Did the Nouvelle Vague over there collapse too? I’d still like to go there.”

Eventually. Vikir couldn’t help but sigh.

“Do as you please.”

Vikir turns toward the portal.

Camus, Aiyen, Dolores, Sinclaire, and Kirko follow him.

And as Pigi watched them all, a faint smile tugged at the corners of his mouth.

“…They are good people.”

And with that, the portal closed.

Beyond the blazing flames, Vikir threw himself into the twisting space.

The Hound of Baskerville, the Night Hound.

He returns to where he came from, having fulfilled all his duties.

Tsutsutsutsutsutsutsutsuts…

His vision began to spin.

Every sense in his body is twisted.

The clockwork was ticking backward.

And blooming between the first and second hands, The last words of a friend who left a long time ago and who is now letting go of him are disturbed.

‘Have a great trip, friend.’

That was his last time in this world.

Chapter 492

The Day After the Apocalypse (1)

◆

…Pas!

A star twinkled in the sky, and then it was gone.

It flickered so briefly that most people didn’t see it.

However, whether by coincidence, a good sense of vision, or simply because she was staring sadly into the night sky, tired of her miserable existence, only one defeated soldier saw it.

Major Janet, 1st Battalion, 207th Regiment, Allied Forces of Humanity.

She pursed her lips, which were stained with burns and sword marks.

“The guiding star is strange tonight.”

Sergeant Miryamu, who was grilling bugs and lizards next to her, asked.

“Battalion Leader. Did you say something just now?”

“Ah, no. The guide star is a bit….”

“What? What’s with the guiding star? It’s the same as usual.”

Then some of the soldiers looked up at the night sky.

They could see the seven guiding stars shining brightly.

But only Major Janet shook her head.

“That’s strange. There were definitely eight just a moment ago.”

“Hahaha – there are seven guiding stars, even a seven-year-old child knows that …Well, now finding a seven-year-old child is like picking stars in the sky.”

At Sergeant Miryamu’s words, Major Janet smiled bitterly and tore her eyes away from the night sky.

The Age of Destruction.

As the rivers of blood dried up, the decades-long war between the human and demon realms seemed to be over.

But on that day, as the surviving humans celebrated their victory and carved their glory into stone.

The true apocalypse had begun.

One after another, horrors that would make the disasters of the past seem like child’s play were revealed.

There were 62 demons, each with a power and evil that far surpasses Ten Corpses.

They turned the human world, which had been devastated by the long rainy season of fire and the great flood that swept through the world for 150 days, into hell once again.

‘…I was happier when I was a soldier.’

Major Janet is reminiscing about the past.

“Battalion Leader, it’s an air raid, monsters are coming!”

Captain Saladin could be heard shouting as he ran up the hill.

The orders shouted by superiors from afar also echo loudly.

Lieutenant General Kirk, Brigadier General White, Colonel Kuberin, and others…, veterans of countless crossfire, were gathering the last remaining survivors of the Human Alliance and preparing for the final battle.

“Battalion Leader, come on!”

“If this line of defense is breached, it’s over! Behind us, the last remnants of humanity are… children….”

Captain Saladin and Sergeant Miryamu paced back and forth.

“Onya, I know. Take your positions!”

Major Janet donned her helmet and raised her sword and shield.

Behind her, Sergeant Miryamu stood with his spear.

She opened her mouth, her voice trembling.

“This is really going to be my last battle.”

“…Probably for everyone here.”

The two soldiers chatted as they watched the swarm of demons staining the horizon black.

It was like a brother and sister talking before bed.

Suddenly, Sergeant Miryamu asked.

“Battalion Leader, how is it that you are always so carefree?”

“Hmm?”

“You’re always calm, never panicking, as if you’re under some kind of protection.”

Now that most of the priests have disappeared, divine protection has become an epic in a vain dream.

But Major Janet just smiled.

“God bless you. If it’s a blessing, it’s there. We all need a little faith to keep us going in this harsh world.”

“Eh! You have a corner you trust? What is it?”

Major Janet smirked at the last man standing, Sergeant Miryamu, with whom she had grown close.

Then, eyeing the swarm of monsters now closing in on them, she spoke.

“A letter.”

“…Yes?”

“A letter. From my old boss.”

Major Janet.

The contents of a letter she held close to her heart as a talisman had gotten her through this far.

It was a memory of a young junior officer she had met many years ago, when she had just joined the army, struggling to make ends meet.

“I think his last name was Baskerville, right?”

“What? Baskerville? You mean those crazy dogs over there on the front lines?”

“Yeah. He was a nice man, unlike the other Baskervilles, a good and reliable hunter, though he was falsely accused and executed in the middle of the war….”

Major Janet’s face fell at the memory of the old days.

Sergeant Miryamu opened his mouth to speak, facing the swarm of monsters in front of him.

“You must have been quite the romantic, leaving all those letters.”

“No, he wasn’t much of a letter-writer… which, when I think about it, is very strange.”

“Like what?”

“The letters. They arrived after he died.”

“Well, what, the postman was lazy or something?”

“Hmm. It’s been too many years for that. The letter didn’t arrive until long after he was executed….”

But the conversation between the two soldiers went no further.

…Boom!

A giant-sized demon appeared at the front line.

The momentum it exuded was different from the other demons around it.

It had two arms, two legs, four wings, and a long tail.

It had curved horns, eyes that blazed like the sun, and dense muscles packed tightly throughout its body.

Major Janet had to swallow hard.

“…Demonic Dragon.”

Cursed half-breeds, born of a dragon and a demon.

Eternal Diaspora.

It is a nasty and evil creature that takes out its anger on all other living things for not being treated properly by both dragons and demons.

[Kua-aaaaahhh!]

It roared like a demon and rushed toward the human camp.

Even the last of the humans was nervous before its overwhelming combat power, capable of tearing thousands of humans apart with a single blow.

“Damn it. What’s he doing here, usually lurking in the depths of the Hell Tree, only to come out when it’s time for the final battle?”

Major Janet gritted her teeth.

They can’t back down from this. Humanity has already been pushed to the brink.

One more step backward and it would be over.

“Stop it! If the line is breached, the refugees behind it will be exterminated!”

Major Janet unleashed her aura to confront the Demonic Dragon.

Against such an absurdly strong opponent, she had only one chance.

A fatal blow!

Swinging with all her might, Major Janet’s sword aimed for the gap left by the Demonic Dragon’s fist.

But.

…Taang!

The once-in-a-lifetime opportunity was wasted.

Major Janet’s sword broke in half as soon as it touched the scales on the Demonic Dragon’s body.

“….”

A shadow of despair crossed Major Janet’s face.

Where she looked up, she saw the face of the Demonic Dragon, grinning from ear to ear.

And then. The Demonic Dragon’s huge fist dropped like a meteorite.

If it hits, it’ll kill her instantly, or at the very least, wipe out a dozen meters behind her.

And a lot of people will die again.

‘…Is this the end?’

Major Janet is just about to resign herself to life.

“Battalion Leader!”

A hand grabbed her by the waist.

Sergeant Miryamu. He risked his life and leaped in, pushing Major Janet to the ground.

Kwakwakwang!

Major Janet flew to the side.

She immediately jumped to her feet and screamed.

“Mi, Miryamu!”

But there was no answer from the dense dust.

No wonder.

“Aaaaah….”

Tears streamed from Major Janet’s eyes.

Even she was surprised at how much moisture was still in her eyeballs, which she had thought had dried up and turned into a hard solid.

Miryamu. The one who had followed him so closely since he was a second lieutenant.

They’d fought together until he’d become a sergeant.

He’d only made it to sergeant over the years, even though it was easy for him to be promoted because his seniors were dying so quickly and in such large numbers.

He was always running away because he was too scared.

“…Such a coward saves me.”

Major Janet gritted her teeth.

She must avenge her subordinate.

She bit down hard on her burst lip once more.

She summoned as much of her depleted mana as she could.

She gripped her broken sword tightly once more.

“Even if I have to die, I will take one of you with me.”

Major Janet stared straight ahead with the last of her strength.

Suddenly, the dense dust settled, revealing a giant shadow.

The Demonic Dragon stared back.

For some reason, it stood still, defenseless.

‘This is my chance!’

Major Janet knew instinctively that this was the last chance she had been miraculously granted.

And before she realized it, her body reacted.

“Aaaaaaah!”

She charged with all her might, her sword energized with mana.

Aim for the heart. A single stab!

Even as Major Janet leaped with all her might, the shadow of the Demonic Dragon, which had begun to reveal itself as the dust cleared, stood still.

As if he were giving the insignificant worm a favor.

“Your arrogance is your signature!”

Then, with all her might, Major Janet drove the broken sword into the Demonic Dragon’s heart.

And in that moment, she once again realized she had failed.

…Ttug! Pagsag-

The broken sword broke once again.

There were too many cracks in the first place, so it didn’t receive the full force.

The wound was quite large, but it didn’t hit the heart at all.

“…Ah.”

Major Janet knew it was really, really over.

She had no mana, no strength.

There would be no excuse, no resistance if her head was crushed in that Demonic Dragon’s grasp right now.

‘I’m sorry.’

I could not avenge Sergeant Miryamu’s death.

Also revenge for other comrades who died cruelly.

Major Janet closed her eyes tightly.

She waited for her death to come.

She hoped it would be a painless one.

….

…But.

No matter how long she waits, death never comes.

‘What is it? Is it already over?’

Is death supposed to come without feeling like this?

Or did it happen instantly, with no time to feel shock or pain?

“…?”

Major Janet opened her closed eyes slightly, ever so slightly, in wonder.

And then she saw an incredible sight.

“…!”

Beyond the dust that had been cleared away, Major Janet still stood before the Demonic Dragon.

His chest was puffed out, showing off a body so hard and majestic that even a sword could not penetrate it.

…The problem was, his the shoulders of the Demonic Dragon were empty.

Pusyug! Pusyusyug!

Black blood gushes out from the severed neck.

Currently, Demonic Dragon has lost his head and is being held by someone.

And at the feet of that, someone is Sergeant Miryamu, sitting there with a dazed expression on his face.

Major Janet didn’t realize what had happened for a moment.

One second. Two seconds. Three seconds. Four seconds. Five seconds. Six seconds. Seven seconds. And eight seconds.

The second hand moved as many times as the number of guiding stars she’d confused.

Only then did Major Janet dare to look into the face of the ‘someone’ who had slain the Demonic Dragon and saved Sergeant Miryamu.

He was…. He was….

“You’re all alive, I see.”

A voice that speaks in such a strange tone.

His attitude was as if he had just gone for a walk or a sightseeing trip somewhere far away.

Like a soldier returning from a long leave of absence, He glanced around the battlefield, his inner circle.

“Captain Kirk, Lieutenant White, Sergeant Kuberin, Sergeant Janet, Corporal Saladin, and Private Miryamu… Everyone was alive. The 1st Platoon of the 4th Company of the 207th Regiment is still alive and well.”

The ‘he’ was clearly the face in Major Janet’s memory. But at the same time, it was not the face he remembered at all.

It was a contradictory explanation, but there it was.

The burns and stab wounds that covered his face were gone, and he looked decades younger.

But.

“It’s great. Well done.”

The aura he exuded was still overwhelming, even more so than before.

Meanwhile.

“This, this guy. He fell from the sky, from a guide star.”

Sergeant Miryamu, who was on the ground, pointed at the ‘he’ and the ‘you from the star’ with a dazed expression.

Then ‘he’ gave a faint smile.

“I see. Private Miryamu. You were too young then to remember my face.”

“What, what, Private? Me? I’m the sergeant….”

Sergeant Miryamu looks confused.

But Major Janet’s expression is completely different.

With tears in her eyes, she exclaimed in a joyful tone.

“Company Commander, you’re alive!”

“…Do you recognize me?”

“Of course, I knew you were alive after all! Where have you been all this time, and why have you changed your appearance so much…?”

“You were alive? Did you not see my throat cut?”

“What? Oh, I did see it, but… Have you not sent any letters since then?”

Major Janet looked puzzled and then drew out the letter she had kept in her bosom.

It was a letter written on parchment, yellowed with age.

-I miss you, comrade. Are you at peace there?

Upon seeing it, ‘he’ looked blank for a moment, then muttered to himself.

“…Then that letter was real, I don’t know what’s going on.”

At that moment, several soldiers from the Humanity Alliance side, who had seen the Demonic Dragon dead, rushed over.

They exchanged glances between Major Janet’s face and ‘his’ face, then let out a cry of wonder.

“Company Commander, Company Commander, is that you?”

“Are you alive?”

“Where have you been, everyone has been waiting for you, Company Commander!”

“We knew you were alive after all! Everyone on the front lines said you couldn’t be dead…!”

But. The reunion was short-lived. No, it had to be short.

Kwakwakwang! Ujijijijijig!

For there was a giant leg that emerged, crushing the Demonic Dragon’s corpse like tofu.

A demonic beast with enormous hooves and a long mane appeared, crushing the body of the Demonic Dragon.

[Fuhahahahaha- I am Orobas, the Equestrian Prince of the Eternal Hell, ranked 55th in the hierarchy! Who is this who continues this futile resistance!?]

At the appearance of the giant demon, the expressions of all the humans are colored with despair.

“Off, it’s over! Number 55 in the hierarchy has appeared!”

“Why is he here!”

“Wrong. With the descent of Demon Lord-level demon, everything is over….”

However. There was no time for the humans to despair.

…Flash! Kwa-kwakwakwakwang!

Five pillars of light fell from the sky.

Burning Iron Skewers, Fierce Snipes, Holy Pillars of Light, Golden Fists, and Sharp Slashes slammed into the ground in a terrifying explosion.

[Kkeuaaaaagh-]

The demon that had appeared just a moment ago was instantly shattered into pieces and scattered.

“Ouch, my back, I’m getting motion sickness, yuck-”

“It’s been a big start since you made your debut.”

“Well, this is my first debut in the other world.”

“I thought the second hand on my watch was drowning me out.”

“The day after the apocalypse is no big deal.”

Five women walk out of the pit where the demons are crushed to death.

All the demons and humans who had been fighting bloody on the battlefield a moment ago have stopped fighting.

They turn in unison, mouths agape.

And then.

Ku-leuleuleuleuleug!

The storm of aura swirled black and swept away dozens of meters around.

A giant black dog with nine teeth appears in the middle of the battlefield.

….

Everyone gathered on the battlefield, both demons and humans, stood frozen and swallowed dry saliva.

And then.

Before all these eyes, ‘he’ said.

“Demon Kills.”

Chapter 493

The Day After the Apocalypse (2) [END]

◆

The year BE 1,020 on the Continental Calendar.

The rivers of blood have finally dried up.

The decades-long war between the human and demon worlds has been recorded in the history books as the Age of Destruction.

And the day the human world’s victory was carved into stone.

A head was hung at the main gate of Tochka, humanity’s last fortress.

Baal.

Aka ‘Mother of Destruction’.

72 The Spiritual Pillar of Demons.

The day its head fell to the ground, the Age of Destruction came to an end.

And there were several people who made great contributions to driving Baal and other demons from the earth.

Camus Morgue, lord of the House of Morgue.

Osiris Le Baskerville, lord of the House of Baskerville.

Bourgeois Ju Sinclaire, lord of the House of Bourgeois.

Dolores L. Quovadis, Pope of the House of Quovadis.

The Warden of the Nouvelle Vague ‘Orca Montreuil-sur-Mer Javert…’.

.

.

There are so many other heroes that humanity has barely survived.

…But.

There were also heroes who fought more brilliantly than anyone else, but never made it into the history books.

They appeared out of nowhere.

Accompanied by the 8th guiding star, they descended upon the battlefield and drove away the demons like messengers promising salvation.

Age unknown, identity unknown, name unknown.

But the man who was the eldest of the six heroes was clearly the Iron-Blooded Swordsman Baskerville.

Rumor has it that he mastered the 9th Form, a rank that was said to be unattainable in a lifetime, but the truth of the matter has never been revealed.

Other figures have also failed to make it into canonical history due to unusual questions.

They surprisingly had the exact same appearance and the same powers as already existing figures, such as Camus Morgue, Dolores L. Quovadis, and Bourgeois Ju Sinclaire, who were among the heroes who saved humanity.

Some were from long-extinct tribes of barbarian warriors, and there was even a deserting prison guard of unknown rank who was vaguely suspected to have once been a member of the Nouvelle Vague.

Eventually, at their hands, Baal fell, and a long peace came to humanity.

Immediately after the end of the Age of Destruction, they were able to receive recognition for only a small portion of their enormous achievements and receive a small amount of territory.

Can Only Share Sorrow and Cannot Share Joy.

They withdrew from the ugly squabbles over the public domain, and, satisfied with a small amount of compensation (considering their merits, a level so small that it would be considered absurd), they quietly retired to their territory and have not been seen in the world since.

The world can only assume that they had raised a large family, had numerous children, and were living out their final days in quiet and comfort.

….

However.

As I write this journal as a conscientious officer, a scholarly historian, a popular author, and a survivor of an Age of Destruction, I cannot help but ask additional questions.

Where did they come from and where are they going?

Who were they, and what were their purposes and intentions?

These are questions that can never be answered no matter how much I think about them and study them, and it is a lifelong task for me, and for all of humanity whose lives were saved by them.

In a situation where everything is questionable, the guiding star they came down to today is silent and only shines brightly.

Seven stars shining ever brighter…

-‘Nymphet’ from 『History of Magic』, Volume 3,021 page-

◆

Whiiiiing-

A dry wind blows, peeling away a layer of desert flesh.

A black robe flutters in the wind, and a long, graying beard.

An old man walks across the salt flats.

A side effect of being a time traveler?

A body that grows one year old only when others have lived ten or twenty years old.

The children grow up, and the children’s children grow up, and the children’s children’s children grow up, and again, and again… Anyway, quite a long time has passed.

The old man is about to leave.

Throwing off all his shackles and restraints, he gives in to the instincts he’s been suppressing for a very, very long time.

Whiiiiing-

Another gust of wind whips up, chipping away at the rocks.

The old man rode silently over the crescent-shaped sand dunes covered in salty salt sand.

And then.

What the old man was looking for came into view.

It was a Tower.

A Black Tower, jutting up against the white horizon.

Like an awl jutting out of the ground, it bathed in the blackness of the night sky and the red of blood.

‘Grave of Swords’

The old man nodded silently as he read the crude writing on the front of the Tower.

“…A true Baskerville is born in the ‘Cradle of Swords’.”

After a moment of silence, the old man continued.

“…A true Baskerville dies in the ‘Grave of Swords’.”

Just then.

[This is the Grave of Swords, the final resting place of those who follow the extreme will of the sword.]

There was a heavy, echoing laugh from within the Tower.

Then the top of the Tower opened like a dog’s mouth.

Inside the Tower was a throne of steel and an old man in black armor seated upon it.

A Baskerville, with a long white beard.

A former Seven Counts who had seen the turbulence of war, and the strongest man in all of mankind, even in the Age of Destruction.

He stroked his pure white beard and smiled broadly.

[This is definitely a familiar face, even though it’s the first time I’ve seen it. The intuition of a superhuman who has reached the realm of the supreme transcends even space and time.]

The gray-bearded old man did not reply to the white-bearded old man’s words.

He simply pulled out a crimson sword with the back of his hand.

Seeing the momentum that the gray-bearded old man exuded, the white-bearded old man smiled with satisfaction.

Then.

The two old men with white and gray beards swung their swords at each other.

It was a split second.

Nine teeth met nine teeth.

The gray-bearded old man stopped moving as if struck by lightning.

In the meantime, his body trembled as if something that had been blocked for so many years had been unlocked.

At the same time, space and time began to distort.

…Ppajig!

In the midst of the nine teeth’s ferocious clashing, a tiny speck of light flashed.

It’s teeth. It was the tenth teeth.

It was so small it was barely visible, but it was clearly attached to the nine teeth.

And then… the storm subsided.

Only one man remained. An old man with a gray beard.

He raised his head and looked up at the Tower.

He stood there for a long time, then slowly took a step.

Inside the tower.

And behind the gray-bearded old man, who slowly entered the Tower.

[Your birth will be like the birth of a sword, and your death will be like the death of a sword].

The voice of the old man with the white beard, who had now disappeared, was slowly becoming distant.

完. Thank you.

◆

…Kwakwang!

With a loud bang, hot flames leaped up.

“Who says it’s over!”

A woman stomped her foot, her anger rising to the top of her head.

“Aaah! I don’t know if it’s a side effect of time travel or whatever, but it made me into a body that never ages, and are you already trying to send me to a venomous workshop!? This is really a dog that can’t give up its old habit of running away without saying a word! Like he’s from Baskerville!”

Her red hair erupts like a volcano.

All around her, flames and spikes of blackened metal soared murderously.

And beside her, pacing was a copper-skinned woman.

Her muscles were toned, her bow strapped to her back, her choker tied around her neck.

“I want to have many children, to rebuild my tribe, and since the human population is so small, and fertility is encouraged as a virtue, … I need to fill at least three digits.”

A native woman preaching the virtues of fertility.

And next to her, a woman in a white nun’s uniform can be seen knitting in a calm manner.

“Oh no. Calm down, everyone. Overexcitement is bad for your body. Well, it’s almost demi-god territory at this point anyway, so there’s no chance of getting hurt…. Ah? Is it possible that just because your body is strong and supreme… you asked for too much, and that’s why he got scared and ran away!”

A saintess who has a calm demeanor but is the first to panic.

The next to speak was a woman with short-cropped white hair.

“Brother, stop being lazy, that’s why it splashed again. If I were him, I’d run away because of the noise. Wherever he goes, you always follow him around. One must have faith.”

The white-haired woman criticizes the other women.

The last to join the conversation was a woman with dark hair and red eyes, who seemed to have a cold demeanor.

“Leave it to me. Catching escaped prisoners is my specialty, and I’ve found where he’s gone this time.”

All the women’s eyes lit up.

“Where? Where did he go this time?”

“The desert again, I’m sure.”

“If he went looking for the Tower, I’m disappointed, it’s the same old pattern.”

“Well, this time it seemed to have a different momentum.”

“Don’t worry. I’ve already found the Tower, and I’ve been there twice, so I can find it with my eyes closed.”

The five women bonded instantly.

Despite their usual bickering, they had always been able to work together to solve problems quickly in situations like this.

“Just wait and see! If he gets caught this time, he’ll get fifty years in prison, he’s dead, really dead!”

“Wow, the bitch who will cry and snot out her tears and beg him to come back whenever we meet is always good at talking.”

“I miss him already, I don’t want to be away from him even for an hour….”

“Don’t worry about it. By the way, if he gets caught this time, I’ll have to cut brother’s allowance in half.”

“I wonder if he’s running away from home because you keep cutting his pocket money like that.”

“Well, instead of cutting his allowance in half, why don’t you double the number of defense battles?”

“I think that would scare him more.”

“I’m fine with just watching from the sidelines.”

“Ugh- you’ve been a sissy for decades, really?”

“Yeah, but this time it looked like he was really trying to run away.”

“Hey! It’s the Gave of Swords, it’s obvious, I’ve got it all mapped out.”

“Oh, there? The place guarded by that basilisk? He hasn’t come out since I beat the crap out of him on my last preliminary exploration.”

“If it had a map, it would have scared it away and moved its nest. It’s a pretty intelligent creature.”

“Anyway, isn’t it about time we found it?”

“Oh, look! I see it!”

The five chatty women cross the desert to the Tower.

[A life of running and fleeing from chase until the end of time, with words that reflect loneliness and solitude].

[But those who pursue you will find you, and in the end, they will reach where you are].

[You cannot escape from them. For all time. Forever.]

[I see the furious faces of those who pursue you. Your miserable future, bound and shackled to them forever.]

It was the moment when the ominous oracle that someone had predicted a long time ago came true.

[In the end, there shall be five bodies!]

Side Story Chapter 1

The river of blood is slowly drying up.

It happened in the highlands of the Western Front, where the battle against the remnants of the Demon Army had not yet ended.

◆

The Morgue’s Citadel is made up of countless towers.

It appears to be made up of countless skewers stuck into the ground.

Among them, the basement of the tower is hidden in the most remote place.

Each of Morgue’s two major factions, the Light Hall and the Dark Hall have their own secret underground spaces.

One of them is the ‘Dark Side’, the deepest part of the Dark Hall.

The underground space stretches more than 600 floors below the ground.

And on the lowest level, the 666th floor is the headquarters of the Dark Hall.

It was a space known only to the Dark Hall’s delegates, inaccessible to Imperial monitoring, demonic gaze, and even the head of House Morgue.

At the bottom of a spiraling staircase with no end in sight.

There, a lone woman sits on a throne, her eyes closed.

Tsutsutsutsutsutsuts…

She is a mage who checks the mana flowing through her veins.

With her red hair and white skin, she is clearly a master mage who has reached the peak of her powers.

Camus Morgue.

She trusts no one and relies on no one.

She has stood alone her entire life, battling the world tooth and nail, sometimes winning, sometimes losing, and living each moment as if she had never been hurt before.

“Huu….”

Finally, Camus opened her eyes from her meditation.

By nature, when a mage checks their mana, they are very vulnerable.

As the saying goes, ‘A mage who checks their mana is like a crab or a shrimp who has just shed their shells’.

That’s why Camus always meditated only on the 666th floor of the Dark Side, where no one else was allowed to enter.

Absolute self-righteousness.

She trusted no one, so she didn’t do any favors.

Only she could guard and protect her own body.

….

“Did you finish your meditation? It took longer than usual?”

When Camus opened her eyes, she saw an unbelievable sight.

A mask with a stork’s beak.

A woman in a grim, ominous mask had emerged from behind a stone pillar.

It was a wonder that any outsiders existed on the 666th floor, where only delegates of the Dark Hall were allowed to enter.

“…More than usual?”

More than anything else, this statement made Camus frown.

This meant that the mysterious intruder in front of her had been watching her meditate a lot and for a long time.

In reality, Camus had been meditating longer than usual, so the words were not just a taunt.

Kuleuleuleuleuleug!

Mana boils around her.

Camus summoned flames and iron skewers and hurled them at the intruder in front of her.

“I don’t know who you are, but die, and I’ll ask questions later.”

As a master of the art of death, Camus was more comfortable and accustomed to dealing with the dead than the living.

Especially when it came to interrogating prisoners or spies.

But.

Kwakwakwakwang!

Her eyes widened at the unbelievable sight.

Flames and iron skewers, flew in from the other side, offsetting Camus’s attack.

And then something else happened that stunned her.

Sssssssssssss…

Tree branches as long and thin as a woman’s hair hang down in front of Camus.

Wraith Tree.

A tree of mana that takes root in the minds of mages and nourishes the karma of souls.

An incomprehensible being that feeds on abstraction and metaphysics and delivers its harvests to the material world.

It was also the signature of the eighth demon lord, Seere.

“No way! Seere, I definitely destroyed that guy along with Snake!”

Camus was aghast.

It was a natural reaction.

The demon lord she’d slain so long ago had returned to life.

But.

“Calm down, I’m not here to fight.”

The masked woman neatly parried Camus’ attack and took a step back.

“What are you, a demon lord? How do you possess the power of the 8th Corpse?”

“Like this.”

In response to Camus’ question, the woman shrugged one shoulder.

Then something crawled out of her shoulder.

“Se, Seere… that?”

Camus stopped in her tracks, about to shout in surprise.

What was in front of her now is something that is a bit lacking to say that it is ‘Seere, the demon of necromancy’ who once brought this world to the brink of destruction.

“…Why is it so small?”

Camus opened her mouth halfway in disbelief as she looked at the tiny, insignificant Seere.

The mysterious woman tilted the mask on her face in a pointed manner.

“Because I’ve absorbed most of it.”

“…Demonic power, is that possible?”

“It is possible.”

Then Camus made a face of disbelief.

“What kind of a crazy bitch are you, eating demonic power because you had nothing else to eat? You’re no ordinary crazy bitch, and you’ll do the world no good by keeping you alive.”

“Don’t lie down and spit on me.”

“…?”

Camus shakes her head in confusion.

Then, the woman removed the mask that covered her face.

Red hair, red eyes, and a vaguely familiar face.

“…!”

Camus’ eyes widened.

It was Camus standing in front of Camus.

“W-what is it?”

“What is it? It’s you.”

The unmasked Camus smirked and walked forward.

“I thought you were a lot older, but you’re not that old? It’s me too. You’re still pretty no matter how old you get.”

“…?”

Camus walked forward and stood in front of the confused Camus.

Camus then revealed her identity.

“I’m you from the parallel world.”

“What the fuck….”

“Does that sound like shit?”

“….”

Camus, in her 20s, raised her head.

Camus in front of her looks no different from Camus in her 20s, despite the fact that she is now well into middle age.

“Let’s just call it ‘you on this side’ and ‘me on that side,’ because I’m from a different world anyway.”

“What kind of nonsense are you talking about?”

Camus on this side said through gritted teeth.

“Demon Kills. We kill people who use demonic powers. We just have to kill them all.”

“…Oh. It’s a lot hotter over here than it is in the West.”

Soon, fire and skewers fly from Camus on this side.

Camus on that side blocked it, using Seere, who was tied to the roots of the Wraith Tree, as a shield.

[Kyaaaaaaah! Camus-nim! It hurts so muuuuuch! I’m not Decarabiaaaaaa!]

Looking at the screaming and wailing Seere, Camus on this side half opened her mouth in disbelief.

Then.

“Can you trust me?”

Camus from that side throws a token of reconciliation to Camus from this side.

…Tug!

It was Baal’s head.

Camus on this side opened her eyes wide.

“This is Baal, the First Demon Lord, did you kill this guy?”

“Technically, only the shell, it looks like the main body is hiding somewhere else.”

Camus from that side continued, unconcerned.

“I’ve never been able to locate Baal’s true body, and I’ve slain many demons, but no one seems to know. Perhaps Baal itself has no great desire to conquer the human realm, the problem was that there were too many low-ranking demons who wanted to continue its legacy.”

“How do you know such things, bitch?”

“I told you, you’re me and I’m you, which is how I got in here.”

When Camus from that side finished speaking, she looked around.

The seals on the door that responded only to Camus’ body, the familiar array of pillars, and the magic circles on the floor.

Everything was as she knew it.

Finally, Camus from that side blinked, her eyes moist.

“This is where Master died. I still get teary-eyed when I think of Uncle Snake….”

“What? Snake? Master? Why is that filthy beast a master?”

“What? Beast? Are you calling Uncle Snake a beast?”

“…?”

“…?”

At this, the two Camus exchanged sharp looks.

“I have only one uncle, Uncle Adolf. He, too, died in an all-out assault by demons. Snake, that despicable, filthy man is nothing but a dog who sold his soul to a demon.”

“If you insult my master, I will never forgive you.”

“Shut up. Snake is a shameless traitor who caused the deaths of Uncle Adolf and Mother”

“Not to me.”

“It’s different from what you just said. I am you and you are me.”

“Maybe not.”

The mood of reconciliation, which had been created only briefly by the shell of Baal, quickly became as precarious as a sheet of thin ice.

Right then.

“I sent you to hold her hand, but what if you start playing the game?”

A muffled voice came from behind the stone pillar.

Then, a shadowy figure stepped between the two Camus.

Vikir. A hound who had crossed many lives.

An old man covered in wounds was standing there.

A moment.

“…!”

Camus from this side froze.

The man’s eyes were deep and intense, enough to make even the most arrogant and stubborn person in the world freeze in her tracks.

Moreover, just by looking at them, for some reason, her body felt weak and her heart trembled, as emotions she had never experienced before in her life suddenly sprouted from the depths of her heart…

“Hey, what are you looking at!”

But Camus on this side was forced to snap out of her reverie by the shout of Camus on that side.

Camus on that side rushed over and grabbed Vikir’s arm.

She turned to Camus on this side and gave her a stern warning.

“Don’t set your eyes on someone else’s husband.”

“I am you, and you are me?”

“Oh, I guess not!”

Camus on this side snorted in disbelief.

Then, turning to the other version of herself and her husband (?) in front of her, she asked.

“So. Why are we here?”

Camus on that side replied.

“Let’s hold hands.”

“Hands? What, are you suggesting we do nail art?”

“I’m you and you’re me, so you know my personality. If you make one more sarcastic remark, I’ll kill you.”

“I’m you and you’re me, so you know my personality. Go ahead, kill me.”

“Ha, is this bitch is really….”

Then Vikir shook his head, as if he’d seen this coming, and stepped between them again.

“Let’s join forces.”

“Join forces on what? Slaying demons?”

“There’s more. There’s something else, something more fundamental.”

“…What’s more important than slaying demons?”

“To restore humanity.”

“!”

Vikir spoke up, answering Camus’ question.

“Since the Age of Destruction, 99.99% of humanity has perished. On this side of the world, Tudor, Bianca, Sancho, Pigi, and countless others met a different fate. The same goes for those who were used as hosts for demons.”

“What can you do about it? The dead are dead. They can’t come back now….”

Camus on this side shook her head, her voice bitter.

Perhaps she was thinking of Raspane or Adolf, who had died in the war against the demons.

But.

“There is a way to resurrect them all.”

At Vikir’s words, Camus on this side raised her head.

And in front of him stood Camus from that side.

Thump-thump.

Camus stamps her foot on the floor with a smile on her face.

And on the floor, a large, yet incomplete magic circle can be seen drawn.

Suddenly, Camus on this side’s eyes widen.

She looks more agitated than she has ever looked before.

And then.

The voices of the two Camus come together as one.

“Liquor of complete revival!”

Side Story Chapter 2

“…The Magic Circle of Full Revival”

Camus on this side was skeptical.

“Isn’t it something that can only be attempted by reaching the state of being able to draw at least ten mana rings, which is practically impossible?”

“It’s close to impossible, but it’s not impossible. Just because it’s close to fire doesn’t mean it’s fire, right?”

“Don’t play games with me. I know, because I’ve tried countless times to perfect this formula, but it’s a wall I could never get over on my own.”

“Yeah. I’m with you on that one.”

“…?”

Camus on this side looked puzzled, and Camus on that side spoke up.

“‘Alone’?”

Camus Morgue.

How many people had betrayed her so far?

How many people had failed to fulfill her expectations?

Her unparalleled skill, her arrogant temper, and her distrust of others honed through countless heartbreaks.

All of this has led her to distrust others.

…But what about herself?

Camus on that side spoke in a confident voice.

“I am a magical genius. The strongest Morgue.”

“….”

“You are a magical genius. The strongest Morgue.”

“….”

“What if we joined hands and made up for each other’s shortcomings? Can’t you see what would happen?”

“….”

Camus on this side remained silent.

She had always kept to herself, even when meditating to check her mana because she didn’t trust others.

Finally, after a long silence, Camus on this side spoke up.

“…Can you really bring them back? All of them.”

“I can’t say for sure, of course. But if there’s even the slightest chance, don’t you think we should try?”

Camus on this side nods in agreement with Camus on that side.

Eventually.

Kkwaag-

The two rare magical geniuses joined hands.

The objective: the ‘The Magic Circle of Full Revival’, a forbidden method that no one had ever succeeded in creating.

“Should we do it right now?”

“Are you sure?”

“Of course not.”

Camus on that side slid down to the floor and stood.

Then she turned to face Camus on this side.

Camus on that side took a small, deep breath.

Then she spoke in a low voice.

“Did you know that the Morgue started out as a morgue, a mortuary?”

“…!”

“And it was a small family that specialized in that kind of business, keeping only unidentified corpses.”

Camus on that side was rummaging through a long, long memory.

‘Morgue’ was the name of a very old bloodline, dating back to before humans had any concept of family or nation, and the main job of those who carried on the lineage was to collect unidentified corpses and find their relatives.

They were paid to collect bodies that had been mutilated beyond recognition, find their relatives, and hand them over to them.

As a result, they were often in the presence of the dead, and as time passed, those who could communicate with the dead gradually emerged.

Whether they were once a power on par with a nation, whether they had been cut off for decades after the downfall, or whether they were once again called a house of Mage, those with this strange ability continued to emerge.

A nostalgic voice that is no longer there.

A lifelong benefactor to Camus on that side.

The voice of a teacher who had left behind a heavy debt that could never be repaid.

“So, technically, Morgue’s origins are very close to death. For from the beginning, Morgue was one who spoke to the dead and called upon them.”

“ …You mean that from birth our ancestors were in touch with the Black Magic?”

“Exactly.”

“Hmm.”

Camus on this side listened to Camus on that side in silence.

Finally, she spoke up.

“That’s the first I’ve heard of such a thing in all my time in Morgue’s territory. I’ve heard the elders of the Dark Hall say something similar before, but it was in the midst of the war against the demons… and I didn’t have time to listen.”

“I only heard it from my master, too.”

Camus on that side is referring to High Councilor Snake.

Knowing this, Camus on this side only frowned.

“But why are you telling me that now?”

“The Black Mages of Morgue know from birth that all the truth a man can seek and understand in a lifetime is a handful of sand picked up from the beach.”

“Then where is most truth?”

“You’re asking the same question I was back then.”

Camus on that side smirked.

“After death. Beyond the gate.”

“…!”

Camus on this side opened her eyes a little wider.

And Camus on that side met her gaze without wavering.

Only by crossing the threshold of death is a human being completely free and eternal.

One can explore the infinite truth behind it.

Then Camus on this side said.

“So you have turned to the Black Magic path. To familiarize yourself with death.”

“No. It’s the opposite, I first became wary of death.”

“?”

Camus on this side shakes her head again.

Camus on that side smiled bitterly, for she too seemed to be seeing her old self.

“Black Mages are the ones who have the least regard for death.”

“Why is that?”

“Because we must first understand and familiarize ourselves with life before we can understand and familiarize ourselves with death.”

“…!”

Camus on this side listens in silence.

At this age, she had never listened to someone so quietly before.

‘Well, isn’t that what someone else said?’

While this Camus was thinking to herself, that Camus continued to speak.

“Life. Feelings for others. Love. Friendship. Trust. Organic relationship with all that is in the world. Gratitude for being alive. The preciousness of life. You have to understand these things before you can truly understand death. Everything is two-sided.”

“Can’t I just familiarize myself with death first? I think I can.”

“That’s a good question. My master’s answer to that question was… No, you’ll be angry to hear that. I was a little angry at the time.”

Camus on that side recalled in her mind the answer she had heard from Snake back then.

‘It’s nothing more than a bunch of drunken fools pretending to be black mages.’

If this Camus had heard that, she would have been furious, even more so if it had come from Snake, the man she hated so much.

“Whatever. Contrary to popular belief, true black mages must be able to love and understand living things more deeply than anyone else.”

“…One who loves all things living and sympathizes with all things dying. In a way, a black mage is akin to a sage or saint in the eyes of the world. Are you saying that the opposites are compatible?”

“It’s me, You understand quickly.”

The two Camus talked for a long time.

And in the meantime, Vikir was watching the two women’s questions and answers for a long time.

Finally.

The two Camus sat down in the center of the circle, facing each other.

“In order to perfect the Magic of Full Revival, we must travel to the Abyss of Magic to learn the theories and formulas we lack.”

“That’s where all the truth is kept, the very foundation of this world, so we may be able to find what we need. It will take time.”

Camus on this side has already tried this trick once before and failed.

“I know how to do it, so I won’t fail this time.”

Camus sat cross-legged with a determined look on her face.

And then.

…Paaas!

The two Camus began to infuse mana into the magic circle.

Deudeudeudeudeudeudeudeudeudeu-

The magic circle began to ignite.

Countless intricate shapes emitted light.

The ingredients are at its center.

35 liters of water, 20 kilograms of carbon, 4 liters of ammonia, 1.5 kilograms of lime, 800 grams of phosphorus, 250 grams of salt, 100 grams of potassium nitrate, 80 grams of sulfur, 7.5 grams of fluorine, 5 grams of iron, 3 grams of silicon, 15 other trace elements, and memories of blood and flesh… All of this began to emit a strong stench, heat, and smoke.

‘…Wait, stench?

Camus on this side stiffened.

She didn’t know what was wrong, or how it happened, but she knew the result.

“Fail!”

Camus on this side had a hunch.

In that instant.

“It’s not a failure!”

Camus on that side shouted sharply.

That brought this side Camus’ mind back into focus, momentarily clouded by confusion and agitation.

Suddenly, something strange began to stir in the center of the magic circle.

…! …! …! …! …! …!

Seeing it, Camus on that side gritted her teeth.

“It’s good to see you again!”

All she could think at the time was that ‘that thing’ should not be allowed outside the magic circle.

But the thought was short-lived.

Rather than preventing ‘that thing’ from coming out of the magic circle, rather, we must go inside ‘that thing’.

Camus on that side began to control the mana with all her might.

Sssssssssss…

The Wraith Tree moves.

The enormous amount of negative dimensional mana it had stolen from Seere was flowing through the magic circle under Camus’ careful control.

“You’re saying you can physically suppress this? Are you a monster?”

“Hoho- What are you patting yourself on the back for, you get a share!”

Camus on that side laughed, and Camus on this side gritted her teeth.

Ku-gugugugugugugu!

The two Camus control the magic circle.

And then.

…Quack!

The magic circle shattered and mana flowed back.

Instant bursts of light, heat, and wind.

The two Camus, who were exposed to a shock wave that made them lose their senses, experienced death at least for a moment.

Near death. The shattering of everything and the return to nothingness.

Just then.

“Camus!”

A voice held the two women’s consciousness firmly in place.

Vikir. He was giving strength to the two Camus beyond the magic circle.

“…! …! …! …!”

Camus on that side straightened her bent back with all her might.

‘Master, give me strength!’

Recalling Snake’s face, Camus took a deep breath.

Tsutsutsutsutsuts…

The sight in her consciousness is shared by Camus on this side.

In the center of the magic circle, she sees a dark door.

Wide open.

Camus’ body was being sucked through it of its own accord.

Toward the vast abyss beyond, where clouds of stars and gas float.

Like dust.

…Just then.

Flutter!

There was someone blocking the way.

A man stood in the doorway, his black cloak flapping. Snake Morgue.

He spoke to Camus without looking back.

‘Go back.’

‘Your journey is not over yet, so go back and tell them it was beautiful.’

Snake stepped boldly toward the doorway beyond, toward the dawn, dew, sunset, and clouds of the abyss.

‘May you be a black mage who can love life.’

And that was it.

…It was like that back then.

But not this time.

“Ulyaaaaaaahh!”

Camus began to release mana with tremendous force.

And then.

Ku-ooooooo!

The darkness rising from the center of the magic circle began to take the shape of a huge door, or rather, a hole.

It sucked in everything around it with incredible power and appetite.

Even the two Camus and Vikir could not escape being pulled into it.

“…!”

“…!”

Vikir and Camus on this side instinctively resist the powerful suction that is sucking them in,

But Camus on that side had a different reaction.

“There’s no need to resist, just let yourself be pulled in, ‘that thing’ is the entrance to the abyss!”

In order to master the Magic of Full Revival, one must go on an expedition into that terrifying hole that evokes the inherent fear of humanity.

‘…Master!’

Camus gritted her teeth once more.

The path that Snake had traveled so long ago.

An unknown realm of stars and clouds, gas and dust.

‘The Magical Abyss’.

Camus’ final destination has been revealed.

Side Story Chapter 3

Two Camus walked through an empty void.

Behind them, the expressionless face of Vikir could be seen.

The Abyss of Magic.

Gas, dust, and star clusters drifted through the void, receding into the distance behind theam.

Camus on that side spoke.

“The mana wheel here seems to play the same role as the wheel of a ship.”

“I see. Mana is like fuel. We can inject it through the mana wheel.”

Camus on this side answered.

The two geniuses worked together as if they were one body.

It was only natural since they were one and the same.

Vikir asked.

“…Is it something that comes naturally to you as you travel through this space? I don’t understand anything.”

But there was no answer from the two Camus.

“I see. All the mysteries of Magic that I’ve been wondering about for so long are here, complete with equations, answers, and the process of solving them. This is, this is amazing!”

“Yes, it was! Time flows differently depending on the motion of an object, and since spatial and temporal mana coexist in all beings, it was necessary to analyze the mana of both factors simultaneously to reduce the error in the formula!”

“The magic circles are also subject to both space and time and the moment the balance between these two forces is disturbed, even the same magic circles will have slight errors, which is why the Full Revival Magic always fails… I overlooked the relativity of space and time.”

“This is heaven! This is an ocean of information! Every speck of dust that floats by is the truth that every mage has longed for all their lives!”

The women were busy feeling and analyzing the countless particles floating through the Abyss of Magic.

The realization of truth.

It was something that was only possible for the most eccentric of the eccentrics who dwelled in the maddening depths of the Magic Abyss, so it was understandably incomprehensible to Vikir.

“…I don’t know what that is.”

When you don’t know something, it’s always better to meekly accept help from someone who does.

They’ll get you at least halfway there.

Vikir decided to keep quiet and follow the two Camus.

The two Camus were still talking to each other as they moved forward in their spirit form.

“The ‘Abyss of Magic’ is similar to the ‘Ring of Reincarnation’. They’re all just abstract names for the ultimate manifestation.”

“If I can combine the formulas I’ve gained from my travels here, I’ll no longer be dreaming of perfecting the ‘Full Revival Magic’.”

“That’s right, If that happens, I will have the opportunity to meet Master.”

“You keep saying Master, Master, why do you follow Delegate Snake so closely? He was the one who signed the contract with the 8th Corpse to become King of the Dead?”

“Not in my world. He was a benefactor who gave his life for me. The reason we are here today is all thanks to the research results he left behind.”

“…So, Snake did that? I don’t believe it.”

“So who do you think was the contractor to the 8th Corpse in the world I came from? House Morgue, for the record.”

“Hmm. There’s someone else in House Morgue who would make such a stupid contract? I can’t believe it.”

The two Camus were getting to understand each other through their conversations.

The occasional argument or bickering escalated, but Vikir, who was behind them, mediated, so there wasn’t much of a ruckus.

Soon, they were traveling deep into the Abyss of Magic.

A never-ending road of paradoxes.

They reached the midpoint between the starting point and the ending point.

After that, they reach a new midpoint between the midpoint and the endpoint.

After that, they again reach a new midpoint between the midpoint and the endpoint.

After that, they reach a new midpoint between the midpoint and the endpoint again and again.

After that, they go again and again and again and again….

An endless hell full of nothingness and emptiness.

Beings trapped in the myriad of fleeting moments that exist between dots and points.

But despite this, they were still hopeful.

“I’ve already thought a lot about what kind of infinity comes from taking a finite number and adding it an infinite number of times.”

“You mentioned the division between the observable and the unobservable, right?”

“Yes. That infinity has a sequence. I just don’t know if it’s very clear.”

Vikir nodded at Camus’s words.

Then.

As they traveled on, they came across something strange.

It was the shattered body of a demon.

Floating in the cold void, the demon’s head opened its eyes.

[…I don’t know if there’s another one that will make it this far. Are they descendants of ‘him’?]

“You are Baal, aren’t you?”

Camus on this side asked.

Camus on that side and Vikir instinctively prepared for battle as soon as they saw Baal.

The being called Baal spoke in a lonely voice.

[Do you know my name?]

“I know. I suffered to death for the war your men caused.”

[All I left behind there is a shell, an illusion. The real me has been trapped here, lost in thought for a long time.]

Baal thought, remembering a time so long ago that it was no longer clear to Baal exactly when.

‘And when the last moment of your life comes, come to this place.’

And as the voice of ‘him’ echoed in Baal’s mind, Baal realized.

[…And so it was. A milestone. Was this my role.]

Baal laughed in disbelief.

Baal turned to Vikir and Camus in front of it and said in resignation.

[Just by traveling here, you will get what you want].

“….”

[But even after you get what you want, you will have no choice but to return here again].

“….”

[Because that’s what ‘he’ wants].

Those were Baal’s last words.

“Demon kills.”

Then Vikir drew his nine teeth in the air.

Camus on that side, also rolled nine mana circles, weaving flames of fire.

…Kwakwakwakwang!

Baal was destroyed.

Demon Lord who ultimately failed to become a demon god, ended up turning into red dust and floating in a space full of nothingness.

“But what is meant by a milestone?”

“…We’ve destroyed it, so it doesn’t matter now. Let’s go.”

Vikir and Camus continued onward.

Just then.

For the first time in their lives, they encountered a crisis.

Tsutsutsutsutsuts…

The size of the mana ring gradually became smaller and smaller, and the amount of mana being injected began to decrease.

“Hmph. It’s difficult to increase the number of mana rings with my current level of cultivation.”

Camus on that side clenched her fists tightly in frustration.

Then.

Tsk-.

A hand touched her shoulder.

Camus on this side looked up and gave her a complex glare.

Finally, she opened her mouth.

“Ever since the fall of mankind, I have lived without trusting anyone.”

The sincerity in her voice is palpable.

“But right now. I can’t help but trust others. It’s funny how I’ve come to rely on others…….”

Just then, Camus on that side tapped Camus on this side on the shoulder.

“It’s no one else.”

“….”

“I am you, and you are me.”

“….”

“And we are us.”

Camus looked at herself and smiled broadly.

“We can do this.”

Then Camus grinned back.

“Who said anything, there’s no disputing that.”

“Am. There’s no question about it.”

“But I guess we have a different opinion on this one. Is it a difference in the environment in which we lived?”

“…?”

A puzzled look from Camus on that side.

Puck.

Camus on this side stretched out her hands.

Camus on that side and Vikir stumble forward, their backs against the wall.

At the same time.

Paaaas!

Camus on this side begins to draw in all of her mana.

Camus on that side immediately realized what she was about to do.

“What!? What are you doing now…!”

“If you were really me, you’d know what I’m about to do.”

“….”

“If you know, don’t hesitate and take it. I don’t want to waste my energy.”

Camus on this side put all her strength into Vikir and Camus on that side and pushed them forward.

Then, she moves backward like an adjunct propellant that has finished its job and is falling away.

With one more strong thrust, Camus and Vikir shoot forward in the blink of an eye.

As they receded into the distance, Camus on this side said.

“Full Revival Magic. If you can’t figure it out, don’t come back.”

“….”

Camus on that side eyes reddened.

But tears didn’t flow.

For her next words.

“And. Did you say Vikir?”

“….”

“You can always come back to me if you feel you’re in danger.”

Camus on this side glared at Vikir.

Seeing this, Camus on that side became furious.

“How dare you flirt with my husband!”

“I’m you, you’re me, we’re us, so he’s our husband~ hohoho~”

She hasn’t laughed this hard in years, maybe decades.

Until the end, Camus on this side said something mixed with a deep laugh that you couldn’t tell if she was joking or serious, and then she was buried beyond the darkness of the abyss.

Soon, only Vikir and Camus on that side were left alone in the vast void.

How much time had passed?

“…Shall we go then?”

“…Yes.”

The two continued to move forward, across the shrinking horizon of time and beyond the bounds of perception.

Something pierced the darkness into their vision.

“Indeed. Is this a scene that can be seen in the Abyss of Magic?”

“Wow, this is huge.”

They had arrived at the ‘Reservoir of the Magic Abyss’.

It was a cloud that contained 140 trillion times more water than all the water on Earth combined.

Jjeoeog-

A fish so huge it could swallow a star leaped over the waves crashing against the cloud’s surface.

It carried countless tiny babies on the tips of its fins.

Vikir and Camus continued to push forward through the clouds.

Soon, they came face to face with a black hole thousands of times larger than the sun.

It was a point of gravity that greedily sucked in everything around it.

“…Is this the main body of the Magic Abyss?”

“It looks like it, for one thing, it’s ridiculously large.”

But they decided to give it the benefit of the doubt.

“Hmm. There’s no way the main body of the Magic Abyss is this small.”

“It could be. It’s big, but not as big as I thought it would be. Maybe it’s a trap.”

They decided to walk right past the giant hole in front of them.

The slightest turn and an unfathomable amount of time passed.

Vikir and Camus passed by the wandering stars buried in the darkness of the void.

Some of them were moaning, with eyes, noses, and mouths.

“Perhaps they were once beings traveling here, like us.”

“If we linger, we could end up like them. Let’s go.”

Vikir and Camus continued to roll their mana wheels, moving forward.

Paas-

It’s getting brighter and brighter.

No, not brighter, but hotter.

A giant fireball was coming their way.

But it wasn’t that big, so Vikir and Camus were able to easily avoid it.

“That must have been a very long snake once.”

“It must have shrunk in length as it aged.”

The two continued to move forward.

And then.

A disk-shaped orb of darkness appeared before them.

Chunks of cold lead floated around it.

Hududug- hududug- hududug-

The solidified lead masses move toward Vikir and Camus as if pulled by gravity.

Vikir pulls out his sword and begins to slash at the flying lead.

Camus, meanwhile, is using her fire and skewers to fend off the lead.

As they cleared the shower of lead, Vikir and Camus faced each other.

Huge pillars rise like the five fingers of the Creator.

-All things are born from the Abyss of Magic and return to the Abyss of Magic.

-One day, when the stars move, a door will open to a new level and all things will come to their inevitable end.

And the moment they saw the words written on it, Vikir and Camus felt a shock like being struck by lightning.

Chalalalalalag-

Countless letters combine in their minds.

Black letters on white drawing paper, form a giant library.

“…Yes, I get it! I get it now! The Full Revival Magic! I’ve found what Master and I were lacking, and now I can revive everyone!”

Camus frantically began to draw magic circles in the air with her hands.

Meanwhile, Vikir was using all his strength to remove the lead from the surrounding area.

And then.

Paas-

Vikir and Camus’ bodies erupted with light.

They had gained all that they had hoped to gain from the Magic Abyss.

The purpose of the ritual had been accomplished.

◆

“….”

Vikir opened his eyes.

The first thing he saw was.

“What, did you come back right away?”

It was Camus.

Vikir asked her.

“How much time has passed?”

“I don’t know, I just woke up. Didn’t we wake up at the same time?”

Vikir was silent.

Surely a long time had passed since he had parted ways with Camus on this side.

But if even that epic amount of time had been just a fleeting, barely perceptible moment in reality….

Then.

“It’s only been about eleven minutes since we’ve been in the Magic Abyss, 666 seconds to be exact.”

Camus beside him spoke up.

She glanced at her pocket watch, which she had set before unleashing the full revival magic circle.

“I never realized the relativity of time could be so extreme. This is the Abyss of Magic.”

“But I don’t think I can go twice.”

“Really? I’m sure I can go again as many times as I want.”

Vikir and Camus looked at each other and smirked.

Just then.

“What is this place, Dark Side? Why am I here…?”

A familiar voice came from behind the stone pillar.

Instantly, Vikir and Camus looked up.

Tears began to form in Camus’ eyes.

“Aaah….”

The person struggling there was none other than Snake Morgue, Camus’ master.

“I’m sure I resisted the devil’s temptation and went on a mana rampage…, but how come I’m still alive… huh!”

Snake stood there dumbfounded, only to be startled by Camus hugging his back.

“Young, Young Lady? How did you get here….”

“Now is not the time!”

Camus decided to put off her emotional reunion with Snake.

She quickly looked back at Vikir and called out.

“Husband, let’s get out of here!”

Snake Morgue’s revival told her that the Full Revival Magic had been successful.

“….”

Vikir nodded, too.

With a rare look of excitement on her face.

And then.

…Bang!

The door to the Dark Side burst open.

Vikir and Camus stepped out into the blinding sunlight.

And then. The gates opened.

The sight before them was something new.

Side Story Chapter 4

Der Vogel k?mpft sich aus dem Ei.

-The bird struggles to get out of the egg.

Das Ei ist die Welt.

-The egg is the bird’s world.

Wer geboren werden will, mu? eine Welt zerst?ren.

-Whoever wants to be born must destroy a world.

Der Vogel fliegt zu Gott.

-The bird flies to God.

Der Gott hei?t…

-The name of that God is…

◆

“Sancho, Sancho, are you alive!”

“Tudor, my friend! How are you!?”

Tudor and Sancho look at each other, dumbfounded.

For a moment, they stare at each other in disbelief, and then they embrace in a passionate manly embrace.

“I thought you were dead!”

“Me too!”

They hugged each other, sobbing profusely.

And then.

“Excuse me. Friendship is nice, but can you give me a little love, too?”

Bianca, standing behind Tudor, had a vein of blood on her forehead.

“Bianca! My funny girlfriend!”

“What, what kind of bitch is funny gf?”

“Well, it’s just an idiomatic expression….”

Tudor and Bianca started bickering as soon as they were reunited.

Then.

“What… here?”

A man stood up from the crowd of revived soldiers.

Tudor, Sancho, and Bianca recognized the man’s face at a glance.

“Second Prince!?”

◆

Here is an old man.

Cold eyes, a stubborn nose, a mouth that looks like it has no hair and a mustache that gives off a heavy aura.

This old man is giving off a chilling impression.

“Huaaaaahhhhh!”

He was crying.

Very sobbing, too.

“Roxana! Penelope!”

Hugo Le Baskerville, the patriarch of the House of Baskerville, was hugging his wife and daughter, every ounce of moisture in his body spilling out of his eyes.

Roxana and Penelope stare into each other’s faces, dumbfounded.

“How did we survive?”

But there was something more important than that right now.

“Pomeranian, my dear!”

Penelope held the small girl, who must have been six or seven years old, tightly in her arms.

Hugo thrust his tear-stained face into Pomeranian’s wide-eyed, helpless face.

“Patriarch, from this day forward, you’ll be the Patriarch of the House of Baskerville, and I’ll do anything you want!”

“Uaahhh- mustache!”

“You don’t like mustaches! Hello! Is there no one there? Bring me my sword! Nope! Just grab it with your hands and tear it away!”

Hugo hugged his wife, daughter, and granddaughter and sobbed like that for a while longer.

…And.

Osiris, his eldest son, was looking somewhat dazed at the sight of his father, whom he had never seen before.

“I see. My father was human after all.”

He smiled faintly and turned his head.

There stood his younger brother, Seth.

“Brother.”

“Yes, brother.”

“I don’t know what to tell you. Because my body was taken over by a demon….”

“I know all about it. Say no more. If everyone has been revived, that’s enough. You are innocent.”

“Brother….”

Seth began to sob.

Osiris, who had soothed Seth’s shoulder, turned away.

Over the railing, in the bell tower, he saw a familiar face.

Cindywendy.

She stared at Osiris with a wavering gaze.

Hwag-

With that, Cindywendy turned and disappeared down the stairs.

…Tatag!

Osiris ran after her.

◆

A little more time passed.

The Morgue and Baskerville families, who had become in-laws, held a friendly tournament.

The instructors strolled among the eight-year-old boys and girls sparring.

“If you hurt each other badly, it counts as a defeat. Keep this in mind!”

“Hehehe- you’re always so eager.”

Instructor Pavlov van Baskerville exclaimed.

And Deacon Barrymore, who was watching, smirked.

The two men began to laugh and chat.

“I hear you’re quite skilled, Deacon. I hear you’ve slain quite a few demons.”

“No matter how I’ve been serving the House of Baskerville my whole life, and even fought with the patriarch when I was younger.”

“Hahaha- speaking of which, the patriarch has also become much gentler as he gets older. I can’t imagine what has also become much he used to be like.”

“That’s true. How time flies.”

Just then.

…Boom!

A loud bang from the rehearsal hall interrupted their conversation.

“Let’s settle this today!”

“I’ll give you a good smashing!”

Highbro of House Baskerville and Highsis of House Morgue fought fiercely against each other.

“Let’s settle the matter!”

“All you can do is parrot your brother’s words, you idiot!”

As their swords and magic clashed, their younger siblings, Middlebro and Middlesis, could be seen holding their own.

Highbro, Middlebro, Lowbro.

Highsis, Middlesis, and Lowsis.

The triplets of Baskerville and the triplets of Morgue are fiercely competitive with each other.

Kwakwakwakwakwakwakwang!

Is it because of the commonality of having survived a war together and risen from the same battlefield at the same time?

Their rivalry was still burning brightly today.

…Of course.

“I guess it’s because my brothers are idiots that they don’t get tired.”

“My sisters are also dishonest.”

Looking at Lowbro and Lowsis holding hands tightly, it didn’t seem like that was the case.

A newspaper fluttered in the wind at the feet of Baskerville and Morgue, a handsome man and woman holding each other tightly.

[Outside] Marquis de Sade, 666th Failed Prison Break!

-Last night afternoon, another prison break occurred at Nouvelle Vague, the worst prison in the world…

-Marquis de Sade is the mastermind of this latest escape…

-His granddaughter, Professor Sadi, disguised herself as a guard and tried to rescue her grandfather, but…

-They were stopped by the combined efforts of Lieutenant General Souaré and Countess Isabella, who happened to be in the right place at the right time…

-The first person to discover Professor Sadi disguised as a prison guard was known as ‘Colonel Kirko’ and became the talk of the town…

-She was a prison guard among guards, an elite among elites, known for her stern and strict behavior…

-Professor Sadi, on the other hand, is known to have had a mysterious behavior since her escape…

◆

And it was not long ago that the Baskerville and Morgue families became in-laws.

“….”

There was another person who gained a new lease on life from the Day of Full Revival.

Unnamed minor graduate.

No one knew his name.

A retired soldier, whose last name is better known as ‘Baskerville’, was sitting alone at the fountain in the square.

“….”

He stood still for a while, taking in the scenery of the square.

Thinking about what to do with his life now that he’s out of the military.

Then.

“Buy flowers – fresh flowers -”

A girl walks by the fountain.

At that time.

“…!”

The girl suddenly stops walking in front of the fountain.

She walked up to the dazed man and handed him the flower in her hand.

It was a white, pristine lily.

The man looked at the flower, puzzled.

“I don’t have any money,”.

“I’m just giving it to you.”

The girl gave the man the flower.

“Why are you giving me this?”

“Just because, for some reason, I felt like I should.”

The girl smiled.

Then she asked the man

“My name is Nympet. What’s yours?”

“…Vikir.”

The girl smiled brightly as the man revealed his name.

“Thank you for protecting this world, Mr. Soldier.”

And with that. After she left, the man was left alone in the square with the flowers in his hand.

He stared at the flowers for a while, then muttered in a low voice.

“…I think I’ll start a flower shop.”

Then.

“There you are.”

An unfamiliar voice came from behind him.

A woman, her red hood pulled down deep, came to the man.

The man stared at her as if he’d never seen her before.

Then, the woman lifted the hood slightly to cover her face.

“…!”

Then, the man’s expression finally shows surprise.

“I see the war hero, The Empress of Heaven.”

“Oh, never mind. No need to say hello.”

The woman walks over with a brisk stride, then slows down again.

She leaned against the fountain’s railing, her gait awkward, clumsy, and somewhat shy.

She was right next to the man.

“ …What brings you here, Camus-nim?”

“Omit honorifics, we’re the same age.”

“You’re the same age as me? I didn’t know that.”

The woman smirked at the man’s comment.

Now, she looks into his face with a pointed gaze.

‘Don’t set your eyes on someone else’s husband.’

‘I am you, and you are me?’

‘Oh, I guess not!’

A voice crackled in her ear.

She smirked and muttered.

“I’m you and you’re me, but… This is this, that’s that, that’s this.”

“?”

The man stares at her in confusion.

She considers for a moment, then nods.

“The flower.”

“??”

“Can’t you give it to me?”

“????”

The man looked a little confused.

But the woman was undeterred.

“It’s just. I thought I’d get to know you a little better.”

That’s one thing.

This was this side’s business.

◆

“Wow. I guess everything worked out.”

“Yeah.”

Vikir smirked as Camus clapped her hands.

All of those who had died unjustly at the hands of the demon’s handiwork were brought back to life.

Camus had controlled the Magic of Full Revival to the finest degree, those who died regardless of whether they were evil or demonic were not revived.

Meanwhile.

“I suppose I’ll be revived in this world, too, since the Red Death was the work of a demon.”

“By the way, the original Vikir from this world is also very handsome. He’s like a mature middle-aged man….”

“Hehe, I heard you used to like flower arranging when you were younger. In a world without fighting, you’d be a flower artist.”

“The Nouvelle Vague on this side of the world has been restored, and judging from the newspapers, it looks like I’m alive and well here too. Happy.”

Aiyen, Dolores, Sinclaire, and Kirko, who had crossed over from their original world to this world, were still busy chatting.

Everyone on this side of the world, and everyone on that side of the world, had been brought back to life.

However, the six from this side of the line had decided that they would no longer interfere with their fate.

“Now we must plan our lives.”

“We’ll have to adapt to this world.”

“There are some subtle differences, but I don’t think it will be too difficult.”

“If you have money, you can live anywhere!”

“You guys are so easygoing. I like that.”

But.

“….”

In particular, Vikir still had unresolved concerns.

[…I see. A milestone. Was this my role.]

[Just by traveling here, you will get what you want].

[But even after you get what you want, you’ll have no choice but to come back here again].

[Because that’s what ‘he’ wants].

The words of Baal that day are stuck in his head.

Also.

‘And when the last moment of your life comes, come to this place.’

Is it the mystery of the Magic Abyss?

What was that voice that came from Baal’s head for an instant?

“….”

Vikir stroked his chin with his finger.

He didn’t know who the voice belonged to, but for some reason, there was a place that immediately came to mind.

“…Grave of Swords.”

Vikir let the words slip out of his mouth without realizing it.

And then.

“What? Grave of Swords? Where is that?”

“I heard about it from a revived soldier. It’s where the demons were mysteriously exterminated.”

“It’s in the Yuuni Salt Desert, right? But why is that….”

“What is it? I have a sudden suspicion. You don’t think he’s going to run off again, do you?”

“It’s possible if it’s him.”

The five women who were busy chatting overheard Vikir’s muttering.

Camus, Aiyen, Dolores, Sinclaire, and Kirko began to silently monitor Vikir’s condition.

“….”

“….”

“….”

“….”

“….”

And Vikir, who is completely unaware of this, mutters quietly to himself.

“Perhaps I should meet the man who guards it once more.”

An old memory flashes through his mind.

‘I will see him again someday.’

He clenched his fists.

…Kkwaag!

It was truly the first victory he felt in a long time.

Side Story Chapter 5

Wiiiiiing-

A dry wind blows.

His black robe fluttered in the breeze, and his long, graying beard.

Vikir walked across the white salt desert.

Hongmen(Great Door).

Once a vast expanse of greenery.

Now a wasteland of rock and salt.

Vikir turned his head and looked out over the desert horizon.

“….”

Desolate and lonely.

Age weathered many things.

Emotions, desires.

…But there was one emotion that still pulsed as strongly as it had in his youth.

A sense of victory.

Who is stronger.

It is greed and a delusion that a mere mortal who lives on swordsmanship would not let go of until death.

So Vikir moved on.

Throwing off all restraints and shackles, he surrendered himself to the instincts he had held in check for so long, so many years.

Wiiiiiiing-

A salty breeze blows in.

His sword sliced through the edge of the storm like a curtain, opening a path into the center of it.

Vikir found what he was looking for.

‘The Grave of Swords.’

An awl-like tower jutting out of the ground, it bathed in the blackness of the night sky and the red of blood.

It still stood there, unchanged from the last time he had seen it.

Vikir brushed the salt grains from his long beard and muttered to himself.

“…A true Baskerville is born in the ‘Cradle of Swords’.”

It’s a famous phrase passed down within the Baskerville family.

But. There’s a sentence behind it that’s actually hidden.

“…A true Baskerville dies in the ‘Grave of Swords’.”

At this point, he’s probably the only Baskerville who knows this phrase exists.

With that, Vikir entered the Grave of Swords.

The steps, each one pointed like an awl, rose high and steep.

This, too, was the same landscape.

A terribly desolate, suffocating, lonely place.

With each step he took, his whole body shuddered, and he felt like his stomach was being ripped open.

Countless swords are embedded in the floor, walls, and ceiling.

The water dripping from them was red and fishy.

Jeobeog- jeobeog- jeobeog- jeobeog-

Vikir continued climbing the stairs.

One step at a time.

In this way, it was sliced, chipped, cut out, and worn away, climbing towards the top.

And then he came face to face with it.

The iron throne at the top of the tower.

Then he heard a heavy, clanging voice, like the clash of steel against steel.

[This is the Grave of Swords, the final resting place of those who pursue the extreme will of the sword.]

And there stood a man in thick iron armor, his long white beard hanging down.

Beneath his white eyebrows, where the whites should have been, there was a hollow darkness, and in the center of it, eyes as red as the sun burned coldly.

His nose was sharp as a knife, his lips tightly pursed, and the dead, blue skin seemed to be so dry that it barely covered the skull.

His dark heavy armor and massive greatsword made the stronghold he was building seem even more imposing.

Vikir already knew his face.

Cane Corso Le Baskerville.

A former Seven Counts who had seen the turbulence of the Warring States, and the strongest man in the world that even the Age of Destruction had not been able to stop.

He stroked his snow-white beard and smiled wryly.

[It’s definitely a familiar face even though it’s my first time seeing it. Does the intuition of a superhuman who has reached the realm of the supreme transcend even space and time?]

Vikir didn’t bother to answer his question.

‘It reminds me of old times. When I first met him, I had a hard time even receiving a single sword slash.’

I wonder how it is now.

He hadn’t really had a chance to test his strength since the war with the demons ended, and this was a good opportunity.

…Chaang!

Vikir drew his favorite sword, Beelzebub, which had been with him all his life.

The two swords clashed.

Cane Corso swings his large serrated greatsword, and Vikir plunges the long, awl-like shaft of Beelzebub through the swirling maelstrom of strikes.

Baskerville’s 9th Form and Baskerville’s 9th Form.

It was only a matter of moments before they clashed.

Nine teeth against nine teeth.

“…!”

Vikir stopped moving as if struck by lightning.

A moment too late.

His mind raced with the many truths he had seen in the Magic Abyss.

Meanwhile, something that had been blocked for a long time was opened up.

…Ppajig!

Space and time began to distort.

A tiny speck of light flickered amidst the fierce clash of the nine teeth.

A tooth protruded from the space where dust, gas, clouds, and star clusters floated.

It was the tenth tooth.

It was so small it was barely visible, but it was clearly attached to the other nine teeth.

…Flash!

The moment it pierced his body, Cane Corso thought.

[… Is it the last one?]

As if in response to this thought.

Ppagag!

The sword hilt of his trusty companion, ‘Fragarach’, snapped in half.

Cane Corso gazed warmly at the broken serrated sword with warm eyes and muttered.

[I see, now you’re going to get your Godhood, congratulations.]

The black energy within Fragarach rose into the sky.

Cane Corso’s body also turned to red dust and began to fade away.

[I may not have become a Sword God, but I was able to become a Sword Immortal. I’ll be content to serve as a milestone for future generations.]

He let himself be carried away by the storm of slashes created by the clash of swords.

It was the end of a man who had spent his life obsessed with the sword.

….

…And then.

The storm subsided.

Only one man remained. Vikir alone.

[Your birth will be like the birth of the sword, and your death will be like the death of the sword.]

The voice of Cane Corso, now fading away, drifted away.

Just then.

“Ouch, you burn!”

There is a loud voice behind him.

Vikir turned around in surprise to see familiar faces standing there.

“I knew you’d come this way.”

“I’ve been keeping an eye on this place ever since I heard you mutter something once.”

“Everyone is so paranoid….”

“We have a former prison guard who is a master of tracking.”

“Uh, you mean me? I’m a former prison guard, but I’m not very good at tracking unless you count arrests.”

Camus, Aiyen, Dolores, Sinclaire, Kirko.

All of his friends from the other world were there.

“I, I was going to come alone, but how….”

On rare occasions, Vikir even stuttered.

It was Camus who stepped forward.

“You should have brought me, if not the others. You don’t even know how to open the gate to the Magic Abyss.”

“….”

Vikir shut his mouth.

Camus stepped into the Grave of Swords of his own accord and stared at the giant sigil carved into the bottom of the spiral staircase.

“…The traces of ten mana wheels.”

Camus looked at the magic circle engraved on the floor and the marks of the mana injection.

“It’s similar to a Full Revival Magic, but far more noble, greater, and powerful. … I can’t believe this kind of magic exists in the world. What was its purpose?”

“It’s almost as if it symbolizes the truth itself, though it’s not for me to know what sister Camus doesn’t know….”

Even Sinclaire, who was no stranger to magic, was breaking out in a cold sweat.

Aiyen, Dolores, and Kirko put their heads together.

“I can tell by the trail. There must have been a huge explosion.”

“From what I’ve heard, this area used to be densely forested. Maybe the explosion turned it into a salt desert….”

“Maybe there was a meteorite or something, and that would explain the two gaps in human history.”

And it was Camus who summarized all these opinions into one.

“We’ll find out when we go there again.”

A second expedition into the Magic Abyss.

This opinion was the only one that matched Vikir’s.

◆

Vikir and Camus reached the Magic Abyss once again.

After passing through the ‘Five Fingers of the Creator’ area, they saw a familiar phrase.

-All things are born in the Magic Abyss and return to the Magic Abyss.

-One day, when the stars move, a door will open to a new level and all things will come to their inevitable end.

These two phrases stand like gatekeepers of timeless nothingness.

Camus stretched out the roots of the ghost tree and twisted the locks on the pillars and between the pillars.

Eight doors opened, and only then did Vikir come face to face with something.

It was a spirit being in the form of a human, a female form.

Vikir knew the moment he saw it.

‘Motherhood (Maternal).’

The being that was now radiating a bright light in front of him was his distant ancestor, the ‘First Mother’.

And the mother said to Vikir, and to her son.

[I missed you].

“….”

Vikir couldn’t say anything.

And the mother opened her mouth once more.

[I was so worried about you that I couldn’t leave. I don’t know how many generations have passed, but you are still my daughters and sons.]

The mother hugged her son tightly.

Then she spoke in a warm, moist voice.

[Now I can finally leave in peace, to where he has gone.]

“Where are you going?”

Vikir asked, and the mother replied.

[To grab him by the hair].

“…?”

At Vikir’s puzzled expression, she reached out and stroked his head.

[Live].

“….?”

[Live. Live to the fullest. Live to your heart’s content. Live this world cheerfully.]

The mother seemed to know and understand what Vikir had come here for.

But Vikir still didn’t know what to do.

“Can’t I go with you?”

The mother shook her head at the question.

[When the last moment of your life comes, a long time later, a very long time later, come to this place.]

“….”

[Until then, enjoy common flirtation and ordinary self-satisfaction, for that is the highest cheerfulness, awareness, and love.]

That was his last word with his mother.

◆

Vikir returned from the Magic Abyss.

He spent a very long time in this world.

His beautiful wives, his cheerful children, and his happy times with them passed like a dream of the Nine Clouds.

How much time had passed?

When all the crimson dust of this world was covered by the sands of time and could no longer decay.

For the third time in his life, Vikir traveled to the Magic Abyss.

Pis-

On his first visit, he learned the Full Revival Magic and the truths of the 10 Form.

On his second visit, he met his first mother.

What will he do on his third visit?

“…………”

Without a word, Vikir walked up the stairs of dust, clouds, and stars that appeared before him, one by one.

And at the end of the staircase, at the edge of the Magic Abyss, he came face to face with someone sitting on the edge.

‘The Five Fingers of the Creator.’

Beyond the five giant fingers glowed the endless jade throne, or rather, the constellation.

An old man sat there.

He fiddled with a handful of personalized glass beads.

“…………”

With a look on his face that Vikir wasn’t sure what to make of.